The Duel Carnival Tournament Finals have begun at last!
The Duel Coasters!
This is my first time Dueling on a roller coaster!
It's so fun!
Wait, what?
Who the heck're these guys?
They're aiming for me in a three-on-one match?
But I won't lose!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
They went and Summoned Monsters!
That means they plan to make this three-on-one!
It's suddenly become a three-on-one battle.
Whoa! Waiting to pursue Contestant Tsukumo at the high end was none other than
the Fallguys, who made it through the preliminaries using their exceptional team plays as a weapon!
And they have already Summoned Monsters!
Now then, don't miss a second of this Duel that's about to begin!
Heart Burning!
Don't lose, Yuma!
Bring it to 'em!
I can't wait.
How will those prize hunters deal with Yuma?
We just need to crush this Yuma Tsukumo brat?
That is the only way you people will receive the reward you desire.
I like the sound of that.
It's settled, Big Bro.
We'll settle on those agreements. We'll crush him as you wish. You can count on us.
But it isn't fun if you simply crush him.
I want to see it.
Yuma Tsukumo's strength.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
"Number 52:
The Duel Coasters Vs the Rampaging Train!!"
Take this!
Shit! They're enemies standing in our way!
We've got no choice but to fight them!
I Summon Gagaga Kaiser!
Gagaga Kaiser! Attack the Saucer in the front!
Yes! You did it!
Wait, Yuma. Now isn't the time to be celebrating.
Look at their Monsters.
Their Attack Points went up?!
Wh-Why?
This is the effect of the Magnet Monsters we Fallguys control.
When an ally Monster with "Magnet" in their name is destroyed in battle,
it increases the Attack Power of the remaining Monsters by 400 points.
The real battle begins now!
Saucer! Attack Gagaga Kaiser!
They killed each other?!
But this is...
My Eagle's Attack Power rises to 2000!
Go on! Direct Attack!
That brings the first battle to a close.
The Attack Points that were increased will now return to normal.
Huh? They got hit fair-and-square.
You're stronger than this, aren't you?
Hurry and show me your strength!
I have no business with those not holding Numbers!
Get lost!
Go! Reverse Buster!
Direct Attack!
Tron! V! I swear I'll kill the both of you!
Kaito...
Don't overdo it...
This way and that way, fierce battles are beginning to unfold!
But the hottest of them all, as I thought,
is over there!
Contestant Tsukumo and the Fallguys!
Will Contestant Tsukumo fall victim to them as one would expect?!
Get fired up! Heart Burning!
I play Magnet Kong Epsilon!
Magnet Crocodile Zeta!
- Summon!
Now we've been surrounded by Monsters again!
Even if I battle them like this...
It will only increase the Attack Power of the remaining Monsters.
What should I do?
Yuma, use Gogogo Golem from your hand.
Huh?
Gogogo Golem won't be destroyed in battle once per turn when it's in Defense Mode.
That's it! If I'm able to evade their attacks and use that time to change our lane...
I Summon Gogogo Golem!
Now! The second battle begins!
Crocodile Zeta, attack Gogogo Golem!
Croc Attack!!
Nice one, Gogogo Golem!
Epsilon, attack Gogogo Golem!
Kong Punch!!
Now! Change our lane before we get hit by the third attack!
Right!
We already saw through that trick!
Go on, Coyote!
There!
What?! The lane's been closed off!
So this is the Fallguys' team play...
He's only got 1000 Life Points left.
My Eagle Delta has 1200 Attack Points.
If this Direct Attack goes through...
We'll have carried out our agreement with Tron.
Then we'll get our hands on a ton of cash!
Yuma!
Darn! What should we do?
This ends it!
Go, Magnet Eagle Delta! Attack Yuma direct-
What!?
Who the hell is this guy?!
Wh-Who in the world are you!?
Three-on-one is such cowardly behavior!
I came to assist you, Yuma!
Y-You!?
Anna!?
What are you doing here?!
Save the explanation for later!
For now, let's crush these guys!
Go, Rocket Arrow!
It's got 5000 Attack Points!?
Big Bro, let me!
You saved us, Anna!
But I thought you weren't participating in the Duel Carnival!
Don't worry about the minor details. You're a man, aren't you?
You didn't...
What the?!
No one even attacked it!
If you don't send five cards from your hand to the Graveyard
after Rocket Arrow battles, it blows itself up.
You forget something really important!
Well, I told you not to worry about the minor details!
Tch, what're you standing around chatting for?!
I activate the Magic Card, Magnet Reborn, from my hand!
I pay 500 of my Life to bring back Crocodile Zeta from my Graveyard!
Go! Crocodile Zeta!
Get out of there, Anna!
What an annoying girl! I'll crush you first!
Anna! It's a Draw Lane! Go on and draw!
Draw!
I Summon Courageous Locomotive Brave Pappo!
I activate the Magic Card, Magnet Fusion, from my hand!
I release Eagle Delta, Crocodile Zeta, and King Eplison!
Show yourself! Super Electromagnetic Dragon - Magnedragon!
3500 Attack Points!?
Yuma! Anna is...
Yeah! Now it's my turn to save her!
I draw!
I Summon Bull Blader!
Just wait, Anna! I'm gonna change our lane!
Yuma, in front of you!
What!?
I won't let you change your lane!
Calm down. There's got to be another crossroad.
You won't make it! Draw!
I Summon Magnet Pandoll!
Draw! I Summon Magnet Jammer!
Magnedragon, attack Brave Poppo!
Magne Inferno!!
When Magnedragon destroys a Monster...
the opponent takes damage equal to its Attack Power!
Anna!
Yuma! If this keeps up, Anna will...
But we're blocked from the front and the back.
Since it's come to this, we'll just have to force a path open!
Go, Bull Blader!
Attack Pandoll!
But I use this timing to activate Pandoll's effect!
The moment it's destroyed, it inflicts 200 points of damage on my opponent!
Then I activate the Magic Card, Magnet Reborn, from my hand!
I pay 500 of my Life Points to return Pandoll from the Graveyard!
Come at me as many times as you want.
I'll cut down your Life point by point!
If you keep doing that over and over, your Life will drop to zero...
I'm fine with that.
We're a team.
Even if you deplete mine or Jackal's Life, as long as Brother Wolf has some left...
I'll crush you and we'll be rolling in dough!
Dough?!
What in the world are they talking about?
We aren't after the championship.
We want money!
We entered a contract stating we have to crush you in order to get the money!
N-No way!
Crush me? Who would do something like that?
Beats me.
Draw!
In my current situation, this guy's the only one I can Summon. It can't be helped!
Strongarm Express Trolleyrolley, please protect me!
1000 Defense Points?
That won't protect you from my Magnedragon!
Go, Bull Blader! Attack Pandoll!
It's useless to struggle!
You won't ever be able to pull down our formation.
Your friend will be finished off by Brother Wolf!
I gotta do something! If this keeps up, Anna will...!
But in this situation...
The finishing blow!
Anna!
I'm not liking your mood, Yuma!
I use Heroic Challenger - Spartas to attack Magnet Jammer!
Gauche!
What the?!
Oh crap! I activate Magnet Jammer's Monster Effect!
It returns both our Monsters to our hands!
Impudent mood-killer...
Hey, Yuma! I'll take this guy off your hands!
Thanks a bunch! I'm in your debt!
I'll return my debt from before, Anna!
Yuma!
Anna!
Go, Bull Blader!
You fool!
Do you really think your 1600 Attack Power Bull Blader
can beat my 3500 Attack Power Magnedragon?!
We'll see!
Bull Blader can negate battle damage and destroy the opponent's Monster!
What did you say?!
You didn't need to do that! I wouldn't get damaged by a guy like him!
Gosh! After you went out of your way to save her!
I'm the one who saved you before!
Yeah! Thanks a lot, Anna.
Huh? It's not like you need to praise me or anything...
You look really pleased to me!
How dare they mock me...!
I'll crush Yuma Tsukumo!
I'll start by negating Bull Blader's Monster Effect!
Use our Final Formation!
- Roger!
- Draw!
- I Summon Magnet Chameleon!
Yuma Tsukumo!
When there's two Magnet Chameleons on the field, the opponent's Monster's effects are negated!
You can't use the effect of your Bull Blader anymore!
What!?
I won't let you!
Draw!
I Summon Heroic Challenger - Extra Sword!
I won't allow Yuma to be taken out by you people!
Coyote!
Shit!
You won't get away!
Yuma! He's my opponent!
Let me do this!
Anna!
In that case, I'll lend you my strength!
This makes no sense! There may be three people here, but only one of us can battle him!
No, it may be possible if you're on the same lane.
Eh?
Yuma, you've got Bull Blader and Anna's got Trolleyrolley.
With Gauche's Extra Sword, they're all Level Fours.
If you've got three Level Four Monsters gathered...
An Xyz Summon!
That's right. It's time to join our hearts together.
Okay!
I Overlay my Level Four Bull Blader with Anna's Trolleyrolley and Gauche's Extra Sword!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, One-Eyed Skill Gainer!
2500 Attack Points?
Hmph! Hardly a threat to my 3500 Attack Power Magnedragon!
When Extra Sword becomes an Overlay Unit, its effect increases its Attack Power by 1000 points!
And my Trolleyrolley has an effect that increases its Attack Power by 800 points!
What the hell?! It's got 4300 Attack Points?!
Yuma, use its Monster Effect!
Right! I then activate Skill Gainer's Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can use the opponent's Monster's effect myself!
So I'll steal Magnedragon's effect!
Not good...
My Magnedragon's effect deals the Attack Power of the Monster it destroys as damage to the opposing player!
I'll take 800 Battle Damage.
And if I take another 3500 points of Effect Damage...
I'll lose by a One Turn Kill...
Take this! This is the bond we share with our friends!
Like I'll let you!
What!?
I won't let my brother be taken down!
Jackal!!
So you ran away! See you!
Enough. We won.
Yeah, by working together.
That was well done!
Contestant Tsukumo used the combined power of his friends
and managed to stop the three Fallguys trio and force them to retreat in defeat!
They did it!
Yuma-kun!
He won! That was so cool!
Shit... Shit...! Shit!
They're unforgivable...
Huh? So you aren't one of the Tournament Finalists?
R-Right...
Goodness... Your spirit is outrageous.
You tied up one of the Tournament Finalists and switched places with them?!
Tokunosuke did the same thing...
I had no choice!
I mean... I wanted to meet you...
Huh? What's that?!
Magnedragon! That guy came back!
I'm here to avenge Jackal and Coyote!
Yuma, this is bad!
I activate the Magic Card, Direct Magnet, from my hand!
I pay half of my Life...
...and halve my Monster's Attack Points in order to attack you directly!
Take this!!
No you don't!
I Special Summon Construction Train Signal Red!
When the enemy attacks directly, Signal Red can force the two to battle!
Anna!!
Anna...
That girl got in the way again!
This time will be a genuine Direct Attack!
Go, Skill Gainer!
Dark Blade!
The loser of the Duel shall be ejected from the lane.
You did it!
You did it, Yuma.
Thank you, Anna. It was thanks to you.
I have faith in you. Don't lose on me.
Later. You better get the championship!
Man, the mood's gettin' really good.
Friendship... Bonds... I see now.
So this is Yuma Tsukumo's power.
The fierce battles that unfolded here in the Park Section have now come to a close!
Those who broke through and qualified shall head toward the next obstacle; the Underground Section!
I'm gonna do it! I'm definitely gonna win!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Now, the battle in the Underground Section Finals has finally started!
Since everyone is busy battling, I'll go all out!
But I can’t see anything in the darkness!
Yuma, the key is to find the troubled Duelists here!
Whoa! A Trap Card?!
Geez, what can you do with only 200 Life Points?
What?! Gauche’s opponent…
That’s…
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
The Fated Rail: Try your Luck on a Trap Card?!
Hey, wait!!