Resume the Numbers Hunt!
Tsukumo Yuma has a very strange pendant...
I didn't see it coming at all,
that the Numbers Hunter would attack me again.
In order to protect Emperor's Key, Shark's soul was absorbed.
In the end the Emperor's Key was stolen anyway.
Not to mention, Astral is still inside Emperor's Key.
Just wait, Astral, I'm coming to save you!
Shark! Shark! Shark!
Get a hold of yourself Shark!
What are the results?
Yes sir, I'm analyzing it right now.
Kaito-sama, why are you so obsessed with this pendant?
I want to know the truth of this matter.
Dr. Faker chose not to tell me everything,
Therefore, I shall find out myself!
Kaito-sama, don't tell me that, you're trying to outsmart Dr. Faker-sama?
Just shut up and focus on your analysis.
Understood!
The doctors said there's no abnormality in his body.
Then, why is he still in this coma?
To summarise then, he's...
...lost his consciousness
No.
Shark's soul was absorbed.
His soul was absorbed?
If that's so, Yuma-kun, what's going on here?
If you lose a duel to him...
that Kaito-guy will seize the Numbers card along with the victim's soul!
And now he has my Emperor's Key.
Astral is still inside there!
Astral you say?
Yes. There is a unique space inside Emperor's Key.
He always stays in that place if he's not with me.
In conclusion, Shark's soul and Astral who is inside Emperor's Key, are all in Kaito's hands now?
Then let's find Kaito!
But how do we find him?
Since he took that key, that must mean he's using it for research purposes!
Yo summarise, he's trying to analyze it using a computer!
Yuma-kun, maybe we can find Emperor's Key after all!
What is this?
What happened?
Unbelievable! There is another gravitational field inside!
Gravitational field? What is it?
In other words, the interior of this pendant is connected with a Different Dimension.
Don't tell me... it's the Astral world?
Can you open an entrance?
Understood!
Spread the Computer Virus?
There is no other way!
The guy who stole the Emperor's Key from Yuma-kun, should be researching it with a computer right now!
In other words, we just need to hack into it successfully and find that data...
It should be a piece of cake considering your computer skills!
But still...
I beg you, Sensei!
If you don't, Shark and Astral will never come back!
Sensei, this way...
Sensei, can't you help us?
Sensei, if you don't, then I will tell everyone that you're the one who spread the Bugman Virus!
Wha- What?
Back then, Sensei,... you caused a heck of a lot chaos in the city.
You... about that...
He said OK!
Awesome!
Then let's hurry, Sensei, quick!
Yuma!
Ah... Kotori?!
After finding the whereabouts of Kaito, you'll go after him?
...and you'll duel him, right?
Kotori...
I understand... that you want to save Astral and Shark...
...but...
Don't worry - it's gonna be alright.
I definitely won't lose to that Kaito-guy!
Hm...
But, class rep, is it really OK to spread the computer virus around?
Of course! Although it's a virus, it's not a spam program.
This program can find all the data about Emperor's Key throughout the network!
By using the virus made by Sensei, we will definitely find Yuma-kun's Emperor's key!
Why does Sensei's virus take the shape of Bugman?
Ah!
Does it have any connection with the previous bugman incident?
Surely that can't be related to you, right Sensei?
...Alright, the modification of the virus is done, go, BUGMAN!
I'm counting on you, Bugman!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
There's no response.
The fated Duel, Kaito vs Astral
Numbers 22:
Looks like material from Earth can't create any reactions.
Then try 'Barrier Light'.
Huh?
Use 'Barrier Light'.
After all, we obtained that from the Balian World.
I expect no less from Kaito-sama! I never even thought of that.
But the important 'Barrier Light' is...
Use your own.
Huh?! Without that energy source I can't move!
It's perfectly fine to just use a little. Hurry up!
Why... why... Understood...
My important, most important energy, allow me to give up a chunk of you...
I'll use the barrier light close to the Emperor's Key.
Oh, the pendent created a resonance!
Currently the interior mass is increasing,
Also changes have occurred in gravitation.
What's this?!
A gate has opened...
Is this the entrance to the Astral world?
Kaito-sama!
What is this space?
Where... where is it?
Finally! A response!
That's...!
It seems to be the Warehouse in the 4th Terminal managed by Heartland.
The Emperor's Key is over there!
Yuma!
I found you!
Are you the messenger from the Astral world?
Kaito, so it's you.
Why do you know my name?
I fought with you once.
With me?
These Numbers...
I see, so the origin of the Numbers attached itself to Yuma Tsukumo.
Did you take the Emperor's Key from Yuma-kun?
So this thing is called the Emperor's Key.
Why are you trying to find the Numbers?
I'm the one who should be asking that.
Numbers are... the pieces of my memory.
What? Memory you say?
That's right, that is why I am collecting the Numbers.
But why are you also doing that?
To learn about the Astral world and the Numbers,
and to learn the secrets of the Balian World.
Balian...?
I shall recover all the Numbers and find the answers.
Now, hand over all of your Numbers.
So are we betting on each others Numbers?
Destiny has opened the gate. Now, duel me!
Wait for me, Astral!
Duel Mode, Photon Change!
Now, let the hunt for all of your Numbers begin!
Kaito... so the time for our battle has finally arrived.
No more running or hiding...
Let's go!
DUEL!
Huh?
What is it?
Don't tell me Astral is...
My turn! Draw!
I play a Monster in face-down defense position!
Then I set one card and end my turn!
The card I set is Gogogo Golem,
When it is in defense position, once per turn it cannot be destroyed by battle.
And the other card I set is the trap card Battle Break.
With this card, when my opponent's monster declares an attack,
That monster will be destroyed and the Battle Phase will end.
Now, how will you deal with this, Kaito!
My turn, draw!
First I will seal off your set card!
I summon Reverse Buster!
When Reverse Buster battles, it can seal the opponent's Magic and Trap cards.
Go, Reverse Buster, attack the Monster in face-down defense position!
I thought it'd be Gogogo Golem!
I activate the effect of Reverse Buster!
What?!
When Reverse Buster battles a Monster in face-down defense position,
it can destroy that monster without applying Damage Calculation!
The timing of activation for Gogogo Golem's destruction-evading ability only applies during battle!
It cannot use its immunity against the destruction by card effects!
Also, when Reverse Buster destroys a Monster in face-down defense position through this effect,
its attack points increase by 500!
An attack power of 2000!
The conditions for Kaito to summon his Ace Monster Galaxy-Eyes are,
to release 2 Monsters with 2000 or more attack!
Is this monster a preparation to summon Galaxy-Eyes?
Tch... anyway, if you think you can destroy my defense with a single Monster, you're...
I set one card, and end my turn.
Well done, Kaito.
Your Dueling skills have always exceeded my expectations.
Such an honor, but you won't lower my guard with flattery.
That's not my goal.
You are the strongest duelist I know of.
Your Duel is filled with your soul.
What made you that way?
Ah... but can you really afford to observe me like that?
I'll just say that I'm shouldering something different than what you guys normally do.
That's how it is.
Your collecting of Numbers is related to that?
I have no intention of telling you, someone who is about to disappear.
I see... what a shame.
I'm fascinated by you, you seem similar to Yuma.
What did you say?
That's right, ever since I was attached to Yuma,
I've been able to feel his heart.
Deep inside Yuma's heart, there is the pain of losing his parents.
And within that pain, there is determination to believe in his parents' words.
You're saying... I'm the same as him?
That's right.
Stop joking around! I've never had parents to begin with, I only have Haruto!
Haruto?
Stop talking nonsense, let's resume the duel!
Now, it's your turn!
My turn! Draw!
I summon Gogogo Giant!
When this card is successfully summoned ,
I can special summon Gogogo Golem from my graveyard in defense position!
And when this effect is used, Gogogo Giant is switched to defense position!
Now there are 2 Level 4 monsters on this guy's field.
So here it comes, Aspiring Emperor Hope.
Kaito's set card is the main problem.
Is that card a trap to counter my Numbers?
I activate the Continuous Magic card from my hand, Double Defender!
When there are 2 monsters in face-up defense position, this card allows me to
once per turn, negate one attack from my opponent's monsters.
I set one card, and end my turn!
I thought you were going to summon your ace Hope.
But if you summoned Hope, Gogogo Giant and Gogogo Golem which are in defense position would disappear.
Even if you have Hope's ability, the number of total defenses will decrease.
Those 2 set cards are to deal with my attacks, right?
Were you worrying about my set card?
Or are you simply afraid of Galaxy Eyes?
My turn, draw!
I activate the magic card Photon Hurricane!
This card returns the Magic and Trap cards on my opponent's field to their hand, up the number of cards in my hand!
Now all of your set cards are back in your hand!
What the?!
That's right, the set card you were afraid of...
... was just a Magic card.
That's right, there was no card to stop your attack!
If you had attacked last turn, now the situation would be much different.
I release Reverse Buster to advance summon Photon Leo!
I activate the effect of Photon Leo!
Howling Blow!
When this card is summoned successfully,
The opponent must shuffle their hand into their deck, and draw the same number of cards.
Now, draw your new cards!
Now all of your strategies go back to zero.
I'm a bit disappointed.
All your strategies have been all about defense.
A bit too afraid, aren't you?
Open - open the door!
Open... open up...
Yuma, the deck again!
Astral is fighting. Astral is facing grave danger!
But how...?!
No clue, I just know it!
He's fighting right now.
Astral? With whom?
With the Numbers Hunter?
Darn! Open, open the door!
I activate the Equip Magic card Photon Spear and equip it to Photon Leo!
When the monster equipped with photon Spear attacks a monster in defense position,
If its ATK exceeds that monster's DEF, it inflicts the difference as battle damage to my opponent!
Photon Leo, attack Gogogo Giant!
Silver Fang!
Was I afraid of him without realizing it?
I can't win against Kaito this way...
Looks like I forgot my... most important lesson.
Its no use...
Damn it!
We came this far...
In the end... I couldn't save Astral and Shark...
Yuma.
Yuma!
Get a hold of yourself! You can't be the first to give up!
Kotori...
That... that's right.
I may be the only one who can save Astral.
Open up!
Open! OPEN!
Open! Open!
The gate opened?
I just implanted a virus into the security system there.
Hurry up and infiltrate!
That's awesome, Ukyo-Sensei! Let's go, everyone!
Aaaa... Kaito-sama, Kaito-sama, are you all right?
Please, if you are fine, please do reply.
OH! EEH? What is this?
Something big, Something big...
Wha- what is it?
Invaders detected at area 3! Invaders detected...
Who are those guys? Wha... what should I do?
If I try anything reckless now, he will turn me into scraps!
You aren't that bad.
But I suggest you give up this duel.
For you to win against me, your heart needs to be stronger!
No... I won't give up!
Indeed my former self would have given up already,
But, I won't give up now!
Thanks to my most important friend, I have learned to bring it to 'em!
Did everyone already vote?
It's the Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal popularity contest for Numbers!
Which Numbers will be our first?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
It's ZeXal.
The miraculous force which can save my world...
We have to get it! No matter at what price!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal! The soul Xyz Summon! ZeXal!!!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
It's the second Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal popularity contest!
Let's Summon the six remaining ones!
No. 10: Illumiknight!
No. 20: Gig-Anto Brilli-Ant!
No. 12: Armored Ninja - Crimson Shadow!
No. 16: Ruler of Color - Shock Ruler!
No. 11: Big Eye!
Chaos No. 39: Utopia Ray!
On our home webpage from TV-Tokyo you can tell us which is your favourite!