Are you ready for your repentance?!
Go! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
Faker...!
Your attacks won't make it past a genius mind like mine!
Behold! This is Heart eartH's true form!
Number 92! Heart eartH Dragon!
Why on earth is there a new Number on his field!?
I'll explain it to you fools!
When Heart-eartH has no Overlay Units while being attacked,
by using Heart-eartH as an Overlay Unit,
I can Special Summon Heart-eartH Dragon!
And when this Monster has been Special Summoned successfully,
all opposing Attack Position Monsters
are changed into Defense Position!
Well, you were fools to try to fight back against a genius!
Bow down before Heart-eartH Dragon!
So our Monsters were changed to Defense Mode before the damage could reach.
So that's why the attack stopped!
It still had an effect like this?
Here I go. Trap, activate!
Fake Form!
When your Monsters have been changed into Defense Mode,
this card deals you 400 damage for each Monster!
What?!
Guys!
Yuma...
It's over now!
You take 1200 damage!
Oh crap!
I activate Kuriphoton's effect!
By sending this card from my hand to the Graveyard,
and paying half of my Life...
...the Effect Damage is negated!
Kaito!?
Hey, is your body...?!
Calm down!
I can't afford to break down yet...
Not until I have defeated you, Dr. Faker!
You fool!
Had you been defeated, you would not have had to suffer on!
My turn! Draw!
"I will defeat you?" Didn't you hear me?
Your defeat is coming closer step by step,
heralding the extinction of the Astral World!
Heart-eartH Dragon, attack Shark Drake!
What'd you say?
He's attacking with Zero Attack Points?!
Not only is Heart-eartH Dragon not destroyed in battle,
but I Battle Damage against me is negated,
while you guys receive the original damage in my stead!
What?!
I see...
By using a Zero Attack Power Monster to attack the 2100 Defense Power Shark Drake,
the result is 2100 from the original damage.
It's all negated on his end and bounced back to us!
Our Life is a mere 600.
If we get hit by 2100 damage...!
Go! Heart Break Cannon!
N-No way...!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
I won't let you! Trap, activate!
Escape Lure!
This card changes the attack target to a different Monster,
"Numbers 70: The Terrifying, Most Sinister Dragon Appears!
The False Skeletal God Dragon, Heart-eartH Dragon!"
and halves the resulting Battle Damage!
I change the attack target to Hope!
Fool! There's no sense in doing that!
Why is he choosing Hope as the attack target?
Yuma, think...
If we reduce that guy's damage, our damage will be reduced!
I see!
Trap, activate! Half Unbreak!
This card halves the Battle Damage!
I will use this effect...
on Heart-eartH Dragon!
You used the Trap to protect my Monster?
That's right! By reducing the damage you would receive,
the damage sent back to us is reduced as well!
That way the damage for Heart-eartH Dragon is 500!
That means we only take 500 damage!
Tch... Useless struggle...
But now I will activate another effect of Heart-eartH Dragon!
Not only is the Battle Damage inflicted on me negated,
but I gain that amount of Life instead!
I set one card and end my turn!
Guys... Good luck!
All hope is.... resting on you three.
Yuma, Ryouga. You braved this well.
You're still patronizing even now?
Damn... Our Life is down to 100 now.
If this goes on...
What's wrong, Yuma?
If you're going to whine, lie down there and go to sleep!
Hey... I-I'm not whining at all!
Like heck will I give up!
Astral is waiting for me to save him!
I will definitely... rescue you!
I'll bring it to 'em!
My turn! Draw!
Look, Astral!
Go, Hope!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope will be the Xyz Material!
Chaos Xyz Change!
The messenger who changes chaos into light!
Come forth, Chaos Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Chaos Numbers. The new power of the Numbers.
But something like that won't beat my Heart-eartH Dragon!
Sure, Heart-eartH Dragon can negate attacks,
and bounce back the damage to us.
But... I'm sure there's something in my hand.
Think... think hard...
That's it!
Go, Hope Ray!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!
Did you finally make up your mind
to throw your life down the drain?
Don't joke around!
I haven't given up at all!
From my hand, I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Gamusharush!
With Gamusharush, I can set the Attack Power of my battling Monster to zero,
and the opposing player will receive 600 points of damage.
I set one card and end my turn!
I see. You actually put a bit of thought into that one.
If attacks won't work, you just reduce his Life with effects.
You're being way too reckless for a mere 600 points of damage.
With the power of our bonds, we will beat this guy!
I'm counting on you, Shark!
My turn! Draw!
Just a bit longer...
At this moment, the effect of Heart-eartH Dragon activates!
After this monster was special summoned,
all cards then Summoned or set on the opponent's field...
...will be Banished on the next turn!
What did you say?!
My Hope Ray is...!
Bonds, you say? Such stupidity.
Things like that are merely an illusion!
If it really exists, show it to me!
The thing you call the "power of your bonds".
It's true that you can't actually see the bonds you share with someone.
They're something deep down within your heart that connects with another's!
As long as they exist, our feelings always will reach one another!
Shark...
With Marine Biting Shark Drake, I will...
...Chaos Xyz Change!
With Shark Drake as Xyz Material, I Special Summon a Chaos Number!
Come forth, Chaos Number 32!
Biting Marine Serpent Shark Drake Weiss!
I won't give up either. I'll it to show him.
My own way to 'Bring it to 'em!
I activate the Magic Card, Deep Sea Attack!
With this card, I send a Water-Attribute Monster with 2000 or more Attack Points from my hand to the Graveyard,
and on this turn, one Monster on my field can attack the opponent directly!
I send Jawsman to the Graveyard!
With this, Shark Drake Weiss can attack directly!
Shark Drake Weiss, direct attack on Dr. Faker!
Depth Chaos Bite!
He avoided Heart-eartH Dragon by attacking Faker!
You did it, Shark!
You fool!
Trap, activate!
Fake Life!
This card can negate the damage from a direct attack,
and then let me recover that amount of Life Points instead!
That darn Faker increased his Life Points again!
I set one card and my tu-...
...end my turn.
Shark!
Ryouga,
Because of Byron's scheme, you lost your pride and your younger sister...
...and now you're going to lose yourself in the most pathetic way?
Shark! Hey, what happened?!
You're injured?!
It's no big deal!
But...!
Ryouga.
Your feelings... I've received all of them!
Let's go! My turn! Draw!
You still don't seem to understand!
Heart-eartH Dragon's effect activates!
Your cards will be Banished!
Disappear, Shark Drake Weiss!
Now try to prove it to me!
What those bonds of yours are all about!
Huh?
I've been waiting for this moment, Dr. Faker!
You're the one who fell for it!
What did you say?
Trap, activate! Xyz-Dimension Splash!
When this card gets Banished by my opponent,
I can Special Summon two Level Eight Water-Attribute Monsters from my deck.
A Trap that activates when it's Banished?!
I Special Summon two Ancient Shark Hyper Megalodons!
The effects of the Monsters Summoned by this effect are negated,
and they can neither attack nor be released!
So you took advantage of Heart-eartH Dragon's effect?
I did say our feelings would definitely reach you!
Kaito...
I'm entrusting you... with this...
The last of my...
Hope!
Shark!
Ryouga...
I Overlay the Level Eight Galaxy-Eyes and the two Hyper Megalodons!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Great Galaxy of Reversal!
Become the rolling waves of light and show your mighty form!
Descend, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
I'm counting on you, Kaito.
Damn...
I can't break down yet...
Yuma, Ryouga...
This is my power!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes' effect activates!
When this Monster has been Summoned successfully,
the effects of all other Monsters on the field are negated!
Photon Howling!
What?!
With this, the effects of Heart-eartH Dragon are negated!
Then, by detaching one Overlay Unit,
all Overlay Units from all other Monsters on the field will be absorbed!
Then, for this turn, its Attack Power will
increase by 500 points for each Overlay Unit absorbed!
5000 Attack Points?! Impossible!
Dr. Faker, I will redeem you with my own hands!
Are you ready for your repentance?!
You fool! You're just a clueless brat!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
You did it! Faker just got some big damage!
Give up, Dr. Faker. It's over.
Release Haruto now!
Kaito...
Do you... have any idea what you're doing?
What did you say?
The only way for Haruto to survive is to destroy the Astral World!
Wha... What do you mean by that?
Without the power of Barian, there is no way now Haruto can survive.
What did you say?
Haruto was a frail child ever since he was born.
Even now, his flame of life
is so small, it might vanish in an instant.
That's why, in order to save his life...
...I just had to visit the Parallel Worlds.
For that reason, Dad and Tron were...
When I decided to save Haruto, I gave up everything.
My friends and partners...
Byron and Kazuma.
I had to sacrifice them to be able to open the door.
Waiting on the other side of the door was...
Barian.
Substance does not exist within their world.
It is a world made up of some kind of energy.
They show no ability of metaphysics in their world.
I made a deal with them.
To give Haruto the power he needs to survive,
I have to destroy the Astral World!
So I started collecting the Numbers,
to use their power in the Sphere Field Cannon,
that I had planned to destroy the Astral World with.
If I don't keep my promise,
sooner or later these guys will come to take Haruto away.
Haruto...
If that's really the truth, then why...
Why didn't you tell me?!
I couldn't say it...
If I would have told you,
you would have tried to burden the bitter fate all on your shoulders.
I was grateful, Kaito...
Without complaining,
you fought for Haruto as Number Hunter.
That's why I didn't want to make you suffer any more than you already have.
That's why...
That's wrong.
Why didn't you believe in your family?
Why did you believe in them and not trust in me?!
Dad!
Kaito...
If they come to take away Haruto's life,
I will protect Haruto!
I will protect him to the very end!
Even if it costs my life!
Kaito...
Kaito, I will lend you my power!
I don't know anything about these Barian guys, but I will beat them to bits!
Me too.
Shark!
Don't get me wrong.
There's something I need to settle with them.
I'll crush them for sure!
With the three of us joining forces, Barian won't stand a chance!
I'll do my best!
Dad!
You don't need to give up anything anymore!
Just believe in us.
We'll settle this with them once and for all!
Kaito...
Dr. Faker.
Dr. Faker... how regrettable.
Father?!
Don't come...!
Don't come here!
Stop it!
What's wrong, Dad!?
I thought you could do better than this...
The Number is...?!
Yuma Tsukumo. Kaito Tenjo. Ryouga Kamishiro.
The Duel hasn't been settled yet.
Who are you!?
I am... Barian.
You are Barian?!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Barian has finally appeared in front of us!
We ran out of answers, being cornered by his overwhelming power!
Our hope and our future...
How could we give them up like this?!
Haruto, don't tell me you...
Astral, I'll come to you!
Our power, we will raise it to the ultimate!
Give me power, ZEXAL Weapon!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Miraculous 'Bring it to 'Em'!
Open a Path to the Future, ZEXAL!
Take the feelings everyone has entrusted to us!
Hope Ray, Shark Drake Weiss, and Neo Galaxy.
What's the sum of their Numbers?
Hope Ray's is 39, Shark Drake's is 32 and Neo Galaxy-Eyes is... umm....
The answer is 71, because Neo Galaxy isn't a Number.
You tricked me...!