It started moving since the scattered Numbers cards were brought back.
This giant puzzle...
The number is the same as my scattered memories, 99 pieces.
This structure... Is it some kind of message?
Why would something like this be in Yuma's key...?
Could it be...
My loss of memories...
Does it mean someone predicted this would happen?
Oh no!
Late, late!
I'm really late!
Careful! Didn't you see the lights...?
You're...
Shark?
Shark... where's he going anyways?
I made it.
Yuma-kun.
Let me have a look at your deck.
H-Hey...!
Huh?
It's not here.
What isn't?
I mean your Numbers.
Where are those cards?
Those? They don't show up in my deck unless that guy is around.
That guy?
Astral!
We're talking about the Dueling spirit.
What is all this?
Oh well, to summarize...
If you don't have the Numbers cards,
then right now, you're just a terrible Duelist, aren't you?
What's with that attitude?
Wouldn't that mean all my victories so far
were all relying on the strength of Numbers and that guy?
Isn’t that how it is?
To summarize...
Without them, there's no way you can win against Shark and Tokunosuke.
You guys!
You just don't get the awesome power of my "bring it on"!
My Duel Sphinx goes up dramatically, you know!
"Sphinx"?
He's trying to say "tactics".
Amazing!
Tetsuo-kun must be Yuma’s human translator!
Well Yuma-kun, can you prove that you are still strong even without Numbers?
Of course I can!
Then, I'll Duel with Shark one more time.
As long as I can defeat him without Numbers, right?
Yuma?
Hey you...
I see.
That way, I'll get to recognize your strength too, right?
Alright!
Then let's hurry up and go to Shark's place.
Wait, Yuma!
I heard that guy hasn’t come to school recently.
After losing that Duel with you,
Shark’s reputation fell dramatically.
Rumor says, he started hanging out with some bad people.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Yuma challenges Shark once again!
Can he win without borrowing the power of Hope?
"Numbers 10:
Shark’s Counterattack!"
Geez, those guys don’t understand at all.
I'm way stronger than before!
Where are you heading to, Yuma?
What do you want, coming out at a time like this?
This is all your fault, for making things so troublesome!
What do you mean?
I will Duel with Shark again.
Shark?
That boy who used a Numbers, is that right?
But why him?
You don't need to know!
This Duel has nothing to do with you!
No, you getting involved would make it worse.
Hey, wait!
Yuma, you're really planning to go?
Of course!
If I don't go see Shark, we won't be able to Duel!
This the place?
Shark is here, isn't he?
H-Hey! This place doesn't look too good! Hey, Yuma!
Such a strange place…
Yuma!
Hey!
Let's go back home, okay...!
This place...
Tetsuo!
The hell you doin' here, brats? This is my territory.
You jerk...! Take your hands off hi-
Yuma!
Le'go!
This stubborn kid's got some guts, ain't he?!
Whas' happenin', Boss?
Just what're these guys up to?
You jerks! I came here to Duel, so lem'me go!
I suggest you give it up.
There is a vast difference between your body structure and his.
You stay outta this!
Bro, what should we do about these guys?
Should we get rid of 'em?
Stop it!
Release them.
Shark…
Do you happen to know these guys?
I do.
Then your lives are spared.
You guys don't belong here.
Wait, Shark! I have something to do with you!
With me?
Please Duel with me once again!
That I can't do.
Why?
I gave up Dueling.
I have no intentions... of ever playing again.
Shark sure has fallen.
Those brothers are punk Duelists.
They attend all kinds of tournaments and threaten people.
What’s wrong, Yuma?
Yuma...
Why would he give up Dueling?
Right, why would he give up Dueling…?
No doubt that’s because of losing to you.
Then why would losing to me make him give up Dueling?
There's something you can never get back after losing.
Something you can’t get back once you lose?
Speaking of which, that Shark started acting bad when he participated in the National Duel Tournament.
Maybe something happened to him then...
That guy... He should love Dueling...
Huh, where’s Yuma?
It seems he went home in a hurry…
Don’t tell me that Yuma…
What do you want?
Duel with me! What’s so fun about hanging around those punks?
What do you understand?
Once we Duel, I'll understand everything about you!
Right?
C'mon! Duel with me!
I gave up Dueling! Quit bugging me!
Shark, wait!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!!
Gonna bring it to 'em!!
So he finally gave up?
Shark…
Duel… with me.
Why?! Why would you give up Dueling?!
What on Earth is wrong with you?!
Why are you so concerned about me?!
That's... obviously because we're friends!
Once we Duel, we're no longer strangers to each other…
We're friends!
Didn’t you feel the same way?!
Are you serious about that?
I mean it! If I win, you have to withdraw from that gang!
Then, what do you plan to bet?!
I…
...bet this!
Yuma, that's...
You shut up!
Interesting.
But don’t you regret it!
This time, I plan to really make you lose your most precious something!
Yuma, are you sure you want to do this?
I said this Duel has nothing to do with you!
I won't be using the Numbers during this Duel.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Numbers can only be defeated by Numbers.
But Shark no longer owns a Numbers!
Yuma…
How can I do such a lowly thing like using a Numbers against a guy who doesn't even have one?
Plus, I've gotten way more skilled than the last time!
I can still win, even without your strength!
Understood. I will carefully observe this.
I can't simply forget that I've lost to you...
Maybe deep inside my heart, I’ve been waiting for this moment.
Let’s go!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Let's go!
My turn.
Draw!
I summon Gogogo Golem!
Be careful, Yuma.
His uses many powerful monsters.
With only Gogogo Golem...
I got it already!
I set one card face down.
I can't attack on the first turn.
Turn end.
My set card is Battle Break.
This trap can destroy one of my opponent's attacking monster, and end the battle phase.
This way, he won't be able to attack so easily.
My turn!
Draw!
I summon Killer Frilled Shark.
Killer Frilled Shark? 700 Attack Points...
What is he planning?
Next I special summon Shark Sucker!
When there is another fish-type monster on the field, I can special summon this card from my hand.
There are two level 3 monsters..!
Don’t tell me...
I overlay my level 3 Shark Sucker and Killer Frilled Shark!
With these two monsters, I construct the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Come, Submersible -- Aero Shark!!
1900 Attack Points, higher than Gogogo Golem's..!
However, I have a trap for stopping Shark's attack.
I activate Aero Shark’s effect!
Once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit, I can inflict 400 damage to my opponent for every card in my hand!
There are four cards left in my hand.
Because of that, you'll take 1600 damage.
What?!
Then, I activate quickplay spell, Cyclone from my hand!
Cyclone can destroy one spell or trap card on the field.
Ah! My trap was...
Go, Aero Shark! Attack Gogogo Golem!
Big Eater!!
I set one card face down. Turn end.
Amazing! With only a single turn, Yuma's life dropped to 2300..
Shark is impossibly strong after all..!
Yuma..
Come on, what’s wrong?
Aren’t you come here to defeat me?
You're here to beat my fallen self again, then make fun of me, aren't you?
You're wrong!
That's not what I'm after...
At this rate, I won't be able to anything...
But if I use the Numbers...!
Damn..!
My turn, draw!!
Ah, this is...!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
Gagaga Magician's effect, once per turn, lets me change its level to anything between 1 to 8.
And then, I have Resurrection of the Dead in my hand.
This way if I revive Gogogo Golem, I can summon Aspiring Emperor - Hope to the field.
Even though, I promised to not use my Numbers during this duel...
But...
Come on, bring it out!
Your Numbers, your trump!
Huh?
What is Shark talking about?
Only Numbers can defeat other Numbers,
He should know that already!
Now, summon it!
Your Numbers, did you really think you can beat me without it?
Since I accepted your duel like this,
It'll only mean something if I defeat you while you used Numbers!
It's true, Shark is unbelievably strong.
At this rate, I...
If I want to defeat Shark here...
Yuma.
Are you thinking of using the Numbers?
You said if you use the Numbers in this duel,
It would be acting shamelessly underhanded.
But I won't object.
I can't afford to lose the Emperor's Key.
The only way, for the sake of winning..
...Is to use the Numbers!
You're right..
I think you're right.
This duel isn't about my pride!
I have to save Shark!
I activate a spell card, Monster Reborn!
I'll revive Gogogo Golem from my graveyard!
I overlay my Level 4 monsters, Gagaga Magician and Gogogo Golem!
With these two monsters, I construct the Overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Numbers 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Yuma used Numbers?
But he promised he wouldn't use it...
To summarize, Yuma's duels are still relying on the Numbers.
It's finally here! the Numbers!
I'm all fired up!
Go, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Attack Aero Shark!
So naive!
I activate the effect of Killer Frilled Shark!
By removing Killer Frilled Shark from play from the graveyard,
One of the opponent monster's attack is negated,
And its attack power is decreased by 500.
What?!
Trap activate, Fish Rain!
With this card, when a fish type monster is removed from play,
I can special summon one level 3 or lower fish type monster from my hand.
I'll summon Big Jaws!
No way...
Even if Hope couldn't destroy Aero Shark...
Just now, you made a mistake because you're too eager to win.
Monster Reborn can revive an opponent's monster as well.
If you revived Killer Frilled Shark from Shark's graveyard,
Activated Gagaga Magician's effect, then XYZ Summoned Leviath Dragon,
Killer Frilled Shark's effect wouldn't have activated.
Then, using Leviath Dragon's ability, you could have destroyed Aero Shark.
So noisy! Everything is still fine!
Hope's attack power is 2000.
There isn't a monster with higher ATK than Hope on Shark’s field.
I'll end my turn like this.
My turn!
Draw!!
I activate Aero Shark's effect!
Once per turn, by detaching an overlay unit,
I can inflict 400 damage to my opponent for every card in my hand!
There are two cards in my hand.
Because of that, you take 800 points of damage!
Then, I summon Skull Kraken!
There's two level 3 monsters...!
Don't panic.
He doesn't have a card that can destroy Hope, a Numbers.
I overlay my Level 3 monsters, Skull Kraken and Big Jaws!
With these two monsters, I construct the Overlay network!
Xyz Summon!!
Appear, Black Ray Lancer!!
This duel is mine!
I activate Black Ray Lancer's effect!
By detaching an overlay unit,
During this turn, the effect of one of my opponent’s monsters is negated!
What?!
Hope---!!
Even if Numbers cannot be destroyed,
But after all, it's merely a card effect!
If the effect is gone, then it can be destroyed!
How could it be?
Hope's...
Numbers’ effects are negated?..
Go, Black Ray Lancer!
Black Spear!!
Hope---!!
Hope.. was defeated...
This boy...
He discovered the Numbers' weakness..
Aero Shark, direct attack!
Big Eater!!
To summarize, it was a complete defeat..
Yuma lost...
You're kidding, right?
Even after I used the Numbers...
That was almost too easy.
Lost to a duelist like you, losing everything and such...
How laughable..
As promised, I'll be taking this.
That's... because we're friends, of course!
This kind of thing... it's not even worth destroying.
Shark...
Wait!
Yuma! You don't understand.
I'm staying with them because I like to.
They gave me a place to stay, to someone
with no place like me.
So don't get involved again!
Shark...
Yuma...
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
Which magic card can be activated on the opponent's turn?
Equipment Magic? Or Quickplay Magic?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Shark, let's duel!
Why are you so concerned about me?!
Because we're friends, of course!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Yuma and Shark: A Traumatic Tag Duel!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is... Quickplay Magic!
Usually magic cards can't be used other than during your own turn,
but Quickplay Magic can be played during your opponent's turn.
Black Ray Lancer!!
Your opponent's monster effect will be negated!