Go, Giant Killer!
Tetsuo and the class rep were defeated by IV.
Based on his true identity, he really is powerful!
If so... I will end this once and for all!
Wait, his opponent is me!
Have you forgotten the face of your greatest fan...
IV!?
Shark...!
I finally found you, IV!
Ryoga... I actually forgot...
You really are my biggest fan out there.
Then allow me to repay the debt I owe you!
Debt, huh...?
Oh right, how's your "precious" younger sister doing?
Younger sister?
you set up everything...
It's all because of me... because of me...
She...
I will exact revenge on you here and now!
Shark... you... seek revenge?
Excellent. I really like people like you.
This is....?
It's a Duel Anchor.
You cannot escape without finishing the Duel with me!
III, this guy is my prey! Get lost!
Brother IV, Ryoga's deck doesn't have any Numbers.
Therefore it won't be necessary for you to become his opponent, right?
Plus, Tron's order is absolute.
The fanservice is over.
Wait, stop! Are you going to run away, IV?
I already finished collecting my Heart Pieces.
I will wait for you in the Finals.
IV!
Calm down. My brother is quite busy.
Plus, your opponent is me.
Just who are those people?
That's the same anchor Kaito uses.
Don't tell me these people are collecting Numbers as well with the same technical power of Kaito?
Anyway, we have to get him to hospital!
Right.
Kotori, Tetsuo!
You can observe this Duel for yourself, and we won't have any problem on this side!
But...
Yuma... I agree with him as well.
Astral...
I got it. Take care of him!
As you wish, I will clobber you first!
Here I go!
Duel Mode, Change!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Duel!!
"Number 34: The Determined Revenge,
The Tragic Duelist, Shark!"
I will go first. My turn, draw!
I activate the Field Magic, Deep Sea Monarchy - Sunken Kingdom!
This card increases Water-Attribute Monster's Attack Power by 300 points!
The field has gone underwater! Where's my oxygen tank?
Yuma, this is AR space.
I Summon OOparts Mayan Machine!
Then I set a card face-down and end my turn!
What the heck are OOparts??
OOparts were art 'works' that were built in the ancient civilization with seemingly impossible technology at that time.
Their existence was still wrapping under mysteries.
My turn, draw!
I summon Hammer Shark!
Then due to field magic, Sunken Kingdom's effect, Hammer Shark gains 300 ATK!
Looks like you weren't aware that I use a Water-Attribute deck.
But in the Field Magic, Sunken Kingdom,
you cannot attack OOparts Monsters with Level Four or lower Monsters.
So that's your insurance, huh?
But... Magic Card, Downward Current!
During this turn, this card can change my Monster's level from any number between 1 to 3!
I will decrease Hammer Shark's LV by 1!
You Duel so strangely.
What exactly do you plan to do by lowering its level?
I special summon Big Jaws!
When I use a Normal Magic card during this turn, Big Jaws can be special summoned from my hand!
Due to Sunken Kingdom's effect, Big Jaws will gain 300 ATK too!
There are 2 LV 3 monsters...
I overlay the LV3 Hammer Shark and Big Jaws!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Black Ray Lancer!
Xyz monsters don't have levels to begin with, so Sunken Kingdom's effect won't work!
Nice one, Shark!
Go, Black Ray Lancer, attack Mayan Machine!
Black Spear!!
Trap, activate! Stonehenge Method!
With this card, when an OOparts monster was destroyed,
I can special summon 1 LV4 or lower OOparts monster from my deck in face-up defense position!
Come forth, OOparts Colossal Head!
I set one card, and end my turn.
My turn, draw!
I summon OOparts Golden Shuttle!
Then I activate the Continuous Magic, Orichalcum Chain!
When this card is face-up on my field when I performed a Xyz summon,
I can use one less Overlay Unit.
Say what?
But Orichalcum Chain has risks as well.
When this card is destroyed,
The Xyz monster summoned by this effect will have its control switch to my opponent!
Is he planning to take such risk for the sake of Xyz summoning?
I overlay LV 4 Colossal Head, Golden Shuttle and Orichalcum Chain's effect!!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters and Orichalcum Chain's effect!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 32!
The biggest, most powerful ruler of the deep sea! Its sharp fang shall exterminate everything!
Sea Biting Dragon Shark Drake!
A Number!
Indeed he is...
So it finally appears.
Due to the Sunken Kingdom's effect, Shark Drake gains 300 ATK!
Go, Shark Drake! Attack Black Ray Lancer!
Depth Bite!!
I activate Shark Drake's effect!
When it destroys my opponent's monster by battle, once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit,
The destroyed monster will lose 1000 ATK, and special summon that target to my opponent's field!
And it can battle with that monster again!
So that Number can attack twice?
But it's more than just 'attack twice'. It's a very overpowered effect!
It will bite you until you have no bones left! Shark Drake attacks Black Ray Lancer once again!
DEPTH BITE!
Shark!
Hey! Are you alright?
You shut up, Yuma!
Do you honestly think I would get defeated like this?
Then I set one card and end my turn!
Well, if you can't think of a way to counter Shark Drake, then you have no where to escape!
That Shark, if this continues...
But there is a way to bring a reversal under these circumstances.
But that would require...
I need to take away his Number!
My turn, draw!
I summon Skull Kraken!
I activate Skull Kraken's effect!
When this card is summoned successfully,
It can destroy one face-up Magic or Trap on my opponent's field!
I destroy Orichalcum's Chain!
Thus I gained the control of Shark Drake!
That's right, that's how it should be...
That's the only thing you can do if you wish to survive.
My mission will...
Shark!
Alright, accept me, Ryouga.
Accept me, and release the darkness inside your heart.
Shark!
Let's Duel again some time!
Let's bring it to 'em together!
Why?! Why would you give up Dueling?!
Didn't I already say we are fiends?!
But...!
DON'T LAUGH!
What's so darn funny?
What's so funny about having a fear of losing?
It must be the same for Shark. That's why Shark's duel, is for real!
I'm not... the same as I used to be!
As if I'd ever be controlled by the likes of you!
Because I am who I am!
So he finally surpassed the Numbers' power, huh?
Shark...
He wasn't possessed by the Number?
As long as I have this guy's power,
Go, Shark Drake! Attack him directly!
Yes! If this connects, he'll receive huge damage!
I won't let that happen! Trap, activate! Antikythera Gear!
When there are 2 or more monsters on my opponent's field, and my opponent declares a direct attack,
I can gain control of the monster besides the attacking one, and put it in defense position!
Dream on! Trap Card, Hyper Water Pressure!
With this card, by destroying one monster on my field, I am allowed to draw one card from my deck!
Now your trap is useless!
Resume your attack, Shark Drake!
I set 2 cards face-down, and end my turn.
Nice one. My mission is give him the Numbers.
Although Tron said after the mission is completed, feel free to lose purposely...
But don't get too overconfident, Ryoga!
My turn, draw!
I activate Magic card, OOparts Technology!
By banishing one OOparts monster from my graveyard,
I can draw 2 cards from my graveyard, and send one card to my graveyard.
I special summon OOparts Crystal Bone!
When only my opponent controls a monster, I can special summon it from my hand!
When this card is special summoned this way, I can also special summon OOparts Crystal Skull from my graveyard!
Revive, Crystal Skull!
I overlay the LV3 Crystal Bone and Crystal Skull!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, OOparts Crystal Alien!
With this card, by detaching 1 overlay unit,
It cannot be destroyed by battle during this turn and the battle damage inflicted to this card will inflict to my opponent instead!
What?!
In other words, the difference of ATK between your Shark Drake and my OOparts Alien is 1000,
You shall receive damage equal to that value!
Go, Crystal Alien, attack Shark Drake!
REFLECT FLASH!
Shoot! If this attack connects...
It's over, Ryouga!
Quick-Play Magic, Plate Salvage!
Plate Salvage negates the effect of Field Spell for 2 turns!
Awesome! Now we are finally above sea level!
Now Sunken Kingdom's effect disappears!
Shark Drake's ATK will return to 2800!
Amazing. By negating Field Spell's effect, he decreased Shark Drake's ATK to preserve his LP!
But... both Shark and III have only 300 LP left.
The next blow will decide the outcome.
He actually survived Crystal Alien's Reflect Flash.
But, he will definitely use Shark Drake's effect in his next turn,
The outcome will be decided at that moment!
I set one card and end my turn!
My turn, draw!
I attack Crystal Alien with Shark Drake!
DEPTH BITE!!
Yes! Now it's Shark's win.
Not yet, I activate OOparts monster Colossal Head's effect!
By banish this card from my graveyard,
I switch one monster on my field from Attack position to defense position!
Darn!
Not good! His LP won't be depleted if his monster was in defense position!
No...
But at this moment, I activate Shark Drake's effect!
When it destroys my opponent's monster by battle, by detaching one Overlay unit, that monster loses 1000 ATK,
And special summons itself to my opponent's field!
Do you think I would forget Shark Drake's effect?
Go, Shark Drake!
Fortunately I haven't underestimated you one bit.
I knew you would be able to control this Number!
Trap, activate! OOpart Ley Line Power!
What?
With this card, when a monster was special summoned during the Battle Phase and battles,
I switch the ATK of the battling monsters!
Now Crystal Alien and Shark Drake's ATK are exchanged!
Then I win the duel!
As I expected.
I am the fortunate one for not underestimating you.
I knew you would expect me to use Shark Drake's effect.
Trap activate! Deep Sea Lord's Judgment!
This card negates the effect of the trap activated during Battle Phase!
How could that be?
Damn!
Resume your attack, Shark Drake!
Great, Shark won!
What a breathtaking exchange of offense and defense!
I see, you are quite good.
I lost to you for today.
But I am going to the Finals. It won't be easy for you if we meet next time!
So that guy finished collecting Heart Pieces as well?
You can keep that Number. Consider it as a reward for winning this duel.
He disappeared?
Yuma!
Kotori!
I'm in the Hospital right now. The class rep is holding up for the moment.
Good. I'll come over there as well!
Shark!
Yuma, don't get involved with me anymore...
Shark... something about revenge...
Shark!
He acquired a Number once again... That means sooner or later, these two will...
Good job, III.
You always successfully complete the tasks I assigned you.
I just do everything I can for you, Tron.
Looks like modesty is one of your virtues as well.
But...
Ryoga wasn't possessed by the Number.
No, that's not the case.
The darkness that sleeps inside people's hearts...
As long as there is even the tiniest of openings...
It will slowly expand without them realizing...
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Photos that can display the future? Plus that future can be twisted according to his wish.
Could such a phenomenon really exist?
Geez, I won't care about Yuma anymore!
Maybe it was due to Numbers!
Kotori, where are you?
The power to manipulate future...
As long as I beat this guy, and take away his Numbers, then the 'reality' shown in the pictures can also be corrected, right?
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Shocking Scoop! Kotori's Dangerous Future!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Let's review the rules of the Duel Carnival!
You have three days to qualify. The city venue is all of Heartland.
Always stand when challenged by a duel!
If 5 heart pieces are collected and a heart is completed, it's a final tournament advance!