Kite it to 'em, Kaito!
I can see in my brother's eyes that he's trying to respond to Yuma.
I have no idea what lies ahead,
but I will open up my own path.
My own Dueling!
Alright, come on, Kaito!
You'll regret waking up the sleeping lion!
That's what I want!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Treasure Cards of Adversity!
When there is no Monster on my field,
and there is a Special Summoned Monster on the opponent's field,
I can draw two cards!
Then, I activate the Magic Card, Accel Light!
If there are no Monsters on my field,
Instead of Normal Summoning this turn,
I can Special Summon
one Level Four Light-Attribute Warrior-Type Monster!
I Special Summon Day Breaker!
Day Breaker... Yuma, be careful.
Right!
When Day Breaker has been successfully Special Summoned,
I can Special Summon another Day Breaker from my hand.
I overlay my two Level Four Day Breakers.
With these two Monsters, I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Radiant Photon Paradios!
There it is!
Get ready for it!
I activate the effect of Radiant Photon Paradios!
Once per turn, by detaching one Overlay Unit,
Until the end of the battle, the Attack Power of one Xyz Monster on the opponent's field is changed to zero,
and the effects of all other cards other than Paradios are negated!
That means Hope's effect is gone...!
That's right! Even if it's a Number, it can be destroyed!
Do it, Paradios!
Photon Dividing!
With this, I end my turn.
As to be expected from Kaito.
Yeah, but if it weren't like that, it wouldn't be interesting.
It has to be this good so you can Bring it to 'em!
This wall isn't so brittle that you can climb over it so easily!
If that's the case, I'll climb it with all I've got!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
My turn! Draw!
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card,
Treasure Cards of Magic Sealing!
"Number 73: The Illusive Grand Clash!
Double Hope vs Double Galaxy-Eyes!"
In exchange for sealing the activation of other Magic Cards this turn,
I can draw two cards!
Yes, its there!
I Summon Gagaga Kaiser!
And when there's a Gagaga Monster on my field,
Gagaga Clerk can be Special Summoned!
Then I activate the effect of Gagaga Kaiser!
Once per turn, I can Banish one Monster from my Graveyard,
then the level of all Monsters on my field becomes the same level as the Banished one!
I'll Banish Ganbara Knight from my Graveyard!
Ganbara Knight's level is four!
Thus, the levels of Gagaga Kaiser and Gagaga Clerk become four!
He's got two Level Four Monsters!
A chance, or not!
You can cat it!
Go, Yuma!
I overlay the Level Four Gagaga Kaiser and Gagaga Clerk!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Heroic Champion Excalibur!
Oh! Isn't that the Monster I gave him?!
Knock him flat, Yuma!
Gauche! Whose side are you on?
With Excalibur, I'll attack Paradios!
But both their Attack Points are...
...both 2000!
The Monster Effect of Excalibur activates!
By detaching all its Overlay Units, his Attack Power is doubled until the end of the battle!
4000 Attack Points!
Go, Excalibur!
Single Strike: Sure-Kill Divine Sword!
Kaito!
Kaito-sama!
When Paradios was destroyed,
I can draw one card!
With this I end my turn!
Kaito...
That was amazing, or not.
Yes.
What a tough Duel.
It's enough to make you purr... I mean, smart!
But they're having fun!
Eh?
To me, it looks like both Yuma and Kaito are enjoying themselves!
My brother is smiling.
He's enjoying this from the bottom of his heart.
Kazuma, does this mean that your son will save Kaito?
Here I go! My turn! Draw!
I activate the Equip Magic, Galaxy Zero!
It negates the effect of the Galaxy-Eyes in my Graveyard,
and revives it with this card equipped to it in Attack Position!
Be revived, Galaxy-Eyes!
Galaxy-Eyes!
That's what I'm talking about!
Due to the effect of the Equip Magic, Galaxy Zero,
it loses 800 Attack Points during battle!
Even so, Galaxy-Eyes still has the higher Attack Power!
Kaito! Go!
Galaxy-Eyes! Attack Excalibur!
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
Yuma!
Then Galaxy-Eyes' Attack Power returns to normal.
I set one card and end my turn.
Darn!
It's not over! I still can go on, Kaito!
I wouldn't want it any other way.
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Gagaga Draw!
From my Graveyard, I Banish three Gagaga Monsters...
... to draw two cards!
Then I activate the Equip Magic, Xyz Revival.
I select one Xyz Monster from my Graveyard,
and Special Summon it equipped with this card!
Come on! Show me all you've got!
I will crush all of it!
Exactly my words!
I target Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Come forth, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
But it falls short of Galaxy-Eyes.
We'll see if it falls short!
I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Chaos Xyz Change!
The messenger who changes Chaos into Light!
Come forth, Chaos Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Hope Ray... Hope...
Huh?
Astral, you once said that I no longer need to be tied down by the past.
Yes.
My Dueling was a Dueling of vows.
Vows?
As I vowed to save Haruto by all means, I had to Duel.
Brother...
But... from now on...
Wishes... Hope...
I will Duel for myself.
That's right, Kaito! Our future belongs to us!
We decide it!
Kaito.
Brother... It's the same for me.
Now bring it, Yuma!
Here I go, Kaito!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray's effect activates.
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
for this turn, Hope Ray's Attack Power will go up by 500 points!
Overlay Charge!
Then the Attack Power of one opposing Monster will be decreased by 1000 points!
Go, Hope Ray! Attack Galaxy-Eyes!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!!
I activate the other effect of the Equip Magic, Galaxy Zero!
When this card is sent to the Graveyard, the destruction of Galaxy-Eyes is negated!
But you still receive Battle Damage!
This is...
Wh... Why?!
The Galaxy Zero I sent to the Graveyard has another effect.
When this card leaves the field, the Attack Power of the Monster equipped with it becomes zero!
Yuma, it's the effect of Zerozelock.
I see. Dang it!
Zerozelock... Your Continuous Magic.
Monsters with an Attack Power of zero can't be attacked.
Therefore, Hope Ray's attack has been negated!
That means...
Right.
The effect of my Continuous Magic, Battle Gravity, will bury you!
When a Monster a player controls did not battle,
that player receives 1000 points of damage!
Not good!
Yuma!
Right! The Permanent Trap, Dimension Gate, activates!
It Banishes one Monster on our field!
Since I don't control a Monster anymore, I don't take Effect Damage from Battle Gravity!
The both of them are in really high spirits!
Kaito...
Kaito-sama, do not lose to that dork!
What an awesome Duel this is!
Both of them keep on moving forward!
Towards the hope lying ahead!
I set one card and end my turn!
Yuma.
Huh?
You have become stronger.
What the heck's with that?
The spirit of your "Bring it To 'em" is truly wondrous.
You're ready to do this on your own...
What are you saying?!
We complete the "Bring it To 'em" together!
Let's advance together, forever.
Yuma, let's win.
Sure!
Yuma, Astral.
I'll be stealing this Duel!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Galaxy Wizard!
Then Galaxy Wizard's level increases by four,
and he is treated as two Xyz Materials.
Here it comes!
I Overlay the Level Eight Galaxy-Eyes and the Galaxy Wizard counting as two!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Great Galaxy of Reversal!
Become the rolling waves of light and show your mighty form!
Descend, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
However, because it was Summoned with the effect of Galaxy Wizard,
Neo Galaxy-Eyes loses 2000 Attack Points.
But this should be enough.
Your Life is a mere 300!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes, Direct Attack!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
My brother wins now!
Yuma!
I activate another effect of the Permanent Trap, Dimension Gate!
When I receive a Direct Attack, I can send this card to the Graveyard,
to Special Summon the Banished Monster with its effects negated!
Resurrect! Hope Ray!
Hope Ray and Neo Galaxy-Eyes have the same Attack Power!
So it's a draw!
Go, Yuma!
Alright! I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Quick-Play Magic, Xyz Double Back, activate!
When an Xyz Monster is destroyed and I no longer have a Monster on the field,
the destroyed Monster and one with equal or less Attack Power...
...can be Special Summoned from the Graveyard!
What?!
Descend, both of you!
Come forth! Aspiring Emperor - Hope! Hope Ray!
Good job, Yuma!
Yuma, you're so cool!
Is this the end?!
Kaito...
Amazing! Hope and Hope Ray side by side!
Now, in the next turn...
Yes, then victory will be ours!
What?!
That is...
That's not possible!
Xyz Double Back!
You have the same card as me?!
You did it, Kaito-sama!
Stupid dork!
When compared, "Kite it To 'em" is far superior to "Bring it To 'em"!
Kaito...
Yuma... Astral...
Galaxy-Eyes and Neo Galaxy-Eyes together, attack Hope Ray and Hope!
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
Go! Ultimate Photon Stream!!
Ow, ow...
Looks like I lost.
Kaito!
Kaito...
I'm definitely gonna beat you next time!
I'll take you on whenever you want.
As often as you like.
Yeah! I'll do it!
As long as I don't give it and keep bringing it...
...I'm sure to surpass you one of these days!
Yuma!
Yuma~kun!
Kotori...
Yuma?
Yuma!
Hey, Yuma!
Yuma~kun!
Huh?
Brother... Yuma... Thank you.
Those were some good spirits!
Yuma, see you again.
Yuma, Astral...
Yuma... Yuma, for goodness sakes...
He's sound asleep, or not!
To summarize...
That's just like Yuma!
Let him sleep on my lap instead!
Hey, Astral... Yuma...
Not even I can do anything about this.
I'm gonna bring it to 'em...!
Can't be helped then.
Just let him be for a bit.
Observation #21:
Apparently, it would seem that one can feel good even after a loss.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Yuma Tsukumo... Astral.
They went far beyond my expectations.
It would seem we will have to appear personally next time.
Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal powers up this October!
Wh-Wh-What is this "Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal Second (II) about?!
A new enemy has come from the Barian World!
Who Rank-Up the Xyz Monsters!
Just what is going on?!
Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal II starts broadcasting October 7th, 5:30 PM!
You absolutely gotta watch it!