The overwhelming power of III's new Number, Atlantal, is striking me relentlessly.
Although Astral has vanished, he still lives within my heart!
I can't afford to lose this duel!
Now you only have 200 LP left.
Let me finish you off now, Yuma!
I set 2 cards face-down, and end my turn!
I won't give up, for the sake of Astral who entrusted hope to me!
My turn, draw!
See for yourself, Astral, this is my real duel now!
This... is the other power you left for me.
I will not waste it!
I'll bring it to 'Em!
When my LP are lower than 1000, I can use Aspiring Emperor Hope as Overlay material,
CHAOS XYZ CHANGE!!
Show yourself, Chaos No.39!
The messenger who turns chaos into light, Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Here it comes! Hope Ray!
Cat it to 'Em, Yuma!
So it finally comes huh...
"Numbers 49: The End of a Fierce Fight!
Hope Ray VS Atlanthal"
Hope Ray, your power definitely can bring III back to his senses.
I activate the effect of Overlay Eater from my graveyard!
By banishing this card from my graveyard, it can absorb one overlay unit from my opponent's Xyz monster,
and attach it to my own Xyz monster!
Nice! Now Atlantal cannot use his effect!
Here I come! I activate Hope Ray's effect!
For every Overlay Unit I detached this turn, he gains 500 ATK,
I will detach all 3 Overlay Units from Hope Ray!
OVERLAY CHARGE!
Also due to this effect, for every Overlay Unit detached, Atlantal loses 1000 ATK!
Astral no longer exists, so why...?
No! He still exists!
He lives within my heart!
He lives within my 'Bring it to 'Em'!
And keeps making me strong!
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
This level of counterattack, I already foresaw it!
Trap activate! Thunder Pot!
This card negates the attack that targets an OOParts monster, and ends the Battle Phase!
Ah... Hope Ray!
Ah! Yuma's attack was...
How can this be?
Seems like even Hope Ray's attack won't be able to hit me.
Tch! It's not over yet!
It's too soon for me to give up!
I set one card, and end my turn!
You are quite persistent, Yuma!
Now our monster's ATK has returned to normal.
You still have no chance of winning!
My turn.
Dra -...
So that's what Tron's been talking about...
Listen well, III.
After obtaining this Crests power,
you shall be able to control No.6 Atlantal.
But while this card gives you enormous power,
it will also take a huge toll on your mind and body.
No... no problem!
I will defeat Yuma to meet your expectation!
I have faith in you, III.
Because you are such a strong child.
Is this the price of using Numbers?
Don't tell me I am still unable to control the Number?
I...I will definitely meet Tron's expectation!
Wha...what's happening to that guy?
Here I come, Yuma! Draw!
Wha...what happened?
While it has no Overlay Units, during my Standby Phase, Atlantal halves each player's LP!
That guy...he is willing to cut down his own LP...
Yuma...
Not yet... I still have some LP remaining, III!
III...you...that's...
III...
III...!
Don't come here!
Forget about me, Yuma.
This is the price of the power I seek!
But even if I will perish...
I...I will still protect my family for sure!
You...
I will defeat you with this attack!
Go, Atlantal!
Attack Hope Ray!
DIVINE PUNISHMENT!!
Shoot! If this attack connects, then Yuma-kun will lose!
Trap activate! Battle Break!
When my opponent's monster declares an attack,
this card ends the battle phase, and destroys the attacking monster!
What?!
Trap - ...
I can't believe you actually endured all that III, so as promised,
I will give the Number and this card to you.
Angolmois...
Tron... this Trap card is...
Just treat it as your Lucky Charm.
This card is the Card of Destruction.
After its activation, I guess both you and your opponent won't be safe anymore...
Just in case, I decided to entrust this card to you as insurance.
Tron...
you will win using whatever means necessary, right?
...against Yuma.
I activate the Continuous Trap, Angolmois!
With this card I can destroy one Equip card on my field,
then it negates the activation of my opponent's trap card and destroys it.
What?!
To destroy my trap, he's even willing to lower Atlantal's ATK!
One strike will be enough! After all, you only have 100 LP left!
Resume the attack, Atlantal!
Blow Hope Ray out along with Yuma!
Trap activate! Half Unbreak!
This card protects Hope Ray from being destroyed by battle,
while halve the damage is inflicted to the player!
Yuma...
He only has 50 LP remaining...
Yuma... you are still struggling?
III!
III... you...
I... I will let you to witness my true power.
Enough, stop it! III!
Haven't we already become friends?
Yuma... I don't need friends.
I still wish to talk to you more!
Talk to you about your family and my father!
Yuma...
Thank you...
But... it's already too late.
What do you mean?
The Trap card I just activated, Angolmois, is the Card of Destruction.
During my next turn, it will inflict damage to you and me, equal to the ATK of Machu Mach it destroyed.
What?
Just what will happen?
In other words, when my next turn comes, both of us will get blown off the field after receiving 2400 damage.
But it won't be a simple draw.
After all, this is an battle between Number holders.
But, I won't mind...
If my sacrifice will satisfy Tron's expectation,
If I can get back my family, that is.
III, you...
Hey! That darkness is approaching here!
It doesn't look good!
Te...Tetsuo-kun, this is just AR Vision,
How could such a thing happen in reality?
Th...this is...don't tell me...
It's reality?!
Sh...shooot! - At this rate we will...
What should we do?
Hey, III!
S... strange... don't tell me the Dimension Gate has...
III!
N... no...
This is a card which will lead everything to destruction..
My Crest power can't control it!
Don't tell me Angolmois's power is capable of destroying the world?
It seems that III used that card.
It can't be....you gave that card to III?!
Angolmois is the card to opens the door of Valian.
Once it's activated, it shall become unstoppable.
Hey, III! What on earth is going on here?
This duel, at this rate, will open the gate that connects the Different Dimension!
You and I...no...virtually everything will get sucked inside!
What did you say?
How can that be?
Help me! I don't want that to happen!
I....I don't wish to annihilate the world.
Forgive me, Yuma.
I'll bring it to 'Em!
You just said that at this rate the door of Different Dimension would open, right?
Then I will win this duel and prevent its opening!
That's impossible. With Atlantal's effect, when my LP are 1000 or lower,
He cannot be destroyed by battle, and I take no battle damage.
We are finished!
Stop joking!! This duel is not over yet!
It' s too soon to give up right now!
Right, if Astral were here, he would still think about how to win!
Use ZeXal.
ZeXal?
That's the miraculous force summoned by Astral and me.
But, he is...
Yuma...
Yuma, there might be a way to call back Astral.
Call Astral back?
Astral has disappeared due to this Crest's power.
In that case, if I pass on this power to you...!
Then... which means... he will come back?
But you might not be able to tame this Crest's power.
And quite possibly, you might be engulfed by this power as well.
I don't care! As long as I can get Astral back!
Come on, transfer your power to me!
Even if I successfully transfer the Crest Power to Yuma,
I am afraid I...
III!
...Astral!
Yuma!
How can I lose to the power of this Crest!
I'll bring it to 'Em!
ASTRAL!
Astral.
You are...
Astral, my son is calling for you. Please go help him.
Yuma...
Yuma.
Astral, you...
I heard your voice. Let's win this!
You... you...
Geez, you always act tough!
Yuma...
III!
Yuma, Astral! Don't mind me, hurry up and defeat this guy!
Yuma, use ZeXal!
Sure. Let's go, Astral!
I will overlay you and myself!
With us both I will build an overlay network!
Just what's going on?
When two distant souls cross each other, the legendary power shall appear!
Xyz Change!
ZeXal!
Yuma fused with Astral?!
Let's go, Astral!
Everything from the strongest duelist's duel is predetermined!
Even the draw shall be decided by the duelist as well!
Shining Draw!
Come, ZeXal Weapon!
Phoenix Bow!
This monster can be equipped to Hope Ray.
When the equipped Hope Ray attacks,
the battle damage will be negated,
and 1000 damage will be inflicted to my opponent!
Go, Hope Ray!
Attack Atlantal!
PHOENIX FINISH!
So this is the bond between Yuma and Astral.
Impossible! III was...
Tron...
I...
Oh... this is...
This is the place from before!
Then, to summarize, we were saved!
Did I... win?
Yuma.
I said we would win.
Astral...
Ri...right, III!
III, III!
Hey, are you alright?
You...
I understand, Yuma.
You recognize the real me.
You are my first, and last friend.
III...
Yuma, I have a favor to ask from you. Can you save my family?
You can definitely do it, if someone can, it's you... with your 'Bring it to 'Em'.
III...
Yuma!
Now you got 5 Heart Pieces.
You are qualified for the Final.
Yuma?
III, I won't let your feelings go to waste...
I will win... the Duel Carnival!
I'll bring it to 'Em
I'm sorry.
It's alright, III.
Can you please hold my hand?
I wish you could always hold it.
Thank you... I feel quite tired.
Good night...
I will remain by your side, so have a good sleep.
Yuma Tsukumo...
Kazuma's son!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Finally, the Finals of WDC!!
Duelists who past the preliminaries after surviving all kinds of intense battles, tonight, they will all gather in the Night Ceremony!
I brought Kotori and others with me.
The attendants are all strong duelists, don't let your guard down.
Ah. I got it.
Eh? That guy is...
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
The Eve of the Storm! The Diabolical Duelist appears - Tron!
Don't tell me he can see me?
Muzurhythm, Tenten Tempo, Mellowmellow Melody
Their effects will suit any tactical situation as the all are Rank 3.
I summon MuzuTenMelody Demon!
At least memorize the effects.