People address me as the Numbers Hunter!!
No way, theres someone other than me collecting Nos. cards?
The Numbers contain your memory...
How come there is someone else doing it?
No idea, everything is complicated!
But don't back down! Your opponent is not your average person!
I'll do it! I'll bring it to em'!
Two Numbers monsters?
And he summoned them in just 1 turn!
"The Numbers Hunter"?
Who in the world is this kid!?
What does he want with the Nos.?
And furthermore, he's not being possessed by the Numbers!
With this I end my turn.
It's your move, be quick!
Be quiet.
I apologize!
Here I go!
My turn, Draw!
It's Gogogo Golem!
Alright, with Gogogo Golem his attacks are futile.
I set monster in face-down Defense Mode!
I end my turn!
Here I go, my turn, draw!
I activate White Knight Illuminator's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, and by sending one card from my hand to the cemetery, I draw one card!
Then I activate Ant Soil Brilli-Ant's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, this monster's attack power increases by 300 points!
Go! Ant Soil Brilli-Ant!
Attack his face-down monster!
Even if its attack power is higher, Gogogo Golem for once per turn can negate battle destruction!
So you still have something useful...
But, I still have one more attack left!
Go! White Knight Illuminator!
This is bad, now my monster is gone...
But, there's no monster on his field that can attack...
That's right, I'm saved...
You're saved, you say?
I'm just starting to get serious!
This guy, he's not serious yet?
I release Ant Soil Brilli-Ant and White Knight Illuminator to Special Summon...!
What!?
He called out those numbers just to release them?
What's that?
The embodiment of light, now descend!
What's that!?
Appear now, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Glaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon can't be normal summoned...
It can be Special Summoned by releasing 2 monsters with 2000 or more attack power!
"Numbers 14:
Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon Descends!"
An attack power of 3000!?
Never heard of a Photon Dragon...
That's...
With this my turn ends.
An attack power of 3000?
Hope's the only one in my deck that can deal with this thing!
But, calling out hope requires 2 monsters!
And If I don't call him out, things will get worse!
My turn, Draw!
I summon Gagaga Magician!
The battle starts now!
I activate the Magic Card, Monster Slot!
I exclude a from my cemetery with the same level 4 as Gagaga Magician!
Then I draw a card from my deck, and if that card is also a level 4 then I can Special Summon it!
Please let it be a level 4!
This duel is counting on this draw!
I'll Bring it to em'! Draw!
Alright, I drew the level 4 Ganbara Knight!
Appear Ganbara Knight!
Now I have 2 level 4 monsters!
I overlay the level 4 Gagaga Magician and Ganbara Knight!
These two Monsters will construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 39 Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
I'm counting on you, Hope!
So it appeared, the Numbers.
May I know what you think about it, Dr. Faker-sama?
The World Duel Carnival, huh?
Yes, We hold a big Duel Tournament for Duelists with tough fighting spirits in Heartland!
It will attract Duelists with Numbers cards all around the world.
And then Kaito can hunt them efficiently.
If Kaito competes a lot of Numbers, will be ours!
I see, Mr. Heartland...
Your idea is a good one.
But what would happen if Kaito were to lose in that tournament?
Don't worry about that,
Kaito's deck was created by me and you Dr. Faker-sama.
Making it an other world's science crystal!
That fine, Mr. Heartland.
Begin organizing the World Duel Carnival!
I should start that Sphere Field experiment now.
With this Sphere Field, I can extract the Numbers powers!
And If I use that energy...
I want to hear more screams!
More, and more, and MORE!!
That's outstanding Haruto, with your scream we can crush the Astral World!
Galaxy-Eyes' attack power is 3000.
Hope's attack power is 2500!
But I'll keep on attacking!
Yuma...
In my battle with Shark, I learned that Hope isn't invincible!
And that offense is my greatest defense!
I get it, those tactics aren't bad,
You've found your own way of fighting.
And a drawn-out battle with this guy will be foolish!
Right, now here I Go!
I activate the Magic Card, Blustering Winds!
This card, I can increase the attack and defense power of one monster on the field by 1000 points!
Now it has higher attack power than his monster!
You're willing to battle Galaxy-Eyes?
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope! Show him your strength!
Hope Blade Slash!
Too bad, after successfully summoning it...
Sorry, it will be sent to the cemetery soon!
Your monster will...
What?
Don't underestimate Galaxy-Eyes' strength!
Galaxy-Eyes' effect activates!
When Galaxy-Eyes battles, it can exclude this monster and the monster that declared the battle!
Hope!
Now your battle wont continue!
So, what will you do now?
I now end the battle!
At this moment Galaxy-Eyes' effect activates!
This turn, Galaxy-Eyes' effect will bring back the monsters excluded after the battle ends on the field!
Hope, so it wasn't defeated...
Since Hope is back, his attack will be canceled!
This is Galaxy-Eyes' true strength!
Galaxy-Eyes, if the excluded monster was a Xyz Monster,
It absorbs it's overlay units, and for each unit it's attack power goes up by 500 points!
What?
Hope's overlay units...!
The units absorbed from from No. are 2!
So Galaxy Eyes' attack power goes up by 1000 points!
An attack power of 4000!?
4000 is exactly the same as my life!
Kaito-sama, extract every drop of his soul!
Soul?
If that's it, the criminal back then...
He indeed looked like he just had his soul taken.
How dare you!?
It's absolutely despicable to impose the opponent with such fear!
I apologize, I apologize!
W-What does he mean? Answer me!
Half-hearted fear will only make you feel worse, so I'll explain.
The way I get the Nos. is a little overbearing.
When I take the Numbers, your soul will also be taken!
And where does that soul go?
Don't know, and I don't want to influence that!
No way...
Yuma's soul is at stake in this duel...
I set 1 card face-down and end my turn!
My turn, Draw!
Galaxy-Eyes attack him!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
Only Nos. can defeat Nos.,
But you'll still take the damage!
Then I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Photon Wind!
This card, during my battle phase, If the opponent's monster couldn't be destroyed and took battle damage I inflict 1000 points of damage!
What, He knew that the Numbers couldn't be destroyed!?
Then with Photon Wind's effect I draw 1 card!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Astral...
My own life.. seems to be depleting...
Damn it!
Don't stand up!
Just surrender this way.
If you don't you'll just feel more unnecessary pain.
Stop kidding me!
I praise you for you fighting spirit, but you will regret it!
I won't give up at this rate!
Then as you wish, I'll take away your soul!
My turn!
Yuma...
My turn, Draw!
Damn, this guy is unbelievably strong!
Even Hope that brings it to em' don't stand a chance.
What should I do? What should I do?
That's right, only Nos. can defeat Nos., his monster isn't a No.!
So if I switch Hope to defense mode, It can always stop it's attacks!
Is that so?
That boy used Numbers to summon Galaxy-Eyes.
Don't you think he already read your mind of switching Nos. to defense mode?
But, what should I do?
You said that "Offense is the best defense".
Stick to that
Well thats right!
If I lose this duel you'll disappear!
Correct, this time we're in the same situation.
Aren't you scared?
I don't know.
However, theres nothing else left.
This is my destiny.
He's so calm!
Do you always have your life at risk while dueling?
Yuma, get over your fear!
You can't win against this opponent if you show your back!
Bring it to em'! Yuma!
Let's Go! Astral!
In this duel let's unite our strength!
Here I go! I'll bring it to em'!
I summon Zubaba Knight!
I activate the Trap, Copy Knight!
Copy Knight, when a level 4 or lower Warrior type monster is summoned on the field,
This card is Special Summoned with the same level as that monster!
I overlay the level 3 Zubaba Knight and Copy Knight!
The 2 monsters will open the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 17 Leviath Dragon!
Oh my!
A Numbers!!!
A second Numbers, confirmed!
His second Numbers?
I see, your a Numbers hunter too.
It's fine to underestimate unnecessary things!
I'll take all of your Numbers!
I activate Leviath Dragon's monster effect!
Leviath Dragon, for once per turn by detaching 1 overlay unit, it's attack power goes up by 500 points!
But thats far away from my Galaxy-Eyes' attack power!
That's not what I'm aiming for!
I activate the Magic Card, Cross Attack!
If I have 2 monsters with the same attack power on my field,
On of the monsters can't declare an attack, and the other one can attack directly!
On my field there are Hope and Leviath Dragon with the same attack power of 2500!
Even if you decrease that boy's life, we don't know how the duel will end!
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope! Attack directly!
An unexpected strategist?
Hope Sword Slash!!
Trying to evade defeat by attacking!?
But...
Trap activate, Photonize!
This card, if there's a Light monster on the field,
If the opponent battled, It negated the attack of that monster,
And 1 of my own LIGHT monster's attack power goes up by the attack power of that monster!
A-An attack power of 6500!?
If I take his attack, there no way I can win...
Yuma...
Damn!
It's an assumption!
An assumption?
Listen carefully, Yuma.
You have one chance of a counter-attack.
A counter attack!? But such a thing...
Set the trap card in your hand.
My Trap?
The one I have is Holy Armor -Mirror Mail-m
That's right, -Mirror Mail-m, if the opponent's battles,
It will change the attack power of the targeted monster to attack power of his attacking monster
That's right!
Even if their attack power is the same, only Nos. can defeat Nos.
In summary, if his Galaxy-Eyes is destroyed, my Hope will remain.
So this is the counter-attack you talked about?
That's right.
Alright, I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Come on Haruto give me more!
My turn, Draw!
Bring it!
It's coming.
I summon Photon Cerberus!
In the turn this card is summon, Trap Cards can't be activated!
What!?
Now, -Mirror Mail-m can't be activated!
What's the matter!?
Do you thing I'd be reckless to attack with you having a face-down card?
Impossible, this boy's duel... is further above me!?
I'll take away your soul!
Go! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Astral!
It's... over now.
Bro...ther...
Photon Stream of-!
Kaito-sama!
Haruto...!
This duel is canceled!
My name is Kaito, remember it well!
Let's Go, Orbital 7!
Understood!
Yuma, what happened?
My arms and legs didn't act like I wanted them to...
"Bringing it to 'em" my foot...
Duel Champion my foot...
How can I become a duel champion in this way!?
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
Have many Magic and Trap cards can be set?
5 cards, or maybe 6 cards?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Due to grandma's order, we came to this place which is far away from the city.
But Yuma, this is...
That's the training base for Dueling, a wise old man is waiting for us.
That man is...
Awesome! Black Magician, and Blue Eyes!
What happened? I become the monster?
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
A Fight to Death! The Duel Lodge; Legendary Monsters Reborn!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is: 6
5 for the Magic and Trap Zone.
And one for the Field Spell Zone. Don't mess it up!