Wh-What's the deal?!
I was just capturing your future on film.
See? It's right here.
Your future has been photographed.
It depicts you lying on the ground after losing this Duel.
Like hell I'll believe that bogus photo!
You can't change a future that's been photographed.
That was decided the moment I flashed my shutter.
All photos I shoot depict the future.
And it is sure to... become a reality.
Is that darn Shark... really Dueling for revenge?
I will exact revenge on you here and now!
Yuma, don't get involved with me anymore...
Yuma?
It's not just Shark... Even that IV guy...
Such painful and twisted expressions!
It shines only during my service!
Take my fanservice!
Dueling isn't a tool for revenge!
Duels aren't meant to hurt people!
All Duelists are friends!
So why?!
Hey, look Yuma! It's a blimp!
It must be a special occasion to celebrate the opening of the Carnival!
Maybe riding it will lift your spirits.
Let's look at Heartland City from up in the sky!
It's unacceptable! There's no excuse!
Hey, how about it?
No excuse!
We're supposed to be friends! We're supposed to enjoy ourselves!
C'mon, obviously we're all friends.
That's why we should cheer each other up.
This ain't funny!
Oh, gawd!
What're you so worried about?
Fine, just do whatever you want!
Shouldn't you go after her?
Kotori seems to be really worrying about you.
Shut up! Just keep out of it!
Fine then.
Darn it...
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Shuuta Hayami?
Ah, that freelancer photographer you
were talking about, editor-in-chief.
"Number 35: The Shocking Scoop!
Kotori's Dangerous Future!"
You told the guy, "It needs to have a bigger impact" and claimed he would give us a trashy reputation.
But lately, he's been able to capture major events on camera before any other journalists even got a chance to report on them!
That amateur photographer somehow managed to capture one scoop after another on film before anyone else.
He shocked many experts around the world!
You have absolutely no idea, eh?
I realize you have other work, but I want you to make contact with this Shuuta Hayami and collect data on him!
Huh!?
Anyway, I want you to convince him to enter a contract with our company's monopoly!
Our sources tell us he is a participant in the Duel Carnival.
His current location is...
God, why me?!
What the hell's that photo supposed to be?!
That's...
It isn't a lie.
This depicts your future.
Here's the proof.
What you see in these pictures will happen...
...as you can see.
I can change the future.
I can then reveal that future in the form of a photograph.
The future?
And that is why I will never lose in a Duel!
So you also didn't have a Number?
Wait!
You okay?
What the hell is that guy?
These photographs were taken before this actually happened...
Does that mean he can really control the future?
Then all the scoops he captured on film up until now...
What were you doing? I'm in a hurry here, so answer immediately!
Big Sis...
You've heard of Shuuta Hayami, haven't you?
Iyami?
No, it's Hayami!
You should know him if he's participating in the Carnival, shouldn't you?
What do you take me for?
I don't know a guy like that!
We can't allow him to create any more incidents.
Incidents? Whatcha mean by that?
Shuuta Hayami seems to have the power to make any future he sees in his mind become a reality.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't fully believe it 100% myself.
But I saw him take a picture of the future.
And they let a guy like that into the Duel Carnival?
I don't know why. And since I don't know why, I'm investigating.
But with that power of his, he can't lose a Duel.
Anyway, if you find Shuuta Hayami, I want you to contact me immediately!
Got it?!
Gosh, what gives?
He won't lose because he can see the future?
But if there is any truth to it, there's a chance this person might be possessed by a Number.
By a Number?
This is cause for investigation.
Yuma, go find him. This man named Shuuta Hayami.
God, every single one of 'em ordering me around... Who do you people think you are?
Right, Kotori?
Huh? Where'd she go?
She left a while ago after you said some terrible things to her.
Huh?!
You really don't remember?
I did that to Kotori? Like heck would I ever!
Kotori! Kotori?
Observation #17: "When human beings hurt one another with their words, they have no memory of it afterward."
Now I understand how you feel, Kotori.
If Yuma really wants to be by himself, I'll just go up in the sky by myself!
Say cheese, everyone!
Look this way! Ready!
Cheese!
Good! Okay!
Upperclassman!
Upperclassman Hayami!
Mizuki-kun?
It's been so long!
It's been about a year or so since I took that picture of you, Mizuki-kun.
Yes, and it looks so pretty!
Though it was a bit embarrassing when it was chosen to be shown in the arts festival.
But it made me happy.
Even now, I consider that photo to be one of my greatest works.
It's a very pleasant middle school memory.
You haven't changed.
Huh? Me?
Yes!
The smiles on those kids' faces...
You still take such nice pictures that really bring out the charm of those in them.
Oh yeah. Let me take a new shot using the blimp as the background.
Sure! Of course you can!
Man, I can't believe I have to find this guy.
I don't even now this Iyami, er, I mean Hayami's face.
How am I supposed to spot him?
Sounds like there's a Duel over there. Let's go.
H-Hey!
That's...!
I knew it...
Th-There's no way something in a picture can come true!
It's flat out impossible!
Attack the enemy Monster!
Sure-Kill First Grade Shot!!
See? Just as I said it would be.
You were fated to be buried in three turns.
I captured all of it on the pictures I shot.
The future?
And they are sure to become reality!
These pictures...
He predicted the future?
He can control the future just like my big sis said!
Hey, you all right?! Hey!
Let's get him to a hospital!
Right!
So he really was using a Number.
Hey, you all right?!
Hey!
Why are they Dueling like this?
Hey, wait!
Are you Hayami?
Why?! Why can't you just enjoy Dueling?
Duelists are supposed to be friends, so why do you need to go that far?!
Why?
Isn't that obvious? It's so I can obtain Numbers!
Unfortunately, that man earlier wasn't a Numbers holder.
But my search will continue!
So I can obtain all the Numbers in the entire world!
Doing so will produce even greater photos!
I'll continue shocking everyone all over the world by capturing unbelievable pictures of big scoops!
This guy's trying to gather the Numbers all on his own!
So you know about the existence of Numbers?
Could... Could you possibly...
Yeah, I have some!
I see! So you have Numbers!
I do! But I'll never let a guy like you-
I thought I told you to inform me the second you found him!
S-Sis!
Do you remember me, Shuuta Hayami?
Well, I guess I can't blame you for not remembering an amateur reporter like me.
But I bet you remember the editor-in-chief of the Net News who rejected all of your pictures.
Oh, you bet I remember him.
He belittled me severely and told me, "News photos need to have a bigger impact"!
Well, now the editor-in-chief wants to enter a contract with you, bit I won't accept that.
There's no way I could ever acknowledge a guy who puts the lives of others in danger
just to be the first to capture pictures of a big scoop!
I put their lives in danger?
I'm shocked! I'm simply trying to capture "nice pictures"!
And you're using this weird power you got that lets you change the future to do so?
Lets him change the future?
You did this before, didn't you?
This incident.
You said something like, "The future will move as I command it to."
Oh yes, I can do that.
Using the power of the Numbers, anyway.
I suppose you won't believe it until you see it.
It sounds like the power of the Number this man is being controlled by has the power to control the future.
Control?
I'll give you these pictures, so please hurry and get out of the way.
I have no doubt that the editor-in-chief will be more than pleased with them!
Stop joking!
I don't see anyone joking.
I'm very busy.
I need to Duel this guy over here, you see.
Yuma, don't do it. You can't Duel with such a dangerous guy.
If you call yourself a reporter, surely you don't have the time to laze about here, right?
Oh yeah, I'll give you a little present that will give you another really big scoop!
This one may make you nauseous, though.
But it can't he helped, since you cornered me like this.
Kotori!
Kotori-chan!
Oh? Are you two by any chance acquaintances of this girl?
In that case, you had best hurry along.
An incident will occur soon, you see, where that blimp has a wee bit of engine trouble in the skies of Heartland City.
That photograph there holds within it the coming of one of the largest scoops to ever strike this area to be caught on film.
And if it should happen... No, all of my photos are bound to become reality.
And you can bet Heartland City will be lead into a big panic.
How could you?
Now hurry along and show the editor-in-chief that picture.
Once that picture of the incident hits the web, the entire world will feel its impact.
Stop this!
Don't do something so stupid!
"Stupid", indeed.
Kotori! Answer me, Kotori!
Hey, Kotori!
Why are you contacting me now for?
What do you want?
Where are you right now?
Somewhere you'll never find me, Yuma!
Don't tell me... On the blimp?
Are you riding on that blimp?!
Oh, you bet I am!
Why can't I?
Are you all right?!
Yup, I'm having a blast up here!
It feels good to look at that city like this.
Not that! I mean, is there anything out of the ordinary?
Huh? Out of the ordinary?
Kotori!
Hey, look over there!
The engine!
What about the engine?
Kotori!
You need to stop this at once!
Hurry and stop it!
No can do, because this just became reality.
You were the one who made it reality, right?! Return it to normal!
Boy do you ever shock me.
As a reporter, you should be jumping for joy right about now.
Who are reporters? They seek out scoops, right?
Now you've done it!
Hitting me won't change this reality.
And while we waste our time like this, the blimp draws ever closer to its impending peril.
Yuma!
I'll do something about the blimp.
Don't you dare take your eyes off this guy!
Finally that nagging pest's gone away.
So how about we begin?
Astral...
If the one being controlled by a Number loses the Duel and has the Number taken away,
they should return to normal, right?
Right.
Meaning if I beat this guy, the future depicted in that photo will disappear and Kotori will be safe, right?
Spot on. However...
Let's go, Shuuta!
Let's Duel!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel Target, locked on!
Wh-What the heck are you doing?!
I'm capturing your future on film!
See? Your future is depicted right here.
It shows you after you lose this Duel and have all your Numbers taken away.
The future shown in these pictures cannot be changed.
My victory and your miserable defeat was decided the moment I flashed my shutter.
Cut the crap!
My future won't be decided by someone like you!
Duel!!
I'm taking the first turn!
My turn! Draw!
I set a Monster in face-down Defense Mode!
And I'll set a card face-down and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Scoop Shooter!
The Monster Yuma set face-down in Defense Mode was Gogogo Golem.
It has 1500 Defense Points.
On the other side, Scoop Shooter has 1400 Attack Points.
If he attacks like this, the opponent will receive damage.
I activate the Equipment Magic, Telephoto Lens, from my hand!
I equip Telephoto Lens to Scoop Shooter!
The Monster equipped with this card gains 400 Attack Power for each card in my hand.
I have four cards in my hand.
So it gains 1600 Attack Points!
It's got 3000 Attack Points!
But it's okay. Gogogo Golem can't be destroyed by the opponent's Monster in battle once per turn.
I then activate the Magic Card, Negative -> Positive Swap, from my hand!
This card forces a face-down Defense Monster to switch into face-up Attack Mode!
And their Attack Power is switched with their Defense Power!
What?!
Using Negative -> Positive Swap reduced my hand by one.
So Scoop Shooter's Attack Power goes down 400 points.
A slight drawback...
But this will be more than enough.
Go, Scoop Shooter!
Attack Gogogo Golem!
We have urgent news.
It seems the blimp flying over Heartland City's skies is currently experiencing engine trouble.
It'll be okay. I promise it'll be okay...
Yuma...
Wait for me, Kotori!
I promise I'll help you!
Not happening!
It's been decided! The picture you saw before was just the outcome,
but this entire Duel is depicted in these pictures here.
On the fifth turn, you will Summon No. 39, Aspiring Emperor - Hope,
and on the sixth turn, you will be defeated by my Number.
The future has been captured within these photographs!
And they will not fail to become reality!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
The future he created using the power of the Numbers...
I'll lose this Duel and Kotori will perish on board the blimp...!
Is there no way for us to win?
If this keeps up...
You're the one who said you decide your own future.
If I can muster up the courage to bring it to 'em, I can change the future!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
""Power To Open A Path To The Future! Hope Ray, The Lord Of Hope"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Let's review the Heart Pieces!
The pieces are all broken up and not all of them fit each other.
The players decide how many pieces they bet!
I gotta hurry and collect five Heart Pieces so I can complete my heart!