Hey, did you hear?
Two kids from our school participating in the World Duel Carnival made it to the tournament finals.
Ryoga-sama was a given, but I can't believe that kid also...
Yup, yup.
Um, who was he again?
That kid with the catchphrase...
- Um...
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Wanna autograph?
I won't hesitate to give our autographs!
H-How about it?
My autograph!
I'll give you my autograph!
Lemme autograph!
I'll autograph for you!
Isn't Tsukumo-kun getting a little full of himself?
Looks that way.
That idiot.
To summarize, he's a braggart.
Hey, c'om, lemme autograph!
That hurts, hurts, hurts, hurts, Kotori!
Stop showing off!
Gosh...
You really are an idiot.
But I made it all the way to the finals, you know.
Let me enjoy myself a bit.
Oh, that's right.
Lookie here.
Take a look at this!
Tada!
I got me an official invitation!
The invitation to the Night Ceremony prior the Finals! It'll be held tonight at Heartland!
Eh?!
Amazing!
There's got to be a lot of Dueling celebrities attending!
Cat! What should I wear?
- This is exciting!
- Hey! I'm the one who got invited!
I just thought of a great plan.
I'm not gonna let Yuma hog all the enjoyment!
The strongest Duelists from around the world have gathered.
They've come to fight it out in the World Duel Carnival.
I beat many guys and finally qualified for the tournament finals!
I don't care how strong they are! Bring 'em!
I'm gonna win the championship!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
"Number 50: The Eve of the Storm!
The Diabolical Duelist Appears - Tron!"
Wait, Tron.
Strengthen me, just like you did with III!
I'm disappointed in you and III.
Wha...?!
Why, you...!
You know, III fought...
...against the Original Number and ended up like that!
Like he is right now!
I want results.
If you guys are unable to do this, I have other options.
Like Ryoga Kamishiro.
I dragged him into this tournament for that purpose.
Why...?
Why, Tron?!
Kaito-sama!
You're at your limit!
If you use Photon Mode anymore to search for Numbers,
your recovery will take even longer!
You're pushing yourself far too much.
You sure that's a good idea, Kaito?
K-Kaito-sama's body is...!
As you can see, it's not a problem.
That's good to hear.
Now is the time to act, while the Numbers have been gathered in Heartland City.
We have high expectations for you, after all.
I know that.
But you better help Haruto as you promised.
Of course. You needn't worry about that.
Ah, that's right.
We'll be expecting you at tonight's ceremony.
Getting a glimpse of the Number Users beforehand may not be a bad idea.
Man, Heartland always looks so friggin' awesome!
For real! It's so pretty!
Cat!
Kotori, you really went all out with that outfit.
As they say, "Chickens need feathers, people need clothes."
Chicken?!
Yours suits you well too, Cat-chan!
That Monster Cat cosplay of yours!
Monster?
What's your problem?!
Stop it, you two. We managed to come to Heartland...
Heartland...
This place was built by Dr. Faker.
A dreamland where everyone from children to adults can have fun.
Children who live in poverty are treated with priority.
When you think about it, such philosophy is praised worldwide.
The total area is...
How did you know all that?
It seems that the Numbers obtained from III
contained the memory pieces of information about this world.
I can’t help but to feel your top-to-bottom view has become even sharper…
This must be the party's assembly hall!
To summarize, it's a red carpet!
I kind of feel like a star.
Meow, meow~!
No means no!
Those uninvolved are not permitted to enter!
I got me an invitation right...
...here.
As you see.
It's gone!
Yuma, you can't mean... again...?
You lost it...
I already said that I'm a finalist!
How can a kid like you be a finalist?
It's true!
If so, show us your invitation!
Well...
Now go on home.
Everything has a flip side.
Tokunosuke?
I came up with an idea.
That’s the female Duelist, Milky Kulala!
Even red carpets have a flip side.
I finally get the chance to wear a dress and it's ruined.
Thank you!
What the?!
Shoot!
Yuma-kun?
Wait up!
God, you really are an idiot!
I'll utilize Yuma and those idiots.
Please give me your autograph!
I'm a fan of yours!
It's someone who qualified for the tournament finals...
Hey, kid!
I told you I'm...
You little prankster!
I was wondering who it was, and it turned out to be Yuma Tsukumo.
You're...
Gauche-sama!
You're making a big scene as always.
What'd you do this time?
Well, he came here without an invitation!
It's fine. He may not look like it, but he's a final participant.
Yes, but...
You feel like you can't believe me?
N-No, sir...
Let's go.
Yeah...
Whacha think? My mood's quite the...
A-Amazing...!
That’s one of the finalists,
the Black Panther from the midst of South America, Garcia Panther!
On that side, it’s the white-night noble, Beroman Sakata!
A-And...
The Fallguys!
During countless Duel Tournaments,
this Dark Trio pushed their opponents to the abyss of terror with their overwhelming might!
Where's Shark?
He's here, isn't he?
Kaito!
That's...
Yuma Tsukumo... You are Kazuma-san's son, right?
Your dad is alive.
In the Astral World.
That's quite unusual coming from you.
Screw you!
Why did you put Haruto through that...?!
Even you're my former mentor…
...you won't forgive me, right?
Why...? Tell me why...
What is your goal?
We merely obey Tron's will.
Tron...?
You will meet him eventually.
Don't tell me... he's in the finals?
Do you really think you'll defeat me and Tron with your body in this condition?
They're gone...
I wanted to ask him something...
Okay, here you are.
You're next, right?
Yes!
Fanservice is my motto, after all.
Move!
You're in my way!
What's wrong?
Where's your usual insults?
The time I've been waiting for is almost here.
I will bet everything I have to defeat you!
You look stressed.
Droite...
I've been able to tell something's wrong with you for a while now.
What are you talking about?
I received word from the medical room.
Your body is already...
You've got bad taste.
It's unfortunate about Haruto.
I know you have to collect Numbers at all costs.
But...
You shouldn't enter the finals.
I have no reason to listen to you.
Kaito!
V is in the finals...
He's now with this man named Tron who kidnapped Haruto.
Kaito!
Above all else, I won't...
...lose against that guy!
I'm just thinking about you...
You showed me quite the night ceremony befitting what is to come.
This is the fruit of our steadily progressing plan.
Has the main cast been gathered?
All but one have shown up.
Who is it?
A Duelist disguising himself as Tron.
Tron?
Does that ring any bells?
No.
Then I, as the representative of Heartland,
will deliver the reception speech to the finalists.
To summarize, Tokunosuke-kun didn't come inside with all of us?
I don't see him anywhere.
Could you be...?
To summarize, you're the powerful Duelist, The Vampire of Dawn, Lord of Terror Nagashima!
To summarize...
Please give me your autograph!
The Class Rep loves collecting his autographs.
Thank you very much!
Flip the flip side!
Flip?
Heart Burning!
Ladies and gentleman!
And all present Duelists!
Are you enjoying the party?!
Starting tomorrow, the Duel Carnival finally reaches the Final!
Please allow me to reintroduce the remaining 23 warriors!
First...!
Wha-What the?
Ah, what a big cake!
And y-you are...?
I'm Tron!
Call me Tron.
Tron...
So that's...Tron?
Gramps...
What is it?
Is something the matter?
Gramps, I'm gonna...
...crush you guys into the ground!
You know, I love cake!
Say, the kid down there!
Let's meet in the finals.
You can see me, can't you?
He's gone!
What's going on?
Eh? Where'd he go?
He's gone!
Just what is he...?
Over there! It's him! Him!
My impostor!
Shoot!
You guys did it again, huh?!
No we didn't!
Damn you!
To summarize, it was Tokunosuke-kun!
So that's what he meant when he said flip the flip side!
Hey! Wait up!
I said you've got it wrong!
Tron...
Is Haruto okay?
You have no reason to be worried about him.
Just focus on settling the score with me.
Kaito...
I will give it my all.
Same here, man!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not going to give my all to defeat you.
I meant Astral!
Darn you!
So you're going to hire us or something, right?
Yes.
We're expensive.
Then we'll start with a small deposit.
The rest comes when you complete your job.
And the target is...?
A boy named Yuma Tsukumo.
Got 'em!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The Duel Carnival Tournament Finals have finally begun!
It’s the final battle between the strongest Duelists who qualified for the Final!
Wait, Duel Coasters?!
Wow, sounds like fun!
Be careful.
There might be some unknown strong opponents among them!
Huh? It's gone!
My Heart Pieces are gone!
Yuma, it's coming!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Here we come, Tournament Finals! Duel Coasters, Go!"
A three-on-one Duel?!
Today we're introducing Heroic Champion Excalibur!
Its effect doubles its Attack Power.
It can save you in a pinch.
Then I got no need for it!
Have you forgotten the time you and Kaito were in a pinch?
I'll permit a Tsukumo Pinch!
Like heck I will!