The strongest Duelists from all over the world clash during the World Duel Carnival.
One must collect five Heart Pieces in order to enter the Finals.
I already got four Heart Pieces! I'm definitely making it to the Finals!
My dear brave Duelists, you've endured the Duel Carnival until the very end!
Tomorrow is your last day to compete for Heart Pieces!
Warriors, rest up for now
and prepare to assault once again tomorrow!
Heart Burning!
Kaito-sama, you use Photon Mode to Number Hunt far too much!
If you keep it up, Kaito-sama, your body will...
I don't need you to worry about me.
Just keep your mouth shut and continue gathering information on the Numbers.
U-Understood!
Haruto.
How are you feeling?
Brother...
I'm steadily collecting the Numbers.
Very soon...
I will cure your sickness very soon.
Just endure it a bit longer...
Brother...
I'm okay. It's nothing.
I must go...
Wh-What is that?!
C'mon, I went so far to root for you.
This is the least you can do to thank me for not abandoning you.
Even so...
God... You're gonna get fat...
Did you say something?
No... Nothing.
Wh-What the?
That kid's in danger!
H-He's...
Kaito's little brother?
Yuma!
What the heck are you-
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
"Number 40:
The Visitor from Heartland, Haruto"
Yuma...
Yuma!
Huh?
Look, Yuma.
Eh?
Wha-
What the heck is this?!
What in the world happened?
He most likely activated some kind of power during the moment of the crash,
which sent everything within that dimension flying back.
Just what is this young boy...?
Aren't you cold?
Huh? Wha-
C-Could you be able to...?
Are you able to see me?
Why? Who are you?
Hey, you serious?!
You can even talk to him?!
My name is Astral.
Astral...
Do you know me?
Yuma!
Are you okay?
About that...
Th-This is pretty bad.
Let's go, Yuma!
Eh?!
I want to hear this child out!
Even if you say that...!
Fine! Guess there's no helping it!
Y-Yuma!
H-Hey! That was my car!
Man oh man, he went and put a giant hole in there!
Guess he was in a surprisingly bold mood.
How can you be so carefree about this?
If Mr. Heartland hears about this...
Heh, good point.
Then I guess we shouldn't let Kaito hear about it either.
His mood'll be scary if he hears Haruto went missing.
Let's go.
Hmm?
This evening in C Block of the eastern area of the city,
at intersection 3562, an incident occurred that toppled a mobile trailer.
Whoa, this became huge news just like that!
Why the heck did I have to bring him home with me?!
Yuma's making a fuss.
Yuma's throwing a fit.
Where did you come from? Why do you know me?
Hey, why aren't you cold?
Yuma!
Huh?
Dinner's ready!
You should help out a little!
Whoa! Duel Karaage!
["Duel Fried Chicken strips"]
Duel Yakiniku
["Duel Grilled Fish (Or Meat)"]
Duel-jiru!
["Soup with Dueling in it"]
Even Duel Nikujaga!
["Duel Meat-Potato"]
Looks delicious!
Hey!
Say itadakimasu first!
[Expression of gratitude]
That's right. It's bad manners when we're in front of a guest.
I got it.
Eat as much as you want!
So let's dig in!
Itadakimasu!
Granny, this nikujaga is delicious!
Is it! Eat your fill!
You aren't gonna eat anything?
You aren't hungry?
Don't feel the need to hold back.
Maybe you should hold back some.
What's your problem?
What?
- Why're you singling me out?
- Haruto.
- I haven't gotten to eat much.
- Liar! You ate a ton of meat already!
I did not eat it!
How is it? Good, right?
This is how you eat with everyone.
Haruto...
Ask for seconds.
Seconds.
Listen up. If you find the boy, notify me right away.
Don't try to lay your hands on him, or you'll end up like that hole.
But I wonder where that kid came from.
I'm not sure.
I have no way of contacting Kaito, and I don't know where the guy's at.
Kaito? If you meet him, you may end up Dueling against him again.
And if you lose...
Well, what happens happens.
Yuma.
Huh?
I have a lot of things I want to ask him... Haruto.
I'm certain that he knows something about me.
Brother...
Brother!
Well, tomorrow I'll take him-
Haruto!
Wait for me, Brother.
Shit! Where the heck did Haruto run off to?
There could be another incident like before...
That's it!
Huh?
This way!
Wait! Hey!
What happened?
What was that? Was like an explosion...
Hey, what's the deal here?
What happened?
This must be Haruto's doing.
Yeah, there's no mistaking it.
Then he might still be around here.
Haruto!
Found him!
Hey, wait up!
Where do you think you're going?
I must go...
Go... where?
To that place.
Brother is...
You're looking for Kaito, aren't you?
I understand. I promise I'll bring you back to Kaito's place tomorrow.
So for today...
Yuma!
Kotori, get away from him!
Huh?
H-Haruto...
Oh, there you are!
We got a response at Block B-12.
Are you positive?
Yeah. The change in atmosphere after a dimensional overspill ain't a joke.
That boy just used his power. He's in high spirits!
Brother...
He's really trying to go meet Kaito.
Yeah, more than likely.
Wh-What the?
Found you!
Okay boy, your evening stroll ends here.
Hmm? You're...!
What do you want with us?!
That's for me to feel. Why are you with Haruto?
Well... He kinda... spent the night with me.
I took him in!
I don't get a damn thing you're saying.
Okay, boy. We're going back.
Going back where?
What are you gonna do with Haruto?
It has nothing to do with you two.
Now let's go.
Haruto...
Hey! Wait a minute!
Haruto doesn't look like he wants to!
You're such a persistent brat! He's just going back to Heartland!
Now, let's go back to Heartland.
Wh-What the?
Do not get in my way.
What? There's a large rise in the dimensional distribution!
Run, Gauche!
The controls...!
Droite!
Gauche! Are you safe?!
Yeah...!
What?!
I understand, Haruto.
If you want to go to Kaito, I'm definitely gonna take you there!
The boy's with those middle school brats!
Listen! Find them at all costs!
Yuma Tsukumo...! That bastard!
Brother...
Is Kaito on the other side of that door?
Yuma...
If Kaito's there...
What's going on?
Kaito isn't here.
Where...? Where are you?
Gone... Gone!
He's gone!
Hey, Haruto!
He's not here!
What do you mean he's not here?
I thought you were looking for Kaito... for your brother?
It's really small...
It's small and sweet...
Small...?
When my brother isn't around...
Haruto!
Isn't this light different from the other times?
This is...
Could this light be...?
Hey!
We should be fine after coming this far. Don't worry.
Haruto, I will protect you at all costs.
Haruto...
Here.
It's called caramel.
It's got a magical power that makes you feel better.
Eat it, Haruto.
Delicious...! It's really delicious!
I feel better!
I see...
Huh? But what about you, Brother...?
I'm fine so long as you're doing fine.
Brother...
Haruto... I'll stay with you forever.
Let go! Let go of me!
Haruto!
Now, let's go back to Heartland, Haruto.
Haruto!!
Brother...
This time, I will...
BROTHER!
Haruto!!
Yuma!
Haruto's searching for something called caramel!
Caramel?
What do we need caramel for?
Haruto likely came here so Kaito could give him caramel!
So Kaito could?
This is bad, Yuma! At this rate, Haruto's power will swallow up everything!
What?!
Sh-Shit...
What should we do?
Haruto, why do you want caramel?
Kotori!
Do you have any caramel on you?
Caramel?
Haruto... Haruto!
Look at this! This is what you're after, isn't it?
This caramel!
You wanted Kaito to give this to you, right?
I'll... let you...
...meet with Kaito!
So...
I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Haruto, you aren't alone.
You aren't alone!
Brother is... always tired because of me.
So...
This time, I wanted to give my brother caramel.
I wanted him to eat the caramel.
I saw Haruto's memories.
Those two were running away from something and were cornered here.
When he saw Haruto was nervous and sad, Kaito gave it to him to give him courage.
More than likely, he wanted to do the same for his brother Kaito.
Haruto... You...
Those guys just won't quit!
I won't let you take Haruto!
If you want some of this, come and-
Wh-Who are you?
I will grant Haruto-sama's wish.
H-Hey, Haruto!
You...
It seems Haruto-sama wanted to see me again.
Let's go.
Hey, hold up a minute!
My mission is to destroy the Astral World.
In order to produce more screams.
Haruto...! Haruto!
Haruto... Just who are you...?
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
What the heck do you mean?
The guy we handed Haruto over hasn't returned yet?!
I'm not lying!
There's a white stone inside the rainbow?
I can hear his voice...
Kaito, I promised Haruto.
That I would definitely reunite you two!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Haruto's Gone! A New Enemy, Tron"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Kaito sure is worried about Haruto!
But now that I think about it, that's just how you treat a little brother.
Is that how sibling relationships work?
Man, I sure want a sibling!
You have one right here!
Oh yeah!