The Duel between Shark and IV has started, full of rage and revenge!
In order to win, Shark Summoned his Number.
But, after receiving eight consecutive brutal attacks from IV,
he has fallen onto the field!
Shark, don't tell me you...
Shark...
Shark!
Hey, Shark!
Get a hold of yourself, Shark!
Astral!
Can't you do something about this?
It's useless.
This chain is made by Varian's power.
For you, who only has power from the Astral World, it is impossible to untie it.
In that case, we have to defeat you in a Duel, right?
Let's settle the score, Tron!
A Duel? Not right now!
After all, we'll miss this entertaining show!
You jerk! This kind of thing's useless against my Bring It To 'em!
Bring it to 'em?
Kazuma had that catchphrase as well.
But he wasn't able to return from the Parallel Worlds.
Ryoga, I won't allow you to surrender!
So stand up, Ryoga.
Stand up and come at me!
Let me give you the final and greatest fanservice!
Ryoga...
You...
Now is the time to accept me.
Become one with me, Ryoga!
Accept me!
No! I...
I already...
I won't be consumed by the likes of Numbers again!
Hey, Shark...Shark!
Shark...?!
I... I...
His expression seems a bit strange.
He is suffering!
Huh?!
The Number is trying to manipulate his heart once again!
What?
Accept me...
Accept me, and release the darkness inside your heart!
If you wish to win, you must accept me!
Become one with me!
No!
No! I... I...
I... definitely won't...
...be controlled by someone else!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Continuous Magic from my hand, Different Dimension Depths!
"Number 58: Shark Awakens!
A New Chaos Number Appears"
A new Chaos Numbers appears!
It banishes one Water-Attribute Monster on my field!
What?
Banish?!
No, it's good. He'll be able to deny the allure of his Number this way.
And since it was banished,
Heaven's Strings' effect is also negated!
I see!
Awesome!
You are awesome, Shark!
Then I set a new Monster in Face-Down Defense Position.
I ...will then...end my turn!
I praise you for that, Ryoga.
I can't believe you actually gave up using Shark Drake.
But now you have just lost your trump.
But I still have Heaven's Strings with 3000 Attack Points.
And this Monster is equipped with Destiny Strings.
It is capable of attacking consecutively like moments ago.
You no longer have a chance of winning!
Is that so?
The Equip Magic, Destiny Strings, comes with great risk.
Tron...
To activate its effects, you must send one card from your deck to the Graveyard.
But it won't work if the drawn card isn't a Monster Card.
And, say the card you draw isn't a Monster,
then you cannot attack, and the battle will end.
You drawing all Monsters before was nothing but luck.
You don't trust me?
I'm just saying it's all just a matter of probability.
I am a scientist, after all.
You've always been like this.
Differing from V and III, who are calm and cautious,
you are hotblooded, impulsive, and loose your temper easily.
Tron!
See? Exactly like I said.
It would serve you best to think this over calmly right now.
If you can even do that, that is...
It's just as Tron said.
Just what would such a risky gamble merit him?
You... You really can't trust me this much?
Just because I can't become an obedient servant like V and III...
But even so... I still also... for your sake...
Dad!
Dad, you always smiled gently in the past,
warmly watching me and my brothers grow.
But...
After you returned from the Parallel Worlds, it's like you had an entirely different personality!
You became the grim avenger, Tron.
Despite that, we were still willing to follow you, Tron.
That includes incriminating Ryoga with our trap, and even his younger sister...
Stop pretending to be a victim!
Even if you were being used, I still won't forgive what you did!
And I don't plan to run from you!
I will settle the score with you here and now!
And I will be the winner!
I will be the one to defeat Dr. Faker!
I will not allow you to assassinate Dr. Faker!
Once Dr. Faker is defeated, Tron will return to his normal self...
Change back to our father, Byron Arklight.
I firmly believe that you are still there!
For your sake, I even did something that cruel!
Even so...
Even so, I...
You still don't trust me?!
I will not trust anyone anymore.
I can only trust myself, as well as the Varian World!
Because they are the ones who saved me!
Varian...
Which makes me your pawn in the end, huh?
III became your sacrificial pawn! The same for V!
But I'm not a mere pawn!
I am now the Asian Duel Champion!
You can't use me that easily!
My turn! Draw!
Screw it! I'll show you I have technique and luck!
Here I come! I attack with Heaven's Strings, equipped with the Equip Magic, Destiny Strings!
Is he planning to gamble once again?
I draw one card from my deck and send it to the Graveyard!
If it's a Monster Card, I can attack up to the number of that Monster's level!
Ryoga, this is your end!
Looks like the result is exactly as I suspected.
He just drew a Magic or Trap Card.
Im...impossible! Why?
Now IV's battle ends.
But I won't let it end like this!
I summon Gimmick Puppet Scissors Arm from my hand!
By destroying an Equip Card on my field, its level doubles!
I destroy Destiny Strings, the Equip Card equipped to Heaven's Strings!
Then Scissor Arm's level becomes eight!
Why?
Huh?
If he had that Monster in his hand,
rather than taking the risk of failure, and activating the effect of Destiny Strings,
he should have used Scissors Arm and Heaven's Strings to attack!
Don't tell me IV misplayed?!
I did suggest that you think calmly.
Perhaps it was me who lead him to this result?
Either way...
I release Gimmick Puppet Heaven's Strings!
And Special Summon this Monster!
I Special Summon Gimmick Puppet Nightmare!
When Nightmare is Special Summoned by releasing an Xyz Monster, it can be treated as 2 Xyz Materials!
I Overlay the Level Eight Scissors Arm and Nightmare, which splits into two!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Another new Number!
This is my true trump card!
Come forth, Number 88!
Gimmick Puppet Destiny Leo!
3200 Attack Points?!
Such a majestic appearance!
I activate Destiny Leo's effect!
When all of this guy's Overlay Units are detached, I will win this Duel!
Plus, once per turn, it can detach one Overlay Unit to the Graveyard.
He can win just by using up its Overlay Units?
Say what?!
That can't be possible!
This is the power of the invincible Number, Destiny Leo!
Destiny Leo still has one Overlay Unit left.
In the next turn, the second Destiny Leo uses its last Xyz Material,
Ryoga, you will lose!
No way! Shark can't lose like this!
With only that Monster in Face-Down Defense Position on Shark's field, he can't defeat a Number.
Moreover, its unnecessary for Destiny Leo to conduct battle anyway.
Because in this situation, he already...
I will lose to IV?
Lose to that IV, who framed me in the Championship, and even got my younger sister injured?
Am I going to lose like this, without getting my revenge?
It's too early to give up.
Tron!
You still have a way to win.
You are different from IV, because you can think calmly.
Tron! Why are you helping Ryoga?
You don't want me to win?!
It doesn't really matter if you win.
I told you, didn't I? All you have to do is fulfill your role.
And you've done superb so far! Pushing Ryoga this far!
Tron...
You can get a nice, long rest after this is over!
Your turn has long ended.
Tron, you...!
Whether it's V, III, or IV, they aren't just tools for your revenge!
So, Ryoga, did you manage to find the answer?
You bastard...!
It's okay if you lose.
But you won't be able to take revenge on us if you do.
I will get revenge, by any means necessary!
Very good. Now we're on the same page.
As expected from the strongest assassin I choose.
Stop kidding! I will not become something like-
Shark!
Th...This is...
It's the Number!
Shark Drake is looking for you.
Recall it.
You can do this... Ryoga.
Never!
I...definitely won't...
It's calling you...
Shark Drake...
... is calling you.
Never...
Defeat IV by combining your strength with Shark Drake!
Call it, Ryoga!
The only way for you to win is to call back Shark Drake, and integrate yourself with the Number!
Accept the Number, Ryoga.
Then everything will go as you desire!
Everything...
No! Stop, Shark!
Everything I... desire...
Defeat IV...
Defeat Tron...
Complete my revenge...
That's right.
Everything will come true.
Stop, Shark! Don't do it!
Ever since that day, since the day my sister was injured,
I have given my all to revenge.
If I can make it come true...
I won't even mind a demon taking over my body.
Shark! No! Don't go there!
I can't lose!
I have to win! And I need power to do it!
My turn! Draw!
I Flip Summon the Monster in Face-Down Defense Position on my field!
I switch Deep Sweeper to Attack Position!
Then I activate Deep Sweeper's Monster Effect!
By releasing this card, it destroys the Continuous Magic, Different Dimension Depths!
In this moment, the card's effect disappears!
Therefore, Shark Drake returns to the field!
Shark Drake is...
...revived?
That's why he set Deep Sweeper on the field!
Impossible!
This means he hasn't completely refused the allure of his Number.
Even if Shark Drake has returned, it only has 2800 Attack Points.
It can't defeat Destiny Leo with its 3200 Attack Points!
This is where I will acquire a new power!
What?
In order to complete my revenge, I am willing to accept everything!
Come, Shark Drake!
Accept my wish, and evolve!
Evolve?!
Don't tell me...
Me and Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake will...!
Chaos Xyz Change!!
Show yourself, Chaos Number 32!
Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake Vice!
Shark Drake became a Chaos Number...
Why is he able to trigger the power of Chaos Numbers?!
Good job, Ryoga. Very splendid.
Impossible! Why... Why is this guy...?
I activate Shark Drake Vice's Monster effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it Banishes one "Shark" named Monster from my Graveyard!
I Banish Aero Shark!
Then its 1900 Attack Power will be stolen from Destiny Leo!
What?!
Shark Drake Vice, attack Destiny Leo!
Depth Chaos Bite!!
Shark... won...
That was beautiful, Shark.
Tron!
Now you are my "friend" as well.
No! I obtained this new power in order to defeat you!
Duel with me!
Please save the best for last.
After all, the last Finalist haven't been decided yet!
Shut up!
Don't get impatient!
Shark!
Yuma Tsukumo.
I will see for myself just how useful your Bring It To 'em is.
Tron!
Ryoga...
I'm sorry for everything I've done up until now.
Cut the bullshit! Why say that now?!
I wasn't able to stop Tron.
So, on that day...
...under Tron's order, I Dueled with your sister,
and used the card he gave me.
What?!
I never intended to do something like that.
But I...
Tron...! Tron!
I ended up injuring your sister.
Then...
IV was trying to save Shark's sister all along!
I incriminated you, and I hurt your sister.
I'm responsible for everything.
Hold your grudge against me.
Just hate me alone.
But I beg you...
Please save Tron, my father!
Ryoga,
you'll definitely able to save my father!
IV!
And please tell him...
...that I'll be waiting for him, along with my brothers.
That we're waiting for you to return to your normal self.
IV!
Shark! Wait, Shark!
IV... No, not only IV,
V and III are all victims of Tron!
Therefore...
If what he said is all true, then I just have to beat Tron to a pulp with my own hands.
If you want to get in my way, Yuma, I will show you no mercy!
Shark...
Shark... Even you're trying to get revenge using Dueling...
But no one will become happy that way!
Dueling is... Dueling is...
Yuma...
Just walk on the path in which you believe.
If you are right, you are certain to open your own path.
I will! I'll do it! No matter what path it is, I'll open it!
I'll bring it to 'em!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Finally it's my turn to Duel!
My opponent is that Gauche.
The battle takes place on the Dangerous Canyon Field!
Yuma, why are you hesitating?
So the more they attack, the more their Life will be depleted?
Shut up! I have my own strategy!
You just can't win this Duel.
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"A Fierce Fight! Yuma VS Gauche:
This is My Manly Dueling Soul!"
Am I actually afraid to Duel?
An amazing card just appeared!
Number 88, Gimmick Puppet Destiny Leo!
When all its Overlay Units are gone, you win the game!
What would you do if you only had a little bit of time remaining?
Um, how should I say it...
Yes, that's all folks.