Let's win.
Wh-Who the heck are you?!
Just who are you?!
Astral.
A-Astral?
If I remember correctly....
Wh-What the heck is this guy saying?
What's wrong, Yuma?
Why are you talking to yourself over there?
You guys don't see this guy?
Heh?
C'mon, here! Right Here!
Is someone actually there?
He's right here!
Here! The strange looking guy! Standing next to me!
Do you think... the guy's lost his mind 'cause he's scared or something?
Look! It's here! IT'S HERE! HERE!
I am not afraid!
Am I the only one who can see this guy?
Did my D-Gazer malfunction or something?
It seems like you cannot comprehend my existence.
Don't tell me you're...
My name is Yuma Tsukumo.
A first-year middle school student aiming to become the Duel Champion and to bring it to 'em!
With the deck my Dad entrusted to me, I started Dueling.
However, my opponent is the former participant of the National-level tournament -- Shark!
In this urgent moment, the thing that appeared in front of me is...
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Don't tell me you're... a spirit!
- A spirit?
"Numbers 2:
My Name is Astral"
What effect does this "spirit" have?
When can we activate it?
Huh?!
What are you talking about?!
It seems I somehow lost some of my memories.
I guess when I came to this world,
there was some kind of impact while crossing through the Gate, which scattered them...
AM-NE-SI-A?
What's all this about your memory and the Gate?
I'm done for!
I must've snapped.
Why'd it have to happen during such an important Duel?
Calm yourself.
This is all your fault, you know!
Will Yuma be all right...?
He's complaining to himself over there...
It was just way too reckless to
challenge Shark to a fight like this...
Even you, Tetsuo-kun!
Why are you becoming so feeble all of sudden?!
Yours and Yuma's decks are both at stake in this Duel!!
There's no way he'll allow Shark to take them away...
Pull yourself together, Yuma!!
I am pulled together!
That aside, it looks like I'm the only one who can see this guy...
What's more...
Ever since Shark Summoned that Numbers card...
the atmosphere changed all of a sudden.
Numbers 17... Revice Dragon!
When this Exceeds Monster appears,
my body was overwhelmed with the endless power!
As I am for now, it feels like there's no way I can lose to anyone!
I will take away your Deck!
I set one card face-down on the field and end my turn!
Numbers...
There should be some of my important memories sealed within it...
My instinct is telling me I need to win this Duel.
"Duel"? You know how to Duel?
Indeed...
I am... a Duelist!
A Duelist's spirit?!
- A Duelist's spirit?
I am a Duelist!
It's... my turn!
It's my turn, darn it!
My turn! Draw!!
I will set Gogogo Golem in Defense Position!
Don't butt into my Duel!
I Summon Gogogo Golem in Attack Mode!
It's got 1800 Attack Power,
but it won't be enough to beat his Monster.
Of course I know that!
I activate the Magic Card, Unprecedented Wind, from my hand!
Unprecedented Wind lets me choose one Monster in Attack Mode and increase its Attack Power by 1000 points until my next turn!
Yuma, here's your chance!
Go! Gogogo Golem!
Attack Revice Dragon!!
I did it! With this, Revice Dragon is destroyed!
And I've reduced Shark's Life for the first time!
YAYY!!
Look closely!
Huh?
His Life was reduced...
So why wasn't it destroyed?!
When they're both in Attack Mode, the one with the higher Attack Power wins, right?!
Hold on a second! Revice Dragon should be destroyed!
Whoops. I guess I forgot to mention this.
Numbers can only be defeated by other Numbers!
No way... I don't have any of these "Numbers" things...
Numbers can only be defeated by Numbers? Then what's he supposed to do now?
Yuma: B-But, I can care less about Numbers!
Gogogo Golem's Attack Power is still higher than Revice Dragon
Next turn, Gogogo Golem will be destroyed.
If he has a Monster with 800 or higher Attack Power in his hand, we stand no chance of winning this Duel.
My Life's still at 1000, you know!
Observation #1: Your Dueling tactics are no where as good as mine.
Not as good as yous!?
Wh-What does "tactics" mean, by the way?
It means "strategy"...
Oh, strategy!
Strategy...
What'd you say?!
With this, the match is decided!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Drill Barnacle!
300 Attack Points...
We've been saved.
I mean it! What the heck are you talking about?!
I activate Revise Dragon's effect!
By removing one Overlay Unit, I can increase its Attack Power by 500!
3000 Attack Points... Are you serious?!
Revice Dragon did have one Overlay Unit remaining,
so it was almost certain that he would would use that effect to boost its Attack Points.
No Way!
Go, Revice Dragon!
Attack Gogogo Golem!
Now my Life's 800?!
This guy can foresee things that far ahead?
I still have an attack remaining!
Drill Barnacle, Drill Attack!!
D-Darn it!
Yuma...!
When in Defense Mode, Gogogo Golem has an effect that prevents it from being destroyed in battle.
If you had listened to my advice and set Gogogo Golem in Defense Position, we wouldn't be in this pinch.
Shut Up!
What is this? My life is fading as well...
Numbers....
Huh?
Astral: I remember now.
Numbers... are the pieces of my memory!
Numbers are special cards, even among the Exceeds.
The cards in this world are no match for them.
And when two Numbers Duel, the winner shall absorb loser's Numbers...
What does that mean?
If we fail to win this Duel, then I will disappear.... from this world...
I must win this Duel at all costs.
I planned to win from the beginning!
But I don't have any card
in my hand that can bring a reversal....
Next turn, as long as I can survive Revice Dragon's attack,
even with an attack from Drill Barnacle, I'll still have 200 Life remaining.
Thinking is a waste of time!
I activate the effect of Drill Barnacle!
When this card successfully inflicted battle damage to the opponent,
its Attack Power goes up by 1000 points!
Additionally, Drill Barnacle is a Monster that can attack the opponent directly, anyway.
Next turn, if its Direct Attack connects, it's all over for you!
Seriously?
If I'm hit with that thing, I'll lose!
What should I do... What should I do?
I set a Trap Card!
Let's see... What card did I set, anyway?
Bye-Bye Damage, huh?
If you activate the card, not only will you have inflicted damage to your opponent, but Gogogo Golem will not be destroyed.
I'd forgotten because you kept distracting me!
It's high time you forfeit this Duel already!
No way I'll give up!
Then, do you still think you have a chance to win?
I won't give up!
"I won't give up"?
That statement bothers me so much.
What should I do now...?
You still have a chance.
To do so, the necessary conditions are for you to assemble two Monsters on the field.
Listen carefully... mmm.
My Name's Yuma!
Then listen carefully...
Toma.
It's not "Toma"! It's Yuma!!
As for your next draw, draw a card which enables you to Special Summon a Monster.
A card that allows me to Special Summon?
You have to draw that card no matter what.
Ahh!! Shut Up!
Mine and Tetsuo's decks are on the line in this Duel!
My turn! Draw!
Resurrection of the Dead, huh?
It seems like fate has not abandoned me yet...
I'm the one who drew it!
I Summon Ganbara Knight in Attack Mode!
Yuma! Why are you playing it in Attack Mode?
Ganbara Knight's Attack Power is zero!
Ahhhh!!! Shoot!!!
It's my win now, so just give up already!
I don't plan to give up!
I'll just bring it to 'em like always!
"Bring it to 'em"?
"Bring it to 'em" means having the spirit to challenge and a heart that will never give up!
A person's heart dies the moment they give up!
You talk too much!
"I won't give up, I won't give up"...
Guys like you piss me off more than anyone!
Besides, how do you plan to stand up to my Monsters with your zero Attack Power Monster?
You've done enough.
Had you set him in Defense Position, you would have lost any chances you had for a turn around...
...Toma.
It's Yuma!
Use Resurreccion of the Dead to revive Gagaga Magician!
What?
I cannot allow myself to disappear from here...
Please believe me!
It's not like I trust you or anything like that....
I activate Resurreccion of the Dead from my hand!
I revive Gagaga Magician from the Graveyard!
What do you plan to do by
bringing back a 1500 Attack Power Monster?!
With this, all the conditions are met.
What?
Overlay your Level Four Gagaga Magician
and your Ganbara Knight.
This... couldn't be ...an Exceeds Summon?!
Take a look at your Extra Deck.
What is this Exceeds Monster?
I can't read its text...
I can read it.
Numbers 39... Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
This is... Numbers?!
Correct. That's the power I've entrusted to you.
I have to gamble on this now!
I'm gonna bring it to you!
I Overlay my Level Four Gagaga Magician and Ganbara Knight!
I construct the Overlay Network using these two Monsters!
Exceeds Summon!
Come forth! Numbers 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!!
Go! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Attack Drill Barnacle!
HOPE KING SLASH!!!
Awright! I dealt Shark critical damage!
That's a Numbers?
That is the only trump card which is capable of bring down Revice Dragon, Aspiring Emperor - Hope.
Numbers again?
Aspiring Emperor - Hope...?
Did Yuma even have that card to begin with?
He didn't... I think.
With this, I end my turn.
I just performed an Exceeds Summon for the first time in my life!
Hey,hey,hey,hey,hey!! Did you see that?
We saw it already.
Did ya' see that?
That's the fruit of my bringin' it to 'em!
What are you so hyper about?
Hope's Attack Power is only 2500.
If it's attacked by Revice Dragon with 3000 Attack Points, this thing's over.
Is that so? Shoot!
Even if you managed to Summon a Numbers,
you are still no match of me!
My turn! Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Surfacing!
This card can Special Summon a WATER-Attribute Monster from my Graveyard in Defense position!
Revive! Big Jaws!
Next, by releasing Big Jaws, I Advance Summon Jawsman!
Advanced Summon?!
It's a method of Summoning which lets you Summon High-Level Monsters by releasing a Monster.
This card gains 300 Attack Points for every Water-Attribute Monster I control on the field!
Revice Dragon is of the Water attribute!
Thus, the Attack Power of Jawsman is 2900!
Finish it!!
First, Revice Dragon will attack Hope!
Doesn't Hope have any effect at all?!
Hope's effect... By removing one Overlay Unit, it can negate an attack.
You shoulda told me right away!
I activate Hope's effect!
By removing one Overlay Unit, Revice Dragon's attack is negated!
RUNE BARRIER!!
Is that Hope's effect?
But even if my attack is negated, you still can't defeat my Monsters and win!
Defeating his Monsters...
You only have one Overlay Unit left to use!
Although Numbers can't be destroyed unless by other Numbers,
you still receive damage!
To avoid that damage, Feel free to use that remaining Overlay Unit!
Go, Jawsman! Attack Hope!
Do exactly as he says! Use Hope's effect once again!
A way to defeat his Monsters...
Alright! I activate the Bye-Bye Damage Trap Card!
Thanks to Bye Bye Damage, my Monster is not destroyed and is protected from battle!
Why are you not using Hope's effect?!
'Cuz I am who I am!
At same time, when the player receives Battle Damage, the opponent receives twice of the damage I took!
Now Yuma only has 100 Life left.
Because you just activated a Trap,
I can activate the Permanent Trap, Urchin Bomb!
When my turn comes, I can inflict 1000 points of damage to you with this Trap!
Now, my victory is as good as decided!
It's over. Yuma lost...
That can't be! Yuma!
It's about time for you to give up!
Not yet! I won't give up!!
There is only one turn left for you!
Why are you still not giving up the Duel?!
Let me ask you!
Why do you want me to give up so badly?!
Going by that attitude of yours, haven't you also given up something important to you?!
Haven't you abandoned something that was precious to you?!
I for one never give up and continue to bring it to 'em!
I'll show you what I mean!
So you still have a way to turn this around?
I do!
I have a combo in my deck that can beat him.
Grandma...
Take it!
W-Wait, Yuma, what are you doing?
This is my victory meal!
My Duel meal!
I've fully recharged!
My turn!
That's it! There's only one thing to do to beat that thing!
I'm gonna bring it to you!!
Draw!!
Here it is!
Go! Hope! Attack Revice Dragon!
I don't believe it!
Why?!
Why would he attack with Hope, who has lower Attack Points?!
I then activate Hope's effect!
By removing one Overlay Unit, I negate Hope's attack!
What's the point in a combo that doesn't deal me any damage?!
Oh, there's a meaning to it, all right!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic Card! Double-Up Chance!
A Quick-Play Magic?!
When my Monster's attack is negated, this card doubles that Monster's Attack Power and allows it to attack once again!
5000 Attack Points?!
Bring it to 'em, Hope!
Attack Revice Dragon!
Did I... win?
Yuma....
...won.
I won! I defeated Shark!
I brought it to 'em!!
To think you'd lose to someone like him...
- We're outta here, Shark!
So this is the Numbers 17 card...
A piece of my memories...
Does this mean... If I manage to collect all 99 scattered Numbers cards, I can recover my memory?
You did it! You are the best! Yuma!
To think I would... lose...
Dad,Mom, I won.
Shark...
As we promised.
So you really did return Tetsuo's deck....
Yuma Tsukumo, I will remember this.
Shark! I had a ton of fun!
Let's Duel again some time!
But we won't bet our decks next time.
Let's bring it to 'em together!
You bet on the draw of a single card,
and bet everything on it, huh...?
Huh? Did you suddenly have a little change in attitude?
Well, it's cool.
What'd ya think?!
Generally speaking, you are a Duelist whom goes beyond my understanding...
...Toma.
It's not Toma, it's Yuma!!
Let's start the Duel!
Here's our question this week!
These are the two important stats for a Monster.
"ATK" stands for "Attack Points". So what do these stand for?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
A computer virus spreads through the entire city all of a sudden!
Who could be behind this and for what purpose?
I'll catch the culprit myself!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"A Sudden Incident During the Aftermath!!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!