Now then, it's time for the finishing touches.
The finishing touches for the destruction of the Astral World!
Finishing touches?
What do you mean by "destruction of the Astral World"?!
Simply this.
You two will be the shells that will destroy the Astral World.
Shot by the Sphere Field Cannon!
Shell? Sphere Field Cannon?
Yuma, look down.
Huh?
This is... The waste disposal plant from the other day!
Right now, you will be sent to the muzzle of the Sphere Field Cannon,
and it is aiming for the Astral World!
- What?!
Then, this is... the memory from my world, when...
The attack level will be much different than before.
Because within the Sphere Field, the power of all the Numbers will be concentrated into one shell.
One strike with this blast and the Astral World will be...
Haruto!
Where is Haruto?
Orbital! Search for Haruto's whereabouts! Immediately!
U-Understood!
For that... For that, you had...
...Kaito collect Numbers?!
The World Duel Carnival has been organized to collect the Numbers.
It was a bit of a pity that Kaito has been defeated by Byron,
but that could have been expected.
In short... with you collecting all the Numbers in the Final,
my goal has been accomplished.
That means, me and Tron, Shark, Kaito, plus III and his brothers...
...all the participants have been nothing but your tools?!
You jerk...! Stop screwing with us!
What?!
It will happen any minute now.
Well, Haruto! This will be your last mission.
Haruto...
Are you absolutely positive?
Yes!
Haruto-sama is underneath the tower, at the underground disposal site.
Haruto should be safe there.
He might be safe there, just... in the place Haruto-sama is right now,
Haruto-sama himself will become a part of the Sphere Field Canon and...
What did you say?!
Haruto! Haruto!
Hey, Haruto! Haruto!
Well, Haruto, you can trigger it all by yourself,
and destroy the Astral World!
Haruto is the trigger?
I understand now! The energy of the Numbers will be the shell,
which will be fired by Haruto's power!
Soon it will be accomplished.
Then the Astral World will be destroyed an I will receive the power of Varian,
to rule the world as I desire!
Haruto!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Everyone all right?
Hey, where is Kotori?
"Number 68: The Overture Towards Destruction!
The Threat of Sphere Field Cannon!"
I don't see her anywhere!
Perhaps she ran off to Yuma!
Akari-san!
Is everyone okay?
Yuma disappeared along with the field...
And Kotori too...
What did you say?!
No way!
Yuma!
Thi... this is...?!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes, given to me by Haruto's power...
Are you suffering, Haruto...?
Kaito-sama!
Very good. that's a good boy, Haruto.
The ruin of the Astral World is approaching.
The moment I reach my goal is coming closer!
Kotori-chan? You hear me, Kotori-chan?
Answer me... Kotori-chan!
Kotori-chan?!
Akari-san?
Kotori-chan... Thank goodness.
Are you somewhere safe?
Right now, I am beneath the Heart Tower.
The Heart Tower? Why there?
Yuma must be around here!
Kaito-sama!
Kaito-sama! Kaito-sama!
That's... Kaito!
Akari-san, excuse me. I have to hang up.
Huh? Wait, Kotori-chan! Kotori-chan!
Kotori-chan...
Yuma... where... where are you?
Oh... this is...
Use more power!
U-Understood!
Just a bit and we've got it.
Out of the way!
Shark!
Aren't you that guy from the other day...!
I'll lift the rubble up.
Use that chance to pull him out.
Hurry it up!
Ye... yes!
Kaito-sama!
Thank you, Shark.
No need for thanks.
Take that guy and get away!
I can't get away...
Kaito-sama!
While we are talking, Haruto will...
What about Haruto-kun?
What is happening with Haruto-kun?
That... it is...
Orbital!
Hey, answer me!
Answer! What is happening with Haruto-kun?!
That... He is a part of the Sphere Field Cannon.
Sphere Field Cannon?!
That's the ultimate weapon to destroy the Astral World.
Dr. Faker made Kaito-sama collect
the Numbers to fill it with energy and-
Where is he now?
Where will the Sphere Field Cannon launch?
Where?!
There's no time. Let's go, Orbital.
Wait! We aren't finished yet!
Upset that I didn't say thank you?
Unfortunately... I don't know words like 'thank you'.
So there's no use expecting it from me.
That's not what I mean!
Or do you want a Duel?
Save it for later, then.
Though, I was positive we already settled the score.
You...
Shut up! Next time I'll beat you, just you see!
What are you two doing?!
Now's not the time for this!
You shut up too!
I don't want any thanks, or a Duel with this guy!
I want...
I just want to help Yuma!
He's probably still inside the Sphere Field.
And if it is a weapon...
No way!
I can't leave Yuma like that!
He's the guy who beat Tron in my place!
Answer, you stupid robot!
Where will the Sphere Field Cannon launch?!
I am not a stupid robot! If you keep on saying that, I won't say a thing!
Please. I would like to help Yuma as well.
And Haruto-kun, of course! And Yuma too always worried about Haruto-kun.
Even you understand that, don't you?
But I promised Haruto!
....who else is gonna protect Haruto!?
I'll protect Haruto, so focus on the Duel for now!
So that's why I'm begging you both to work together to save them both?!
Let's go, Orbital.
Understood!
Kaito!
If you want to help, come along.
Haruto and Yuma should be at the underground waste disposal sight.
Waste disposal sight?
Over there?
My body is... getting so heavy.
No use... I can't stand up anymore.
It's all my fault. My power is getting weaker and weaker.
Astral!
Yuma...
At the very least, I want to get you out of here.
Don't be silly... I can't leave you alone in here.
Me and you... and Haruto... We'll be saved together.
I won't give up until the very end!
I'll bring it to...
Useless. The underground passage is blocked off!
Isn't there another way?
Check it, Orbital.
Understood!
Although I have to say, from here I won't be able to...
...access the host computer to identify the points which-
You can't do that?! You stupid robot!
How about you helping, you long haired punk!
I know! Perhaps Akari-san!
Yes, I got it. Listen, Kotori-chan.
From where you are, on the third block to the left, are stairs.
These will lead you to the underground!
As expected, Akari-san! Thank you so much! You were a huge help!
But don't push yourselves too hard!
Be careful, Kotori!
To summarize, we can only rely on...
... Kotori now. I'm leaving Yuma to you!
We need to stick together!
Everyone, over there!
I just know it. I have to save them, for the sake of everyone.
Therefore, stay safe, Yuma!
There's Haruto-sama in front!
I was expecting you, Kaito.
Perhaps the painful screams of your little brother were resonating in your ears?
You bastard...
Haruto...
Haruto, Haruto!
Yuma... Yuma is there too!
Whoever dares to stand in Dr. Faker's way will not be forgiven!
Go, crush them!
Crush these annoying people!
. . . Cleaning . . . Cleaning . . . Cleaning . . . Cleaning . . . Cleaning . . . Cleaning . . .
Fight them back, Orbital!
Understood!
I'm coming!
Excuse me!
Beg your pardon!
Oh, that was a good one!
Stop admiring me and try harder yourself!
U-Understood...
. . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . .
Damn, there's even more of them coming!
If this goes on, then Haruto...
Don't you worry. Haruto will complete his mission very well.
What?!
Because it is his desire to help Dr. Faker, his father.
Stop joking!
I am not only not joking, but very happy indeed.
Dr. Faker's dream will become a reality very soon.
And his dream is connected to mine.
That is why I bet everything on Dr. Faker-sama.
And that is why I won't let anyone cause any trouble for him.
You all can right out disappear together with Yuma Tsukumo!
So, I'll open the gates to hell now!
What... is this?!
The space underneath is connected to the Astral World.
This will be an eternal farewell to you all!
This guy wants to dispose of us like trash!
If we fall into that hole...
Haruto...
Any moment, Haruto will turn into the trigger of the Sphere Field Cannon.
With this, my expectations as a father,
and my desires will be achieved!
Go! Beat them into that pit!
. . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . . Trash . . .
They keep coming out...
Hey, you stupid robot, don't you have any ideas to counter them?
Who is calling me a stupid robot?! You nasty shark!
It's not the time for quarreling!
These Obots move on orders from somewhere.
If we find that location, we can destroy it.
Oh! Why haven't I thought of that?!
I'll investigate immediately.
All orders are transmitted by the main computer,
If I hijack that and inject a high voltage shock...
Got it! Over there!
I don't need the explanation! Get going!
Stop ordering me around! I am not your servant!
Do it, Orbital!
U-Understood!
Orbital Step!
I'll bring my service to 'em!
And this is solely my turn!
I overcharge the main computer with a high voltage shock!
Wha... what's happening?
What?!
Orbital!
They stopped moving!
Im... impossible?!
Haruto's energy is decreasing?!
Oh?! Wha... what is happening!?
Wa... Wait!
Someone! Can someone save me, anyone! Please...!
Orbital!
Well done, Orbital!
Kaito-sama praised me... I wished for that my whole life...
Orbital... Thank you.
What... what has happened?
Over there...!
Kotori! Shark! Kaito! You here...?!
The energy of the Sphere Field Cannon is decreasing.
Maybe it will work now...
Yuma, deactivate ZEXAL!
Astral!
Astral...
Go, Yuma.
Huh?
Only you can escape now.
What are you saying? You have to escape as well!
I can't do that.
Right now, I only can exist inside the Sphere Field,
because I am the embodiment of the Numbers.
Tha... That is...
These are...
Hope.
And the future.
Astral... You...?!
You have to go now, Yuma.
Go save the Astral World and help Haruto.
The future is entrusted to you.
Yuma!
That... hurts...
You don't stop causing me trouble!
But whatever you try, it will be useless!
Soon you will be eliminated, together with the Astral World!
With this Sphere Field Cannon!
Dr. Faker!
Oh!
I see! That's what you meant! I got it, Astral!
Shark, Kaito! Lend me your power, please!
Please protect the hope and the future that Astral has entrusted on me.
Hope and Future...?!
So you entrusted them to me as well...
...hope and the future.
Our hearts are resolved!
The future of everyone is at stake!
We challenge you to a Duel, Dr. Faker!
Interesting.
Until the auto restoration of the main computer is completed, I will accept for entertainment purposes.
Also, the Numbers have to be collected again.
Very well, I will be your opponent.
Yuma... Kaito... Shark...
The hope of everyone is depending on you three and you three alone.
Please protect it,
the future!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The last Duel against Dr. Faker has finally started!
And his Number finally makes an appearance!
How can we loose this?!
Shark, Kaito, let us unite our powers!
What kind of form is this?
It's truly the strongest Number!
Let's go! Let's show him the power of our bonds!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Three Heroes Unite! One Last Duel For The Future!"
The destiny of the worlds now is entrusted to you...
Dr. Faker, this is our final battle!
Kaito, Shark, you came too?!
Just be sure not to hold me back!
No matter how you look at it, you're the one holding them back, Yuma.
I knew you'd say that.