Let's Duel~
Darn right, Kotori~
It's really been bugging me.
I mean, this is Yuma we're talking about, the guy who never beat me once!
But when you look at his recent record, he's been winning one Duel after the next!
Huh? And what exactly is so wrong about that?
His "bringin' it to 'em" fits him best when he's a loser!
Eh... Did you really have to call him a loser?
Gotta wonder if this "Astral" guy really exists...
Sup!
Ah, good morning, Yu...
...ma?
What's with the long faces?
I can't take it anymore!
Listen, Yuma...
I don't really wanna talk about a person's fashion sense...
But yesterday...!
Good morning!
The day before that...!
And the day before that, even...!
Good morning!
Everyone's just gonna laugh when you dress like that!
Th-The heck do you mean?
Gosh!
Take a look at yourself!
T-The hell is this!?
Wait... You really had no clue?
I-I had no idea!
What is up with this getup?!
And it's not just this, either!
You've been acting really weird for days now!
Having a bentou you didn't even know about!
And the fancy food that made no sense whatsoever!
And there's that 100 you scored on that test!
And then, yesterday...
Here goes!
Gonna bring it to 'em!
What the heck's he up to?!
Wh-What the heck?
Someone stop me!
You're right! That put me through a ton of crap!
Who the heck did that?
She's always been watching you.
Say wha?
Yesterday was no exception.
She entered your room late at night and was up to something.
If you knew the entire time, why the heck didn't you tell me?!
I didn't feel the need to say anything.
I also hang out in your room.
So I assumed other people coming into your room was natural.
"Natural", you think?!
Darn! In that case...
I swear to find the culprit!
What a thing to say while dressed like that...
I didn't choose to wear this!
I wonder!
You have no fashion sense at all, Yuma.
The heck's that supposed to mean?
Well then, what would you have me wear?
Oh, I assure you I'm much better than you!
Then let's see some proof!
Sure thing! It'd be a pleasure!
How about I pick out clothes for you this Sunday?
How amusing~!
Let's meet at the shopping mall at 3 O'Clock sharp!
Got it?
Sure!
Don't you dare be late!
Of course not!
Thank you... You guys are the only ones who concern yourselves with me...
This is the girl!
This is the girl trying to steal away the person I care about...
The cat burglar... Kotori Mizuchi.
Remember her face well, all of you.
That's right! She's your prey!
You cats can go ahead and gobble that Kotori right up!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
"Numbers 9:
Cat Surprise - Cat Deck!?"
Ah, GEEZ! I told him not to be late and I ended up late myself!
Shoot, I'm really late!
What is this?!
Ah, c'mon...
She's so slow!
What the heck's Kotori doing?
Wh-What in the world are these?!
Something about their arched backs and four legs strikes me as bizarre!
Huh? Could it be that you're not good with cats?
It's only because I haven't made note of them in my daily observations!
Welly then, let me inform you...
Cats are really sensitive to spiritual activity!
They can probably see you clearly!
No, Yuma... They appear to be looking right at you.
Huh?
Huh? That ribbon...
It's Kotori's...
What?!
Kotori's been kidnapped?!
Damn it!
Kotori...
Kotori!
What is this place?!
Cat, cat, cat...
Thank you for coming.
Who the heck are you?!
I am Cathy.
Cathy?!
Yes.
But you can call me Cat-chan!
Wh-what's with her?!
I know her.
No matter how far away you are from her, she's always watching you.
Ahh...!
Now that you mention it...
Now that I mention it...?
I got no clue.
It's fine.
I'm used to it, after all...
That aside, where's Kotori?!
Why did you do this?!
You can't go...!
That's why I...!
Huh?! Whatever! Just give Kotori back!
If you're that worried about her, I'll give her back.
If you defeat me in a Duel.
A-A Duel?!
But if I win...
Damn her...! Could it be the Numbers?!
If that's the case, you must win this Duel.
You don't need to tell me. I'll win!
Let's Duel!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Since cats always dash forward!
So I'll be taking the first turn!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Inviting the Cat, from my hand!
A Magic Card right from the start?!
Using the effect of this card, I can add a Stray Cat into my hand.
And then, the Continuous Magic from my hand!
A Rally of Cats activates!
A Continuous Magic?!
Now, given the circumstances are handled properly, she can use the magic over and over again.
And I then Summon Stray Cat-chan in Attack Mode!
And now, the effect of A Rally of Cats will activate!
When my Stray Cat-chan is Summoned,
I can Summon another Stray Cat-chan using A Rally of Cats!
What's the point?
Summon all the 100 Attack Power Monsters you want! It's nothing to write home about!
Don't be so sure!
I set one card.
Turn end!
Feel free to attack as you please.
Kotori... I'll definitely save you!
Okay! It's my turn!
Draw!
I Summon Achacha Archer!
When I successfully Summon Achacha Archer,
the opposing player takes 500 points of damage!
How dare you pierce me heart~
I don't get a damn thing you're saying!
I'm going on the attack!
Wait, Yuma!
Her aim is-
Stuff it!
Wh-Why are you hesitating?!
Attack the Stray Cat over there!
No, that one!
Or... maybe that one?
AH, which one?!
Who cares which cat, just attack me!
I bet you'd like that!
You sure are mean.
When a Stray Cat-chan is face-up on my field in Attack Mode,
you can't attack either of my Stray Cats!
Meaning... Erm...
It would appear you are in quite the predicament.
Huh?
There are two Monsters, both being a Stray Cat.
Choose one and get the other's effect.
The very fact that your only option is to attack a Stray Cat...
...the end result is that you can't attack either.
Wh-What gives?!
Kotori...
Darn it, what should I do?
Yuma, there is only one way to get out of this…
You are so annoying!
Didn’t I tell to shut up already?!
I will use my own strength, to save Kotori!!
Kotori…just wait for me!
You are Dueling with me...!
Ok! Looks like I already got it!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand, FLIP FLOP!
This card can change the Battle Position of one Monster on the field!
I will switch the Stray Cat from my life side to Defense Position!
Go! Achacha Archer, attack the Stray Cat on the right side!!
The kitty!!
Right, as long as one of the Stray Cats switch to Defense Position, the effect of Stray Cat will disappear,
and the other Stray Cat in Attack Position can be attacked as well.
I can’t believe he just thought of this strategy... He's definitely different from the usual Yuma.
I will definitely save you, Kotori!!
How… how come it’s not me in front of you?
You only pay attention to that girl!
Don’t let me leave your sight…
You have to always look at ME!!
Wha…what the?!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic Card during my opponent’s Battle Phase, Monstrous Cat Transformation!!
This card activates when Stray Cat is destroyed by battle,
and I can Special Summon one Monster Cat from my hand, deck or Graveyard!!
M-Monster Cat?!
When a Monster Cat shows up, all LV 4 or lower Monsters on your side of field are destroyed!
And for every Monster destroyed by this effect, you take 800 points of damage!
How come you haven't noticed this passionate feeling?
Darn! I set one card face-down, and end my turn!
My turn, draw!!
I activate the effect of Monster Cat!!
Once per turn, I can add one Stray Cat from deck or Graveyard to my hand!
Then I Summon the Stray Cat added from my deck!
There are three LV1 Monsters on her field!!
So the Numbers are going to appear...
Just bring it on!
I Overlay my two Level One Stray Cats and Monster Cat!
I construct the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth! Twin-Tail Cat Lady!!
How come she didn’t summon a Numbers?!
I activate the effect of Twin-Tail Cat Lady!!
Once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit, she gains 800 ATK!!
Wa…wait a second! There are still two Overlay Units left... if she used them all...
Let's see...
There will be an increase of 1600, up to 3400 ATK.
3400?!!
Sorry, just stay with me for a while...
Don’t tell me…she is going to…
Awesome! Good job!
Then… cat!
...you have to always gaze at me!
Field Magic reflects the world!
I will change the battle stage!
The world I created, Cat World, Activate!!
Th-The heck is this?!
This is the paradise for cats, a world that contains only me, my cats and you!
And in Cat World, the ATK of these little kitties will increase up to its original ATK!
Sh-She's got 2800 Attack Points!?
Yuma is finally looking at me!
Now, my Twin-Tail Cat Lady, time to capture Yuma’s heart!
Direct Attack!
Darn it!
Trap Card, open! Fairy Gong!
This card can only be activated when I received a direct attack!
I can Special Summon one Monster with “Fairy” in its card name from my deck, in Attack Position!
Come! Fairy Joe!
So be it. I'll end my turn with that.
Sharp, very sharp!! You are so strong!
R…Really?!
Sure!
But…
But….only within this world of Dueling…
I can’t do it… in the reality…
I can’t say anything in front of that person! He didn’t notice me either…
Wow... That guy sounds like a jerk.
Despite the fact that I kept using magic on him, it still doesn’t work.
Not even a single glare…
So at least… I can connect with the person I love in Dueling…
Just say it!
Those things… just express them clearly… Don’t give up!
No matter how many times it takes, bring it to 'em all the way!
Cat...!
I'm gonna cat it to 'em!
I will confess! Actually….I always….
My turn, draw!
I activate the effect of Fallen Cone!
When I discard Growing Pinecone from my hand, I can Special Summon Fallen Cone!
Then the effect of Growing Pinecone in the Graveyard activates!
When this card is send to Graveyard from my hand, I can Special Summon it!
H-Hold on...!
Alright! I will use three Monsters to conduct a Xyz Summon as well!
I Overlay my Level One Fairy Joe, Fallen Cone and Growing Pinecone!
I construct the Overlay Network with the three!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Baby Tragon!
Then I Summon Gagaga Magician in Attack Mode!
I activate the effect of Gagaga Magician!
Until the end phase, his level can be changed! I will change Gagaga Magician’s Level to one!
Then I activate the effect of Baby Tragon!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, one LV 1 Monster I control can attack directly!
Hey…I didn’t finish what I am saying… yet!!
Gagaga Magician, Direct Attack!
GAGAGA MAGIC!!
C-C-CAT!!
I'm fired up! Go on!
I attack Twin-Tail Cat Lady with Baby Tragon!
Yuma, it doesn’t have enough ATK!
I know that, no need to worry!
I activate Quick-Play Magic from my hand, Giant Shadow of Egotism!
This card can increase one Monster’s ATK by 1000 during battle, and I choose Baby Tragon!
I… Yuma… I always…
Then, thanks to the effect of Giant Shadow of Egotism,
the Monster that battles with Baby Tragon will have its ATK switch to the original value!
Yuma, I've always lo-
I'm gonna bring it to ya!!
Go, Baby Tragon!
Baby Scream!!
Cat…!
Meo-why~!!!?
Awesome, I win!
So she doesn’t have a Numbers after all….
Hey…
Are you OK? Please tell me where Kotori is….
Cat…
The little kitties got tripped up!
So cute!!
K-Kotori!
Yuma!
Wh-What on Earth are you doing?!
I already told ya that I was forced to play with kitties, so it couldn't be helped.
Gosh, how long are you gonna be mad for?
I'm not mad at all!!
See... you are!
Um...
Ehhh… Morning…!
Mornin'!
Ehh… who is that?
How rude! She's our classmate… uhh...
Kathy the Cat-chan! She's so good at Dueling!
Ahhh... I don't know her.
Now that you mention it, do you know the culprit who embarrassed you with those pranks?
Ahh… I don’t know it at all!!
Then I'm off.
Hey, Kotori…
Observation # 11: "It seems Yuma still doesn’t understand the thoughts of females…"
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
The types of cards you can activate from you hand... Are they Magic Cards or Trap Cards?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
You're… Shark!
Looks like he's ganged up with some scary people!
Let’s go home, Yuma!
Why… Why would you give up Dueling?!
So are you gonna Duel with that boy again?
Shark, you don't belong with these people!
Without using the Numbers in this duel, I will definitely defeat you!
I will bring you back to the normal world!!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Shark’s Counterattack!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
And the answer...!
Magic Cards!
Magic Cards can be used from your hand.
They're quite convenient cards!
You better remember that!