Well then, here's to our beloved Yuma...
...passing the W.D.C...
...right into the Tournament Finals!
To summarize, he won the Semi-Finals and advanced!
Congratulations...
Cheers!
Phew, thanks a bunch!
Yuma's incredible!
I can't believe he made it through the Semi-Finals!
C'mon, Kotori... Cheer up.
Oh my, are you still angry?
After being left behind by Yuma on the Canyon Field...
What gives?!
Cat!
I said I was sorry! I was so engrossed in the Duel...
Engrossed by butt!
You suck. Don't fuss.
Kiddies, the snacks are ready.
G-Grandma...
Wow, looks great!
It looks yummy!
Eat as much as you like.
I'm starved!
Hey!
Grandma?
You must express your gratitude before you begin.
You must pay your respects to the Duels!
So be sure to show your gratitude.
Thanks for the food!
But you know, Yuma... there's bound to be a bunch of formidable opponents left.
Shark, and Kaito, and Tron.
I don't care who it is! Bring 'em on!
Cat it to 'em, Yuma!
Goodness... You barely won as it is.
I'll handle it, Kotori!
It's true that we must not rush in
unprepared against those remaining.
Tron's Number is aided by the power of his Crest...
Kaito has his incredibly powerful Neo Galaxy Eyes.
And Shark...
What was with that Chaos Number?
Why does he have a Chaos Number?
I'm definitely gonna win the Duel Carnival!
Yeah! As long as I got this deck a' mine with me...
And who exactly is Dr. Faker...?
It's gone~!
It's gone! Gone! Gone! My deck's gone!
I lost my deck~!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Gosh... I seriously can't believe this!
"Number 60: The Overture Towards the Final Battle:
The New Foe Dr. Faker!"
You actually lost your important deck...
It can't be helped.
It's already lost, after all...
So is it really here?
Yes! There's a GPS feature attached to our deck cases
that operates together with our D-Pads.
Which means Yuma-kun's deck case is...
...here in Heartland!
Excuse me! Is there anyone here?
Please open the door!
It'll only take a second, so please do this for me!
Hey, please open it!
Open it!
Open it! Open up already! Open up!!
Guess they won't open it no matter what.
Then we just gotta climb over and pass through!
That's obviously not possible!
If I just think of it as the 30 step jumping blocks...!
I'm gonna bring it...
...to 'em!
Darn~!
I did it!
It really is impossible to sneak in.
Gosh... You really are an idiot.
There's trucks entering over there.
Yeah, that's the place where the trash collected by the O-Bots from the trash bins are returned.
I just had a light bulb! It's the hidden side of this joint!
Eh?! We're gonna hide inside these trash bins?!
That's correct.
When they go to return the trash the O-Bots take from the trash bins,
we can sneak inside Heartland!
That sounds like it could work!
So, I'll...
Eh?
Yuma-kun, I'm preying for your success!
H-Hey! That rascal...
Okay! Let's get this done with!
Hey, hold it!
Huh? He really got inside there!
Gosh, it can't be helped.
Help me out, Tetsuo-kun.
Huh? You don't really expect me to go in there?
But I'm worried about Yuma going alone.
C'mon...
Just cat a moment!
There's only one more trash bin!
I won't let Kotori take it from me!
Eh? I don't really want to go inside a trash bin that badly...
It's really sly of you to try to go together with Yuma, cat.
And I don't really think you'd be of any use, Kotori.
*Clank~*
Um, in that case, Cat-chan can go in my place.
Fine then! We'll decide this with rock, paper, scissors!
That's exactly what I wanted!
Eh?!
Rock, paper, scissors! Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
Is this how humans show affection for one another?
Or is it simply their fighting spirit?
Oh yeah! I won!
I get to go in the trash bi-
Will you guys hurry it up already?!
- Right...
Cleaning! Cleaning! Cleaning! Cleaning!
H-Hold on!
Trash rejected. Trash rejected.
Huh? Why? Hang on a minute!
I'm trash enough for this! Wait up!
Look, everything went as I said it would, didn't it?
The plan is proceeding well.
Tomorrow, all the Numbers will belong to me.
But I have to make them pay for rendering III, IV, and V as sacrifices.
It's a pity, but it was unavoidable.
But they've done well.
I expected no less from my sons.
It seems he's come.
IV... You...
But I beg you...
Please save Tron, my father!
Ryoga,
you'll definitely able to save my father!
Tron...!
You're the one who incriminated me and injured my sister!
You're responsible for everything!
I won't let you get away with it at any cost!
Tron!
I've been waiting, Ryoga.
Where are you, Tron?! Where did you go?!
I caught you.
Now you belong to me...
You probably believe that you overcame your darkness in that Duel before,
but it was all as I planned.
IV worked diligently for this, after all.
Now I'll spread it...
The darkness in your heart.
I'll make it into a darkness that far exceeds what it was!
That's...
Yuma Tsukumo...
Gosh! Treating a lady like trash...!
But now we were able to get in!
Oh crap! We're gonna fall!
We're falling! Save us!
Yuma!
Huh? I-It stopped...
Huh? That's...
Phew... We're saved.
What is this place?
Huh? Is this all trash?
Amazing...
Why's there such a huge garbage disposal underneath Heartland?
What was that vision just now...?
There's something happening here...
Yuma.
Huh?
Haruto is above us.
Haruto is?!
No one's here.
Are you really going in here?
Yeah, so let's go.
Haruto... Haruto!
Where are we?!
There's an elevator over there!
Maybe he really is above us!
Alright, let's go!
Huh?
What the?
Intruder detected. Intruder detected.
Intruders will be eliminated through a Duel.
Wh-What'll we do?!
If it wants to Duel, we're just gonna have to do it!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
S-Something just appeared!
What is it?
Look!
A bunch of cards just appeared!
They're all Xyz Monster Cards?
I Summon Scrap Recycler.
A Monster appeared!
Oh! I see!
All the cards here are Xyz Monsters!
Hey, Kotori, jump on the 3 panel in front of you!
This?
Okay! I Xyz Summon with the two Level Threes!
Come forth, Wind-up Zenmaines!
An Xyz Monster!
He did it!
Go! Wind-up Zenmaines!
Attack Recycler!
Alright!
I Summon Scrap Searcher!
Another one came out.
Yuma, leave this to us and go on ahead!
Huh?!
Just get going already!
Tetsuo...
You want to meet Haruto-kun, don't you, Yuma?!
Okay. I'm counting on you!
Yuma!
Hey, this way, useless robot!
We're your opponents here!
Kotori, press two Level Ones!
Two ones... One... One... Here!
I use three Level Ones to conduct an Xyz Summon! Come forth, Mira the Giant Star!
Go! Attack Searcher!
Finally found it!
I Summon Scrap Hunter.
Kotori, press Level Two!
Okay!
Come forth, Shining Elf!
I'm counting on you guys! Tetsuo! Kotori!
I reached it!
Oh crap!
Just how many does it have?!
Th-This is Haruto's...
Haruto...
It seems like Haruto still hasn't regained consciousness from that time.
You know, Haruto...
I'm gonna win the Duel Carnival.
I will definitely beat that Tron down, and return as the champion.
I won't hold back against even your brother, Kaito, when the time comes.
So...
So please...
Haruto...
I...
If I hadn't let Tron and the others take you that night...
Yuma... Yuma.
Where are we?
Yuma. Astral.
I always believed that you guys would come here eventually.
Haruto! Haruto, you...
I have a favor to ask of you.
Please save my brother.
Huh?
My brother is already pretty tired.
But I don't have the power to save my brother.
And I cannot get out of here.
Please, save my brother.
Hey, Haruto!
That was...
Haruto's consciousness.
Haruto's consciousness?
Most likely,
Haruto’s true consciousness was sealed deep inside his heart.
If we are able to release his true consciousness,
maybe Haruto can recover from this.
Then how should we do that?
I am not sure either. But maybe it has something to do with Kaito collecting Numbers.
Eh?!
Then...
Haruto...
If I start collecting Numbers, Haruto may never get cured!
But if Kaito collects them…
What the heck should I do?!
You are the one who’s battling.
Thus you should make that decision.
But if I lose, you'll disappear!
Yuma...
While I Dueled alongside you, I have learned a lot from you.
I started to think that I was glad I partnered with you.
I will follow the path you choose.
No matter what kind of path it is.
Astral... you...
Why'd you have to say something like that?!
You should shout and cry more than that!
Just say, “Help me get back my memory! I don’t want to disappear like this!”
That would help me harden my heart for the upcoming battles.
And yet, why...? Why?!
Yuma...
My name is Dr. Faker.
Dr. Faker?!
Then you're Kaito and Haruto's dad?!
Welcome, Kazuma Tsukumo's son, and the Original Number.
He... knows about Astral!
So you can see me, then.
Dr. Faker.
Why are you collecting the Numbers?!
Aren't the Numbers my memories?!
Hmph. I made a deal with the Varian World.
Varian World...?
Yes. Another different world that coexists with the Astral World.
As long as I destroy the Astral World,
I can obtain the strongest power.
and become the ruler of this world!
Cut the crap! For that reason,
you forced Kaito to hunt the Numbers?!
Don’t you know how much Haruto and Kaito are suffering because of that?
Aren't the both of them your own children?!
They are just some minor sacrifices.
What!?
In order to obtain the strongest power, sacrifices are unavoidable.
Kaito, Haruto, and you, Yuma Tsukumo.
As well as your father, Kazuma.
People always need to strive to survive while giving up something.
Do you really think that way?
Original.
I am looking forward to tomorrow’s matches.
Shit... Ouch!
My deck...
Geez, treating people like trash again!
Dr. Faker...
Heart Burning!
The World Carnival finally reaches its Semi-Finals!
Just who will be the strongest Duelist that wins the honor as the first-generation W.D.C. Champion?
We will now announce the match-ups!
Tron VS Kaito!
Yuma VS Ryoga!
Astral, I'm definitely gonna win the championship...
And I'll resolve everything with my own hands!
Right.
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The W.D.C. Semi-Finals finally began!
My opponent is Shark, and I'll give you everything I've got!
Huh? Hey! Shark!!
So this is the Duel Tower?
That Shark seems kinda strange.
It's probably the power of his Number...
Yeah, I'll win! I will win this and awaken Shark!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Vanishing Bond!
Yuma VS Shark: The fated Duel!!
What did you say? I made your sister… !?
Tron's family.
Faker's family.
Now that I think about it, they're all men!
I really wanna have an all-men family!
Observation #20: "Akari is a woman".
You just realized that?!
He disappeared.