C'mon now!!
Get a hold of yourself!!
There's another trap, Yuma!
Wha-?
Hurry, Yuma!!
We're safe...
Ugh!! What is wrong with you, Yuma?!
Yuma?
Droite...
Kaito...
IV...
V...
...and now Shark...
I'll...
In front of you, Yuma!!
Whoa, what's this place?
It seems that this is our battlefield.
I've been waiting.
Wait, you're...
Gauche!
Alright, satisfy me, Yuma!!
With our Duel, that is!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Heart Burning!!
So who will be the last entrant in the finals?!
Will it be Yuma Tsukumo or will it be Gauche?!
The field the two will be battling in...
...is the Dangerous Canyon!!
Let's go!!
Yeah!!
Number 59: A Fierce Fight! Yuma VS Gauche:
This is My Manly Dueling Soul!"
--Duel!!
I'll take the first move!
It's my turn! Draw!!
I Summon Heroic Challenger - Double Lance!
Whoa! Due to the Field Magic's effects,
Gauche has suddenly received 200 points of damage!
Due to this field, when a Monster is Summoned or declares an attack,
The player receives 200 points of damage!
So the more you attack, the more your Life is depleted?
Wha-? That's really bad!
And I only have 100 Life points to boot!
How was it? Did you like my little present, Gauche-kun?
I get it. So that's your little gimmick, huh?
When Droite and I were kids, we were picked up by Mr. Heartland.
He then taught us how to Duel and always did what we asked.
But after seeing his--Yuma's Dueling style,
it reignited my burning Dueling spirit!
These are the Duels I crave for!!
Double Lance's effect activates!
When used to Xyz Summon a Heroic Champion,
it counts as two materials.
I Overlay my now two Level Four Double Lances!
I build the Overlay Network and Xyz Summon!
Come forth!
Heroic Champion - Gandiva!!
He completely disregarded the Field Magic's effect damage.
Now I set two cards face-down and end my turn!
Now bring it, Yuma!
Show me that spirit of yours!
Man, that Gauche!
I can't attack blindly due to how low my Life is.
Why are you hesitating, Yuma?
He's all pumped up.
If we don't do our best...
I get what you're trying to say!
It's my turn! Draw!
And now you'll take my Trap!
A-Ah crap!
Here it comes!
Heroic Gift.
When my opponent's Life is less than 2000,
it changes it to 4000 Life.
Why did he boost my Life?
Then I can draw two cards!
Why'd he change Yuma's Life to 4000?
The hell is this all about, pal?!
Don't get me wrong.
All I wanted was to draw some cards.
Besides, it's not my style to hunt down weak prey.
Why you!!
To think that Gauche gave Yuma some Life...
He's giving his all in this Duel, it seems.
I set a Monster in Face-Down Defense Mode!
Yuma, you can't win against him with just defending!
It's fine! I got a little plan of my own!
I now set a card and end my turn!
Heh, taking quite the defensive stance, aren't you?
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Heroic Challenger - Night-Attack Kantera!
Alright! He got 200 more damage!
So what?!
I use Night-Attack Kantera to attack your Face-Down Monster!
This card...
...can destroy a Monster in Face-Down Defense Mode...
...without conducting Battle Damage!
Now your field is empty!
Gandiva can attack you directly now!
I was waiting for that!
What?!
When Mog Mole is destroyed, it can be Special Summoned in Face-Up Defense Mode!
That little attack that cost you 400 Life Points...
...was all a waste!
Why you! You ruined the mood!
I activate Gandiva's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
I can destroy a Level Four or lower Monster that was Special Summoned!
What?!
If you're gonna fight cowardly, I'll crush you!
Now go, Gandiva! Direct Attack!!
Trap, activate! Battle Break!
It destroys the battling Monster...
...and ends the battle!
Stop defending this mood!
Trap, activate! Battler's Pride!
It negates and destroys a card that ends the Battle Phase!
Now go, Gandiva!!
I set a card and end my turn.
You get it now?
You can't beat me with that spirit of yours!
But I can't afford to lose this Duel!
Yuma, you just can't win this Duel.
Say what?
Now that you're being too cautious, you fear winning in this Duel.
Huh?
It's probably from watching Kaito's and Shark's Duels.
Due to you watching, you must've developed a fear of Dueling.
You think I'm afraid?!
It's my turn! Draw!
Am I wrong...?
I'll...
I Summon Gagaga Magician!!
And from my hand, I activate One-Shot Wand!
This card raises the Attack Power of a Magician-Type Monster by 800 points!
Now Gagaga Magician's Attack Power is higher!
Go, Gagaga Magician!
Attack Gandiva!!
This mood won't work with me!
Trap, activate! Heroic Advance!
Because you attacked Heroic Champion,
a Heroic Challenger's Attack Power is doubled,
and becomes the attack target!
However, the Monsters aren't destroyed!!
I activate One-Shot Wand's effect!
By destroying this card when a battle has finished,
I can draw one card!
Alright! I Summon Grandran!
When there is an Xyz Monster on my opponent's field,
I can Special Summon him from my hand in Attack Mode!
And now I Overlay my Level Four Gagaga Magician and Grandran!
I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth!!
Gagaga Gunman!
What? In Defense Mode?!
It's obvious that he put him in Defense Mode to avoid taking damage from the Field Magic.
When Gagaga Gunman is in Defense Mode,
once per turn, by detaching an Overlay Unit,
I inflict 800 points of damage to my opponent!
I did it! How 'bout that, Gauche?!
I set two cards and end my turn!
How 'bout that? That was such a cheap attack!
I don't...
I don't wanna have such a lame Duel with you!
It's my turn! Draw!
From my hand, I activate the Equip Magic, Xyz Crowned Jewel!
This card makes the Xyz Monster's Rank to a Level and is treated as two Xyz Material.
What? Using an Xyz Monster to Xyz Summon?
I Overlay my Level Four Night-Attack Kantera and my, now two Gandivas!
I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth!
Heroic Champion - Kusanagi!
Bring it!!
If you really wish to defeat me,
show how you truly Duel!
Come at me!!
How I truly Duel?
Yes! The true way to Duel!!
I see what he means...
Now matter the circumstance, Gauche kept his Dueling style as is.
But all I've done...
I set a Monster in Face-Down Defense Mode!
How 'bout that, Gauche?!
Yuma...
What are you doing, Yuma?
Get off, Kotori.
I'm going alone from here on out.
Wha-?
Please!
The way he Duels...
I gotta give it my all against him, got it?
Yuma...
Well go win and pick me up afterwards.
Yeah!
Go for it, Yuma!
There's no doubt that Shark and Kaito are strong.
They also possess fearsome power.
To people like them, even you are feeling fear,
I can understand how you feel enough.
But haven't you always overcome that fear, and come all this way?
Astral... Let's go.
In the end, I have to Duel in my own way!
Yuma...
Gauche!
Now I will let you to see my real Dueling!
Oh! So you're finally acting serious!
Let's do this!
I activate the Magic Card from my hand, Fighter’s Charm!
This card can switch a Monster from Defense Position to Attack Position!
But this turn, its Attack Power becomes the same as its Defense Power!
Then I attack Gagaga Gunman with the 2500 Attack Power Kusanagi!
I activate a Trap, Overlay Burst!
Until the End Phase, this card increase one Monster’s Attack Power by 500!
I got this!
Don't be so sure!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, Kusanagi can negate the activation and effect of a Trap Card,
and gain 500 Attack Points during this turn!
3000 Attack Points?!
Finish it, Kusanagi!
Their difference in Attack Power is now reversed!
Go, Kusanagi! Attack Gagaga Gunman!
Dream on! I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Fighting Bond!
It negates one Monster’s destruction in battle!
But you still receive damage!
I set two cards, and end my turn!
Hmph! Now you only have 600 Life left.
About ready to give up?
What are you talking about?
The real match begins now!
That's it! That's the mood I wanted from you all along!
What?!
The heck?!
It's a new Field Magic.
Battleground of the Setting Sun.
You can only battle with one Monster.
When a Monster is destroyed,
it inflicts 300 points of damage to that player.
Let's do this... Yuma!
Heck yeah!
My turn! Draw!
I attack Kusanagi with Gagaga Gunman!
What can you do with that guy?!
Mine has higher Attack Power!
When Gagaga Gunman is in Attack Position,
by detaching one Overlay Unit, it gains 1000 Attack Points,
and lowers the Monster my opponent controls by 500!
Not too bad.
Go, Gagaga Gunmen!
I activate a Trap, Heroic Change!
Then I activate Kusanagi’s Monster Effect!
I negate the Trap I just activated,
and increase Kusanagi’s Attack Power by 500!
A draw...
To think you defeated my Kusanagi...
Yuma, you're not half bad!
Right back at you!
But this will be our final battle!
I activate a Trap, Xyz Hotblooded Battle!
When an Xyz Monster is destroyed by battle,
by paying 1000 LP, both players can use the destroyed Xyz Monster as the material,
and Special Summon an Xyz Monster with the same rank!
Special Summon?
Come forth! Heroic Champion Excalibur!
But the Xyz Monster Summoned by this effect will be destroyed after the battle!
So bring it, Yuma!
It's your turn now!
Summon Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Hope?!
It won't be any fun if you don't, right?
Let's both duke it out with our aces!
He wants to fight against a Number?
Fine... I accept your challenge!
Come!
Come forth! Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Now bring it on!
Yeah! Aspiring Emperor - Hope attacks Excalibur!
I activate Excalibur's effect!
During a battle, I detach all of its Overlay Units
to double its Attack Power!
It's got 4000 Attack Points!
I activate Hope's effect!
Rune Barrier!!
He protected me!
Still, once the battle ends,
due to Xyz Hotblooded Battle’s effect, the Monsters will be destroyed!
And thanks to the Field Magic's effect, you will take 300 points of damage and lose!
No... I still have this card!
What!?
I'm gonna bring it to ya!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic from my hand, Double-Up Chance!
When a Monster’s attack is negated,
it can double its Attack Power and attack once again!
What?! 5000 Attack Points?!
Go! Hope Sword Double Slash!!
It is decided!
The one who advanced to the Final is…
Yuma Tsukumo!
Tsukumo...
Yuma...
Sorry, Droite... I lost...
Gauche!
As expected, your mood is simply great.
I had a blast!
Yeah!
Yuma, take this with you.
Huh?
In exchange, if I ever catch you Dueling without a good mood...
I'll beat the hell outta you!
This is...
Excalibur?!
But this card...
What we call a “Duelist” also means to inherit the loser’s feelings.
He entrusted his feeling towards Dueling to you.
Thank you, Gauche. I'll definitely inherit your feelings!
Yeah! Please do, Yuma!
Do your best!
Gosh, Yuma! Get back here!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
It's the Duel Carnival Tournament Finals!
The ones who advanced are: Kaito, Shark, Tron, and me!
No matter who my opponent is, I have to find a way to win!
Huh? My deck's gone!
God, you're such an idiot!
Haruto is above us.
Just leave this to us!
You… Are you really okay with this?!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Overture Towards the Final Battle:
The New Foe Dr. Faker!"
You're Dr. Faker?
Here's today's introduction!
Straight out of the Gagaga Academy, our new friend, Gagaga Gunman!
Gagaga Academy? When did we name it that?
And we nominated you as the university's principle!
I'm Principle Astral.
You really did become it!