Kaito's disciple Jin, has captured Kotori and the others!
Furthermore he can see through cards.
If I lose, their lives will be in danger.
I ain't losing!
I'll bring it to em'!
Now, kneel before my master, Kaito-sama!
With this, I end my turn!
Kotori... Everyone...
Yuma...
I'll save them for sure!
Please... Everyone will...
I'm feeling fear... but why?
In that duel, it was the first time I thought about death.
I see.
Astral!
This is fear...
Hey, Astral!
What are you daydreaming about!?
If you're not gonna do anything, get lost!
Yuma, you have no monsters in your hand.
And due to Shock Ruler's effect, you can't use Traps.
If you don't draw a monster card on this draw..
We will...
That's why I'll get a monster!
My Turn, Draw!
Alright! I got a monster card-
Kuribolt?
He only has 300 attack points!
That monster is...
Yuma, summon that Kuribolt!
This weak monster?
Just summon it already!
I get it!
I summon Kuribolt!
This is good.
By detaching the Overlay Units currently on our field,
Kuribolt can Special Summon Kuribolt Tokens on your field.
Currently on the field, Shock Ruler's Overlay Units are 2.
That's right!
I activate Kuribolt's effect!
Kuribolt will multiply itself by 2 equal to Shock Ruler's Overlay Units.
Alright!
Awesome!
Now there are 3 Kuribolts!
What an outstanding effect...
But what can you do with three weaklings?
I can see it!
The number of monster cards in your hand is 0!
You can no longer summon powerful monsters!
Don't panic, Yuma.
Use Boltage Summon!
R-Right!
I activate the Magic Card, Boltage Summon!
This card, by releasing all Kuribolt Tokens on the field,
we can Special Summon level 4 or lower monsters from our deck equal to the same amount of Tokens.
That's right!
I release the 2 Kuribolt Tokens!
To Special Summon Ganbara Knight and Shadow Lizard from my deck!
But the monsters Special Summoned with this effect have their attack and defense power reduced to 0!
I overlay the level 4 Shadow Lizard and Ganbara Knight!
I use these two monsters to construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 39 Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Yuma...
In such a situation he drew Kuribolt,
And used it for a combo to call out Hope!
Someone like him...
So this is your Numbers?
Go, Hope!
Attack Shock Ruler!
Hope Sword Slash!!
Alright, I destroyed his Numbers!
I still have an attack left!
I now attack directly with Kuribolt!
Unbelievable!
He did it~ura!
Just wait everyone!
I'll save you right away!
Okay. With this I end my turn-
Wait!
Set the Traps in your hand!
You can't use Traps yet, but they'll be useful.
That's right, I understand!
I set 2 cards face-down and end my turn!
I see, so there might be some hope after all.
What is it!?
What's funny!?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
You've simply allowed yourself to suffer even more!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
It's my turn, Draw!
"Numbers 18: Chaos Xyz Change! The Light of Hope: Hope Ray!!"
From my hand I Special Summon Rainbow Shaman!
If I don't have any monsters on my field,
And, if there's a Xyz Monster on the opponent's field, I can Special Summon this card from my hand!
Level 8!? That's not good.
But it's attack power is 0.
Then I select Rainbow Shaman, to activate the Permanent Magic, Xyz Plant!
The Continuous Magic, Xyz Plant is Special Summoned as a monster with 0 attack power!
And its level will be the same as Rainbow Shaman which is level 8!
A Magic Card became a Monster!?
Could it be!?
I overlay the level 8 Rainbow Shaman and Xyz Plant!
I use these two monsters to construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 11!
The ruler with the All-Controlling-Eye, Big Eye!
N-No way!
Two Numbers!?
Furthermore it's a rank 8!
Did you think that I had just one Numbers?
I have obtained this power from Kaito-sama!
C-Can he really win against him!?
To summarize, he's too powerful!
Believe in Yuma!
Yuma, don't panic!
You have Hope's effect!
I know that!
By detaching Hope's Overlay Units, I can negate attacks.
Even if it's rank 8, its attacks are useless!
I activate Big Eye's monster effect!
By detaching an Overlay Unit,
Big Eye can control one of the opponent monsters!
Your Numbers, Aspiring Emperor Hope is mine!
W-What!?
Now, Big Eye!
Temptation Glance!!
No way, my Hope is...
This is the ability of a rank 8?
It can control any monster!
Now Aspiring Emperor Hope,
As my pawn, attack Kuribolt!
Save us~ura!
In the turn that its Xyz effect was used, Big Eye can't attack.
They are in deep fear now!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Not yet!
My turn, Draw!
It's here...
I can summon a monster now.
Did you forget that I can see through all of your cards?
What!?
You drew a monster card!
I activate the Continuous Magic, Dance of Forbidden Summon!
Both players, for 2 turns ,
Cannot Summon, Special Summon, or set a monster from their hands!
If he can't summon monsters, he can't block his attacks!
No way!
With this I end my turn!
My turn, Draw!
It's over now!
Fall into the pits of Hell along with your friends!
Battle! Big Eye attacks directly!
The Trap Card, Yuma!
Th-That's right!
I can use Traps this turn!
Trap activate, Hope Block!
With this card, if the opponent's monster attacks directly,
By sending a monster card from my hand to the cemetery,
The battle damage goes down by its attack power!
Dododo Warrior, protect us!
Don't think you've escaped the fear of death just yet!
Take this!
Aspiring Emperor Hope attacks directly!
Yuma, your other Trap!
Right.
Trap, activate! Xyz Weight!
With this card, for each Overlay Unit attached to a Xyz Monster,
It's attack power goes down by 800 points!
Yuma!
Kotori...
Managed to somehow survive these 2 monster's attacks, eh?!
Then I activate the Continuous Magic, Dance of Prevent Reborn!
Both players cannot summon monsters from their cemeteries!
I've basically tied your hands and legs here!
Yuma...
You have no monsters on your field!
On the other hand, I have 2 powerful monsters!
Resistance is futile!
In my next turn, your life and your friends' lives are over!
I end my turn!
Damn it...
Now it's... over.
Everyone...!
There's only one way to save your friends.
Just surrender this duel and bare witness.
Accept your defeat and give me one of your Numbers!
If you do that, your friends' lives will be saved!
What did you say!?
So how about it? It's a pleasant offer.
Just one sacrifice and all of your friends will be saved.
Save us, Ura!
Yuma...
Don't do that!
Yuma!
This has become even more entertaining!
Weep in your own suffering!
As I though, I couldn't fight after all.
There's no possibility of a counterattack.
If you continue dueling like this you can't save them.
Right now there's one thing in our hands that we can do.
By surrendering the Numbers cards and me!
You...
I will be annihilated with you.
Just surrender.
STOP KIDDING ME!
Yuma...
I'm dueling to save them.
Even though I might end up losing.
But...
They're my best friends that dueled along side me!
And I can't betray them!
Yuma, that's why I-
You still don't get it!?
You're my...
...best friend, Astral!
Astral?
Yuma...
Hey kid, hurry up and surrender and hand over the Numbers!
Stop joking around!
I will never surrender!
Fine then.
Kaito-sama will enjoy taking away your soul!
Hey, Kaito!
If this guy really your subordinate?
Is this guy with you in your duels?
Hey, is that really Kaito over there?
W-What do you mean?
It can't be...
I'm gonna cat it to 'em!
A puppet?
What does this mean?
No way, my Kaito-sama!
As I thought.
I've dueled Kaito before.
His strength is fearsome.
But he's not the type of person that enjoys dueling by watching people suffer.
He's not someone who'd use your ways!
I was afraid of that thing?
I was afraid as well.
But we found hope by not giving up!
Let's bring it to em'!
Yuma...
That's right.
The feeling I had was not only fear.
The precious feelings you gave me.
Yuma...
I want to win for you... and your friends!
You...
W-What?
Is that... Astral?
Let's win, Yuma!
Astral!
Here I go, my turn... Draw!
The Magic Card, Come Back!
Bring Hope back with this card!
Alright!
I activate the Magic Card, Come Back!
With this card, I take back the monster that was controlled!
Come Back, Hope!
What!?
The pieces of a new way to victory have all gathered here!
This is...
The power of hope, the one who can truly change light,
Chaos No. 39!
Chaos Numbers?
This card overlays Aspiring Emperor Hope with its own Overlay Units,
And evolves it!
Let's go, Yuma!
Right!
Chaos Xyz Change!
Appear now, Chaos No. 39!
Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
Wh-What is that!?
Amazing!
Chaos Numbers?!
But my Big Eye is still stronger, you can't win!
Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray's effect activates!
For each of its Overlay Units used,
Its attack power goes up by 500 points!
I'm using all of its 3 Overlay Units!
Hope Ray's attack power goes up!
Overlay Charge!
What!?
Then the opponent's monster's attack power goes down by 1000 for each Overlay Unit!
No way!
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
Attack Big Eye!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!
W-What the?
Yuma!
You're safe!
- That was amazing, Astral!
- Everyone, over here!
Thank you, Astral!
That was outstanding!
We're friends from now on.
Y-You guys, why are you all thanking Astral?
I saved you!
You guys are really rude, you know that?!
Yuma!
Wait!
Observation #13...
"If you have friends, you can believe in hope."
Thank you, Yuma.
For acknowledging me as a friend.
What stupid people.
I still had one more Numbers left with me.
You're...
Could you be, Kaito-sama!?
Kaito-sama I truly acknowledge you as my God!
That's why I want to be your servant!
Is that so?
Then I'll take away you Numbers and your soul.
Numbers taken successfully.
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
In order to summon a high-level monster, does the monster on the field go to the cemetery or back to you hand?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
We're about to disclose Yuma's childhood.
The secrets behind his parents and the Lord of Keys.
And...
They never let me come on their adventures with them!
That Lord of Keys your father owned...
It seems to have some relation to me.
It was my Dad who taught me how to "bring it to 'em".
Yuma, you don't look kinda down.
It was then that I saw something from another world.
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal.
"The Promised 'Bring it to 'Em'"
Dad... Mom...
The answer is... they go to your Graveyard!
We call this term "release".
Level Five and Level Six demands one.
You release two Monsters in order to Summon Level Seven and higher Monsters.