What happened?
What's wrong?
That... that's...
What on earth is going on?
Clea... ning...
How annoying!
This damn Trashbot!!
Clea... ning... Clean... ning...
What on earth is happening?
What are you going to do with my conditions?
Don't you worry about the safety of those hostages?
Money! Hurry up and prepare some money!
And don't forget the helicopter!
Now the criminal who is inside the shopping mall
demands cash and a helicopter for running away.
This is bad, a big incident!
Yuma, you're in the Shopping Mall right now, aren't you?
What are you talking about? I... eh... school, I'm still in school!
Yuma!!
No need to say that.
Yesss~
I know you were there for sure!
Because you're already on TV!
Ahh! They're recording me!
Do you understand? Hurry up and shoot some scoop photos for me!
Just you say so - Geez!
Besides the helicopter for getting away...
Hurry up and provide me those things!
What a scary face he has!
Look, Yuma! It's Numbers!
The criminal actually has a Numbers?
Please let me pass, sorry!
Yuma!
Numbers, confirmed.
All right, let the hunt begin!
Understood!
Let... let me pass!
Eh... what the heck is that?
Shit! What happened to the money they promised me?!
That hurt!
What happened?
What is going on?
Time stopped?
Why would such a thing happen?
What's... going on?
What happened?
Who the hell're you?!
I am the light that illuminates the darkness
stagnating in the hearts of humanity...
People address me as the Numbers Hunter!!
Numbers... Hunter?
Then allow me to reclaim your Numbers!
How... how dare he do that to my friend?
I want to teach him a good lesson, Master!
No... I mean Kaito-sama!!
Alright, then let's duel!
Let me tear up the darkness inside you!
You... you said duel?
Ahh. Numbers can only attach to Duelists.
Is that so? Then this card... is known as Numbers?
Then you must have this kind of card too, right?
Interesting! Then your Numbers... is mine!
Foolish!
Then allow me to release you from your suffering!
Understood!
Duel mode, Photon Change!
Then, allow me to hunt your soul!
Wa... wait! Can you let me pass by?
Yuma, there is a duel on the top floor!
Wha... what happened?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Kaito, who is collecting the Numbers cards, -->
<--his goal for doing that is...
What the hell are you...?
What the hell are you!?
"Numbers 13: The Soul Hunter!
Numbers Pursuer Appears!
Is that all the power of your Numbers offers...?
Go, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
Photon Hand!
The hunt for Numbers is completed.
Understood.
This is... why the criminal...
Num... Numbers Hunter...
What... what did you say?
Numbers Hunter?
Don't tell me...
This is...
The Numbers was taken away!
It's like earlier...
What's happening? That boy...
LET'S GET HIM!!
How... how did that boy...
How did you get in?
...Just be quiet!!...
W... wait!!
Trash... trash... trash... trash...  ...
Let me hear... more screams!
More... more...!
Come in.
Is the Numbers reclaiming going well?
Yes.
That's excellent.
That zealous duel of yours can definitely bring peace to the Heartland!
Then how many Numbers did you manage to collect?
Orbital.
Understood.
So far we collected 11 Numbers.
Fantastic!
You were able to collect that many within such short time period.
Looks like I've made the right choice.
What happened, Kaito?
Is that right?
You seem to worry about the snatched souls, don't you?
It can't be helped.
With the science we have currently, we can only take away Numbers along with the holders' soul.
But no need to worry.
People who were controlled by Numbers all were attached to evil forces.
Those forces amplify their desires, so they all are bad people.
Is it true that if I manage to collect all 100 Numbers,
then Haruto... my little brother can go back to normal?
Of course.
The only treatment to cure Haruto is to collect all Numbers.
Now all you have to do is to believe.
No need to worry,
your ambitious heart can will certainly touch Dr. Faker.
Yes.
Continue your Quest for Numbers!
The sooner you find them, the faster Haruto will recover.
How's the progress with the reclaiming of Numbers?
Dr. Faker-sama, everything is going well.
Is that so, then good!
In order to protect something important,
people have to give up something in proportion as well.
Just like me. For the sake of protecting this world, I gave up the right to be a human.
In order to protect Haruto, Kaito resigned to be a human as well.
Yes, Dr. Faker-sama.
One day, I know there will be a messenger from the Astral World.
That day, that time... there's no mistake, that messenger shall come here.
WE HAVE TO BEAT THAT PERSON UNTIL NOTHING REMAINS!
AND SEND BACK HIS REMAININGS TO THAT WORLD!!
OTHER THAN THAT, THERE IS NO WAY TO SAVE OUR WORLD!!
As you wish.
Here is the News Coverage of the incident in the Shopping Mall.
Like I said, you guys made a mistake!
The boy who was caught along with the bandit,
accidentally appeared between the policemen and criminal...
So you became the spotlight of my special features?!
Somehow Yuma got mixed up in the crime scene.
But how did you do that?
Eh, don't worry about those details.
Geez.
Yuma, do you need to tell her about Numbers?
Are you an idiot? My sister never allows me to duel!
How can I tell her that?
Wh... what?
Eh.... no... nothing.
You! Don't tell me...
It's not like that, I didn't duel!!
Numbers Hunter...
Thank you!
Big brother...
Haruto, how are you today?
What's wrong?
Why is everyone laughing?
I don't need laughter...
All I need is screams...
...something that can comfort me...
For me... I need more, more screams!
Haruto...
Big brother... am I strange?
No... you're just having a bad dream...
Dream?
Yeah... a bad dream.
So don't worry. I swear I'll awaken you from that dream!
Yuma!
What's up?
If besides me, there are other people collecting Numbers...
Something about that Numbers Hunter, huh...
Does that mean, one day that Hunter will come after me?
It won't take too long for that Hunter to find you.
No... maybe he already found you...
What the... are you trembling?
Then watch how I duel, and win in my way!
I have a bad feeling about this...
There is a huge Duel square in the neighboring town!
Nice! Let's check that out on Sunday!
Hey, Kotori, I'll let you witness my brigning it to 'em!
Oh? If you can win, then why not?
Ah! That's a close one!
If I had decided to attack then...
Right, Kotori?
Geez, didn't you lose all your matches?
Hey! Bringing it to 'em means endless challenges!
The important thing is to never give up!
Then when can you win for once?
Next time, for sure!!
Yuma... looks like we should be on guard.
I have a bad feeling...
Here we go again...
What happened?
Oh nothing - nothing!!
Rain...
Darn it, it's raining... Let's go, Kotori!
Yuma!!
You are so slow, Kotori!!
Geez, Wait!
KOTORI!!
Yuma, Yuma!
This is...
Kotori!
What on earth is this?
Ah... It's same as the last time!
This whistle...
Don't tell me...
Who are you?
Did you do all this?
Now there is a special field within this area.
The time flow is slowed down to 1/10000 its normality.
It's me, Orbital's power!
Only those who hold Numbers can move freely in this area.
Looks like you have Numbers too.
Numbers... Don't tell he's...
...the Numbers Hunter!
Yuma, this man is extremely dangerous! Hurry up and run!
Now you're telling me to run...?!
What's this?
This duel anchor... until the Duel has an outcome...
...we cannot separate from each other!
What?
In other words, you cannot run away from this duel!
Let the hunting begin, Numbers!
Although I have no idea who you are...
but I will accept your challenge!
Yuma... I will help you in this Duel.
What are you saying?
Didn't you tremble like crazy seconds ago?
I never believe such things like instinct.
But... this opponent is an exception,
You cannot defeat him alone.
Eh? Is that guy that strong?
I am afraid so.
He might be the strongest one you have faced so far.
No... stronger than anyone I have faced...
If you said that, then I am all fired up!
Don't forget my goal is to become duel champion!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!!
Duel Mode, Photon Change!!
What the?!
AR Vision - link established!
Now, let me hunt... your soul!!
DUEL!!
I will go first.
My turn, draw!!
I activate the Magic card, Photon Veil, from my hand!!
This card can return 3 LIGHT monsters from my hand to my deck,
and add 3 LIGHT monsters to my hand!
Exchanging 3 monsters...
Then I activate the Quick-play Magic card Photon Lead!
This card can special summon one LV4 or lower Light Monster, which was added to my hand from deck,
in attack position!
I special summon Daybreaker!
When this card is successfully special summoned,
I can special summon another one from my hand!
Come, another Daybreaker!
The newly summoned Daybreaker activates its effect!
I special summon Daybreaker once again!
What? Summon 3 monsters in a row?
Oh no, all monsters on his field are LV4!
In other words...
I overlay three LV4 Daybreakers,
I construct Overlay Network with these three monsters.
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, No.10, White Knight Illuminator!!
Impossible!
He's able to summon Numbers in his very first turn!
It's not over yet!
I activate the effect of No.10 Illuminator!
Once per turn, by detaching one Overlay Unit,
he allows me to send one card from my hand to the graveyard, and draw one card!
And I activate the effect of Light Serpent which was send to the graveyard!!
When Light Serpent is sent to my graveyard from my hand,
it can be special summoned to the field!!
Then I normal summon Plasma Ball!
There is more? Now he has three monsters...
How many monsters does that guy plan to summon?
No... that's...
I overlay the LV3 Light Serpent and Plasma Ball!
I construct the Overlay Network with these two monsters!
Xyz summon!
come forth! No.20
Ant Soil Brilli-Ant!!
You gotta be kidding...
He summoned 2 Numbers in one turn?
Now... let the hunt begin...
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
Basically, how many monsters can you summon to the field in maximum?
5 or 6?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
This guy is unbelievably strong!!
Don't tell me this guy's dueling is even above mine?
Impossible!! I'm actually feeling fear to duel...
Yuma, overcome that fear!
Let's work as a team in this Duel!
It's all... over now...
No way!
Next  time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Come forth, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!"
I'm gonna bring it to him!
The answer is 5! When 5 monsters are assembled, there must be a great pressure, right?
I want to summon a bunch of monsters too, and use them to battle!