My name's Yuma Tsukumo!
A Duelist aimin' for Duel Champion!
We have to get back the pieces of my memories that have been scattered, the Numbers cards!
Can it, will you?!
Something big's happening in my city right now!
A computer virus bomb's about to spread!
If it activates, the city'll be thrown into a huge panic!
And the culprit's my highly respected teacher!
I gotta beat him in a Duel to stop the virus bomb!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Darn it!
I can't believe he used my Monster that way!
20 minutes remain until virus bomb is released.
It's my turn!
It's my turn, pal!
Is it just me, or has Yuma-kun been talking to himself this whole time?
In summary, is he okay?
It's fine, it's fine. Don't pay him any mind.
That's just Yuma's "Bring it to 'em" mode...
My turn! Draw!
Yuma, go Summon Ganbara Knight.
Don't butt into someone else's problem!
A Numbers is riding on this Duel.
If we do not get his Numbers, I will be obliterated.
Not that I give a care about you.
You aren't strong enough to win on your own.
Come again?
If that's your reason, then that's the final straw!
I won't do a single thing you tell me to do during this Duel!
What do you mean by not doing anything I tell you?
It means if you tell me to move my right hand, I'll just move my left!
And if you tell me to play Ganbara Knight...
...I'll Summon Achacha Archer!
You can't be serious...
When this card is successfully Summoned, my opponent takes 500 points of damage.
Nothin' to it!
I just gave Sensei some damage!
But it came with a high price.
Had you Summoned Ganbara Knight, you would have had two Level Four Monsters.
You could have Exceed Summoned Aspiring Emperor - Hope.
I see! I messed up!
I knew that already!
How dare you damage my Life...!
I activate a Trap Card!
Damage Vaccine OmegaΩ MAX!
When I take damage, this card recovers
my Life by the damage I received!
*Shock*
So my attack just now was wasted!
I yearn for a perfect victory!
I won't let you injure even a speck of my Life!
This is not good!
Even if I try to say I was being used, the fact remains that I was the one who launched the virus bomb!
In summary, I'll be blamed as the culprit!
We're running out of time, Yuma...
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
"Numbers 4: The Countdown to Reversal!
The Ace-In-The-Hole's Astral!?"
There's gotta be a switch for the virus bomb in here somewhere.
And I'm gonna stop the thing!
I'll end my turn now!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the effect of Numbers 34 - Computer Beast Terabyte!
I can remove one of its Overlay Units once per turn
and gain control over one of my
opponent's Level Four or lower Monsters!
AHH! He snatched my Gogogo Golem again!
If you had Summoned Hope, he wouldn't have been able to steal him away.
The effect Terabyte holds only allows it to control Monsters with units of level.
But Exceed Monsters don't have actual levels.
Your Dueling is defective.
You should just obey me.
Shut up!
I'll take damage, but Gogogo Golem's gonna return to my field!
When it does...
I'm not so foolish a Duelist that I'd use the exact same strategy I used in my previous turn.
I activate the Continuous Magics, Virus Mail and Cracking!
Hey, what's a Continuous Magic?
Unlike Normal Magic Cards,
Continuous Magics will continue their effects as long as the card remains on the field.
The effect of Virus Mail lets me select a Level Four or lower Monster and Direct Attack with it.
And afterwards, the Monster is destroyed.
He's...
Go, Gogogo Golem!
Direct Attack him!
After the battle, Gogogo Golem will be destroyed by Virus Mail's effect!
Gogogo Golem!
Furthermore, I activate the effects of my other Continuous Magic, Cracking!
When your Monster is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard,
you receive 800 points of damage!
Now do you see?
This is my Terabyte Combo.
Darn...!
This Terabyte Combo's gonna bring me some problems!
Huh?
Your body's starting to fade a bit.
Just as your Life is injured, my own life is obliterated.
Your... life...?
If you fail, you will lose something of great value.
What's wrong with Yuma all of a sudden?
He seems kinda down.
That is not good!
Ahh, gotta do something!
That's it!
Yuma-kun!
Yuma-kun, you're...
...a Garyouhousuu!
[Literally "Unrecognized Genius", but also can literally mean "Crouching Dragon, Young Phoenix"]
A Gachouhoso?
[Literally "Weak Goose"]
NO!
Garyou as in a crouching dragon!
And housuu refers to a Houou - a young Phoenix!
In summary, outstanding talent lies dormant within you!
In me?
If you unlock that talent, you will no doubt win!
Wow, you're praising me too much!
Sweet! Lem'me do my best!
Observation number six...
"Humans work their hardest when they are praised."
Yuma, truthfully, I need to speak with you.
About what?
You possess an eternal combo of recovery.
You jump aimlessly over boxes and you drown yourself in the pool.
You change your character at whim.
And you are weird.
In summary...
...you are intriguing.
Ya jerk! You looking for a fight!?
What the?!
The elevator...!
It's moving!
I-I can see the sky!
We're moving upwards!
I did it!
This is the final door!
Fine.
I'll take you on.
Don't mock the Karate Glove!
This will be your front row seats
to the view of my virus bomb's success!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Shoot! What's wrong with Sensei?!
Yuma is going to lose to him...
But I must win at all costs.
I won't do a single thing you tell me to do!
It means if you tell me to move my right hand, I'll just move my left!
I've got that approach too...
Here goes! My turn! Draw!
Cool!
Got me a sweet card!
I Summon Goblindbergh!
Yes! When Goblindbergh is Summoned successfully,
in summary, he can Special Summon a Level Four or lower Monster from his hand!
Yuma, use Zubaba Knight from your hand.
Heck no!
Since you told me to play Zubaba Knight...
...I'll go an' Special Summon Ganbara Knight!
I got the Level Four Ganbara Knight and Goblindbergh!
That means...!
I can go an' Exceed Summon Hope!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
I Overlay the Level Four Ganbara Knight and Goblindbergh!
I construct the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Exceed Summon!
Show yourself, Numbers 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
It's up to you, Hope!
Number 39.. Aspiring Emperor, Hope.
Yuma. Don't set down the trap card from your hand.
This one you cannot use.
Shut up! Listen up, I'm not gonna follow your orders!
I set one card from my hand, turn end !!
It's about time that you gave back my manuscript!
You...
You...!
Alright!
It's my turn!
Draw!
Terabyte's effect activates!
I use an Overlay Unit to gain control of Achacha Archer!
Took my Monster again...!
Then, with the effect of the Continuous Magic, Virus Mail,
Achacha Archer will be destroyed after attacking you directly!
If this continues, in summary, Yuma-kun will lose!
Isn't there something I can do?!
Doesn't Hope have a great effect of his own?
Hope's effect!
That's it!
I activate Hope's effect!
I use an Overlay Unit!
I can then negate a Monster's attack!
Virus Mail has the effect to automatically destroy the Monster when it successfully attacks you directly.
By negating it using Hope's effect,
it will not go into the Graveyard.
And moreover, Cracking's effect won't activate.
I get it! So Sensei's combo was blocked!
Oh? And here I thought you were dumb.
Yuma-kun seems much smarter than usual.
In summary, it's because of the Dueling Spirit?
Dueling Spirit?
Now he can't use his Overlay Units anymore.
Right! He can't use his Terabyte Combo!
But I do hope you didn't think I hadn't read right through your little strategy.
What?
The conditions for my perfect victory have been set.
Trap, activate!
Bug Switch!
When Bugman X, Y and Z are in my Graveyard,
I can switch my Defense Position Monster into Attack Mode
in order to Special Summon Super Bugman in Face-Up Defense Mode!
W-Well...
I thought it'd be in Attack Mode, but the Monster's in Defense Mode...
You really thought I'd do something so pointless?
I activate Super Bugman's effect!
When this card is in Face-Up Defense Mode,
I can switch the Attack Points of all Attack Position Monsters with their Defense Points.
Terabyte holds 2900 Attack Points.
Thus, Terabyte's Attack Power becomes 2900!
2900 Attack Points?!
Plus, Hope's and Archer's Attack Power...!
I then proceed to attack!
Go, Terabyte!
Attack Hope!
Dodge!
Duh! Of course I'll dodge it!
I activate Hope's effect!
I use an Overlay Unit to negate a Monster's attack!
He did it!
That's no good!
He just used all of Hope's Overlay Units!
So Yuma-kun can't block any more attacks!
I set one card in reverse, ending my turn!
His set card...
It would appear that the next turn will bring this match to a close!
My turn! Draw!
Terabyte's got 2900 Attack Points.
If I don't beat Sensei this turn, Hope's a goner!
Let me give you a warning.
I may be wrong, but I think using Zubaba Knight and Achacha Archer to Exceed Summon Revise Dragon would be a good idea.
Oh yeah! I have another Numbers!
I Summon Zubaba Knight!
I'm gonna bring it to you!
I Overlay the Level Three Zubaba Knight and Achacha Archer!
I construct the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Exceed Summon!
Come out, Numbers 17!
Revise Dragon!
A second Numbers, is it?
But you seem to have forgotten about Super Bugman's effect.
As long as Super Bugman remains on the field,
the Attack Power and Defense Power of all Attack Position Monsters on the field are switched.
Revise Dragon's Defense Power is zero!
So its Attack Power is now zero!
I went through the trouble of Summoning Revise Dragon, too!
It's because you had to go and open your big mouth!
You just had to go and butt in before!
If you hadn't told me to dodge before...
Dodge!
No way this guy would tell me to do something so stupid...
It means if you tell me to move my right hand, I'll just move my left!
You can't mean you...! On purpose?!
Yuma, activate Thunder Shot from your hand.
If you do, your victory is set.
This is not a lie.
If you do not, I will be obliterated from this world.
I activate the Thunder Shot Magic Card from my hand!
This card damages my opponent by 500 points for each Monster they control on the field!
That's 1000 points of damage!
What useless struggling!
I will once again activate Damage Vaccine OmegaΩ MAX!
This card recovers my Life by the amount of damage I lost.
That was totally pointless!
Yuma, use your Trap Card.
My Trap Card?
Bingo!
I activate the Trap Card, Excessive Insecurity!
Wha-What?!
When my opponent recovers his Life,
one of the Monsters my opponent controls is destroyed!
And I'll be destroying Super Bugman!
Smart! So that means, in summary, Super Bugman's effect disappears,
and the Monsters whose Attack and Defense were switched are returned to normal!
Dammit!
Terabyte has zero Attack Points!
Go, Revise Dragon!
Attack Terabyte!
And I Direct Attack with Aspiring Hero - Hope!
GO!
Hope Sword Slash!!
He did it! Yuma won!
What a brilliant victorious turnaround!
I won, WON!
I BROUGHT IT TO 'IM!
You managed to win somehow.
But how'd you know Sensei was gonna try to recover his Life?
Because he was seeking perfection.
So he was naturally playing his Dueling at the utmost perfection.
I decided to bet on the high chance that he would try to recover the damage he lost from Thunder Shot.
This is another of the cards holding my scattered memories...
Numbers 34...
A piece of my memory.
My name is Astral.
And the place I come from...
...is the Astral World.
I came to this world...
Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei!!
Wh-What was I doing?
Sensei, you have to hurry up and stop the virus bomb!
Virus bomb?
It's no use. I can't stop it.
I don't have the deactivation switch.
Say what?!
That means the city...!
You're way too persistent!
Way to go me!
The timer didn't stop...
3...
2...
1...
The city's about to go into a huge panic!
It's all over!
What's all this about a "huge panic"?
But Sensei, didn't you hack the city's computers to try and plunge the city into a state of mass panic?!
Why would I do something so terrifying?
Nothing happened...
I confess to causing a bit of trouble for the city while making preparations...
S-So...
You weren't making a virus bomb?
Okay, it's ready.
It's perfect.
Kids, try looking into the sky with your D-Gazers on.
Look at the sky with our D-Gazers on?
Is that Bugman?!
A GIANT BUGMAN!
I came to realize.
Coincidently, the night view in this city happens to make up the matrix code.
So it responds with our D-Gazers and materializes Bugman!
But the code was incomplete.
Because of the light in that building down there.
So the perfection you were talking about was putting light on that building?!
Sure was.
Sensei~
Here, Yuma-kun.
This is... the Bugman card?
Read it over.
It's Bugman!
Cute~!
Bugman!
We didn't make it in time, but nothing happened...
"Bugman...
An electrical fairy that lives off of the other bugs.
It becomes extremely powerful because it lives off its bug friends.
It's said that those who witness its full moon-like appearance may forever live in happiness."
In summary, Sensei just wanted all of us to live forever in happiness.
Observation number seven...
"My memory pieces, the Numbers cards...
They grow the desire and darkness that dwells inside those they come into contact with."
I'll be sure to remember that.
Let's begin the Duel!
Here's this week's question!
When a Monster is placed in Attack Mode, it's in an offensive stance.
So, how about when it's in Defense Mode?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
EH?! You're gonna give me an Exceed Monster?!
You can't!
The guy's obviously after something!
Tokunosuke ain't like that!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Read The Opposite Side Duel... NOT!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Defense Mode means going into a defensive stance!
In Dueling, whether the Monster is in Attack or Defense Mode is a very important point to keep in mind!