Wait, Yuma. It’s dangerous!
It's fine! It's fine! We're just passing through.
Forget passing through. We should just go the other way!
Gosh!
Write it off as a shortcut all you want, but we can’t walk around on a construction site!
Yuma, what exactly do you use a construction site for?
You don’t even know that?
Um, er... well, you see...
It's obviously a place for people to work!
Yuma! C'mon, let’s go back.
Get over here already!
Kotori!
Why is it chasing us?!
Jump!
Are you alright, Kotori?
Yeah...
Wh-What the heck was that? N-No one's driving it!
No way!
Damn you!
Not even wearing safety helmets!
Not to mention walking around on a construction site!
Darn, looks like it won’t stop if my foot is unable to reach brake, damn you.
T-The driver is an Elementary School student?!
What?! An Elementary School student?!
I'm Shobee Yuatsu! I'm a Middle schooler! Damn you!
Oh… So you're same as us.
I'm Kotori Mizuki. This is Yuma.
Thank you for saving us, Shobee-kun.
I-It was nothing, god darn it!
What a huge truck.
That thing can still move even it carries 300 tons of grout at once.
Wow, 300 at once?! Impressive!
Uh…no. Not that.
Oh, this is the 750-ton class crane. It can easily handle a rocket.
Really?! That's awesome!
There are hexagonal parts over there as well.
I guess every structure here is connected by those tin parts.
When you think about it all, it's really incredible!
So you get it? I guess you do get it!
Boys really love these kinds of things, don’t they?
I really want to try operating that thing!
I know, right! Don't you just?!
Nonetheless, this is why I decided to participate in the Duel Carnival.
In Dueling, even a short guy like me is able to control heavy-class cranes,
and all those machine Monsters I’ve dreamed of.
You know, it's always something I've wanted to do.
I think I can understand how you feel.
Huh? You're in Duel Carnival too?
Yep!
Alright, let's make it clear that you won't win against my almighty Construction Equipment Deck!
My deck has considerable power as well!
Alright, then let’s have a match!
Sure. Let's Duel!
Here goes!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel Target: Locked on!
Duel!!
The World Duel Carnival has attracted the strongest Duelists from all over the world!
In order to pass through the preliminaries, you need five Heart Pieces!
I currently have two Heart Pieces.
Let’s go to finals with this momentum! I'm definitely winning this!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
I go first!
"Number 28: Construction Site Duel!
Destroy Construction Equipment Deck!"
It's my turn! Draw!
I summon Drilling Construction Equipment: Drill Jumbo!!
Next I activate the Magic Card Top-Speed Construction!
When a "Construction Equipment" Monster is summoned this turn,
this card lets me Special Summon a "Construction Equipment" Monster from my hand in Defense mode.
So now I Special Summon Grading Construction Equipment: Road Roller in Defense mode!
And now Drill Jumbo's Monster effect activates!
It gains 300 Attack power for every "Construction Equipment" Monster on the field.
Woo-hoo! Construction Equipment Monsters are so cool!!
Is this really the time to be saying that?
Your opponent has already summoned two Monsters.
Wha-
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Now, feel the power of my Construction Equipment Deck!
It's my turn!
Draw!
I summon Gagaga Magician!
I'm counting on you, Gagaga Magician!
Yuma, your opponent has two Monsters. One with 2100 Attack and the other with 2100 Defense.
I question why you summoned Gagaga Magician when it only has 1500 attack.
Ahh! Right!
I dun goofed.
Use your Equipment Magic.
Oh, yeah yeah.
I activate from my hand the Equipment Magic Bound Wand!
Bound Wand lets the equipped Monster gain 100 Attack points for each of its Levels.
But it still has 1900 Attack.
You'll need a better power up than that to scare me!
Yuma.
Gagaga Magician has an effect that makes it change it's Level to anything between 1 and 8.
O-oh, that's right!
I activate Gagaga Magician's effect!
I change it's Level from 4 to 8, gaining 400 Attack points in the progress.
And thanks to Bound Wand's effect, its Attack becomes 2300.
Well, aren't you something, damn you!
Gagaga Magician attacks Drill Jumbo!
Nice one, but I activate my trap.
A Hot-Blooded Man’s Red Soul!
When a Machine-type Monster I control battles,
this card reduces my opponent's Monster's Attack power by 1000 points!
What?
Be gone!
Yuma!
Use Bound Wand's effect!
Alright, already!
When the Monster equipped with Bound Wand is destroyed,
it ends the battle and Special Summons the Monster.
But the situation has not changed.
Defend.
When a Monster in Defense mode is destroyed, the Player receives no damage.
I got ya!
I Special Summon Gagaga Magician in Defense mode.
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
You think defending will work?
It's my turn! Draw!
I summon Construction Equipment: Strong Shovel!
Now that's there's another "Construction Equipment" Monster on the field, Drill Jumbo gains another 300 Attack points.
I use Strong Shovel to attack Gagaga Magician!
Yuma!
I activate the Trap card Half Unbreak!
Half Unbreak prevents my Monster from being destroyed by Battle.
And the damage the player received in battle is halved.
To finish, Gagaga Magician is now in Defense mode!
So this means that your Monster is safe for this turn?
But that won't last against my Construction Equipment Deck!
Still, Half Unbreak is in effect!
I use Drill Jumbo to attack Gagaga Magician!
Drill Jumbo's Monster effect activates!
When Drill Jumbo attacks a Monster in Defense mode,
If it's Attack power exceeds it's Defense power,
then you take damage to your Life!
You liked that? High Output, High Horsepower!
My Construction Equipment Deck with it's high potential is known for its great durability!
Huh? It's in Defense mode now?
Well, it's this.
When Drill Jumbo attacks, it switches to Defense mode until the end of my next turn.
I can't change it.
Goddammit!
So it's in sleep mode?
W-when Construction Equipment reach their maximum power,
they need maintenance.
You never know when the engine'll malfunction.
Which means you have a chance, Yuma.
Yeah.
It's my turn! Draw!
Now for an all-out attack!
I switch Gagaga Magician to Attack mode!
Next I summon Puripriest!
Once per turn, by making Puripriest's attack zero,
I can increase a Monster's attack or my Life by 800 points!
So now I activate Puripriest's effect,
and raise Gagaga Magician's Attack power by 800 points!
What?
Gagaga Magician attacks Strong Shovel!
I set a card face-down!
I end my turn!
Gagaga Magician and Puripriest's Attack power return to normal.
Like I'll lose to the Construction Equipment's power.
Duels ain't all about power!
I see.
Then what else is there besides power?
Uhh, well, you see, uhh, that!
That?
It's just not all about power!!
What was that?
How can you win without power?!
The one with more power wins!
S-Shobee.
When I was still in Elementary School,
everyone in class mocked me because I was such a wimp back then.
Dammit, gimme a break here!
Even if I got more power...
It was then I discovered the Construction Equipment.
Then I realized,
No one will dare to bully me,
with the Construction Equipment's power.
I'm gonna use the Construction Equipment Monsters to win the Duel Carnival!
Shobee...
Shobee-kun...
It's my turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic card Scrap and Build.
This card lets me summon a Level-3 or lower Machine-type Monster from the Cemetery.
Revive, Strong Shovel!
It's Level is increased by one when Special Summoned from the Cemetery.
And now I activate the Magic card Overhaul!
Overhaul increases the Level of all Machine-type Monsters on my field by one!
Now see this ultra-gigantic power!
Here it comes, Yuma!
I Overlay my Level 5 Drill Jumbo, Road Roller and Strong Shovel.
I construct the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
The mecha arm which can destroy rocks!
Come forth, my Xyz Monster!
Construction Equipment Lord: Doboku Zaaku!!
3200 Attack power?
So freakin' huge!
This is my great Xyz Monster!
Construction Equipment Lord: Doboku Zaaku!!
Be careful, Yuma.
Yeah.
I activate Doboku Zaaku's Monster effect.
By detaching an Overlay Unit, Doboku Zaaku can send the top three cards from my opponent's Deck to the Cemetery.
The cards from my Deck!
And this effect destroys cards on my opponent's field equal to the number of Monsters that were sent!
What?!
He sent two Monsters to the Cemetery!
So I now destroy your two Monsters!
Take this! Full-Horsepower Crusher!
Yuma's Monsters are gone...
Now I'll lose if I'm hit with a direct attack!
Calm down, Yuma!
--Now-
--Now then, Doboku Zaaku!!
Full Throttle!
What? So noisy!!
-rap!
Eh? What was that?
I can't hear you!
More!!
Let your engine roar, Doboku Zaaku!!
Wipe out all of Yuma's Life!
-rap! U- ou- ap-!!
Do a rap? Why should I rap?
Go!!
Ultimate Machine Impact!!
Your trap! Trap card!!
You mean Trap!!
I activate the Trap card Tiny Resistance!
Tiny Resistance can select one Level 4 or lower monster with less than 1000 Attack in my Graveyard.
During this turn, one of my opponent’s monsters will lose of its Attack equal to the selected monster’s Attack Power!
Help me out, Puripriest!
Reduce Doboku Zaaku's Attack Power!
Yuma!!
Had enough of my super awesome power?
With that I end my turn!
I slipped past that, but I only have 100 Life left.
And I still have that 3200 Attack power Monster to deal with.
Yuma, look at that.
That M-.....
...rt
What? I can't hear you!
Damn, I guess it's the end...
So you assume that yourself.
What was that?
Huh? Hey, how come I can hear you now?
I've always been able to talk to you through your heart.
Oh yeah!
I have been observing various things inside this "construction site".
And I realized that even the highest man-made buildings,
were assembled by various small pieces.
And what about it?
Look at the hexagonal part at your feet.
It's just a nut.
That hexagonal part, though small, supports the entire building.
Dueling is the same.
Small parts supporting huge buildings...
So it ain't all about power.
What's wrong, Yuma?
Feeling helpless against my super power, my Doboku Zaaku?!
It's my turn! Draw!!
Yeah, it's here!!
I summon Kuribolt!
300 Attack?
What are you gonna do with such a low-class Monster?
I activate Kuribolt's Monster effect!
Doboku Zaaku's Overlay Units!
This effect turns Overlay Units into Kuribolt Tokens.
W-what?
Turns Overlay Units into Monsters?
Damn you!
Even with three of them, they're still no match for Doboku Zaaku!
I activate the Magic card, Minimum Guts!!
Go, Kuribolt Token!!
What do you really plan with those little Monsters?
W-what's wrong, Doboku Zaaku?!
The Magic card, Minimum Guts allows you to reduce your Monster's attack power to zero,
by releasing two Level 1 Monsters.
Doboku Zaaku...
But how could some weak Monster...
Finish it, Yuma!
Yeah! I'm gonna bring it to 'em!!
I use Kuribolt to attack Doboku Zaaku!!
Damn you!!
And due to Minimum Guts' effect, the Attack Power of your destroyed Doboku Zaaku...
will be inflicted to you, Shobee, all 3200 points of damage!
Here's punishment from the power you had pride in!!
Alright!!
But why?
Why did I lose to such weak Monsters...
Don't underestimate small power!
Small power?
Every skyscraper and building are all supported by these bolts.
Well, I lost.
So you take my Heart Piece, damn you.
Yeah, I did earn it.
So that makes three.
You got a point.
I forgot one very important thing.
You don't need huge power to build huge things.
Shobee-kun, you may be small, but you're cool!
Wut?
No, no way!
Small power, huh?
The hell?!
The hell are you guys doin' here?!
What'll happen if y'all got hurt?!
S-sorry!!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
I got assaulted by some stranger during the Duel Carnival!
Now she's chasing me non-stop!
Next time, Yu-Gi-Oh ZEXAL:
The Railroad Deck Departs! The Runaway Duelist Anna
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!!
The Number Popularity Contest's Top Three!!
So in third place!
Numbers 17: Leviath Dragon!
I knew it, that dragon's so cool!!
In second!
Numbers 83: Galaxy Queen!
She's got one protective effect!
And in first place!
Chaos Numbers 39: Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!!
Let's go! Hope King Chaos Slash!!
Thanks for voting everybody!!