To save Tokunosuke, I started a Duel
against both Droite and Gauche at the same time!
But for for some reason, Astral isn't showing himself.
Their attacks are coming one after the other!
This is bad! At this rate, I'll...
Gagaga Gardna!
There's no point in trying to defend your Monster when you have no cards in your hand!
No cards in my hand?
That's right!
I activate the effect of Tasuke Knight in my Graveyard!
If this card is in my Graveyard while my Monster is attacked when I have no cards in my hand...
...I can Special Summon this card and end the battle this turn!
What did you say!?
The Monster's attack was stopped!
I managed to make it...
What a persistent bastard!
Alright, it's my turn.
I have two Level Four Monsters on my field.
If I can just manage to Summon Hope...
Astral!?
Now, it's your turn!
If he's not here, I can't call out Hope!
Yuma!
Where the hell are you looking?!
Be gone, Astral!
Yuma...
Hope!
Go back to Yuma! He needs you!
You think I'll just let you run away?!
Hope!
Even if Hope isn't here...
My turn! Draw!
This card can't defeat their Monsters!
I attack Phantom Butterfly Assassin Morpho with Tasuke Knight!
Hell Push!
Only 500 points?
That ain't enough spirit to beat us!
Hope!
Go to Hell!
What's the matter, kid?
Hurry up and end your turn!
Yuma...
I'll put an end to this.
Damn it!
I set a card face-down...
W-What!?
T-This is...
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Why just Hope?
Astral... Are you here, Astral?
Astral, did something happen to you?
So he got away, huh?
But Astral...
Now the only one who could defend you has left.
The stupid fool left all so he could help out some lowly human.
Now, come to me, Numbers!
I will absorb all of you myself!
The Numbers!
Now all of them are under my control!
And you're next, Astral.
It's your turn!
Wh-What was the deal with that light just now?
Something isn't right here.
Be careful, Gauche!
It looks like the Hope card has returned!
Astral...
Are you off fighting somewhere or something?
Thats why you sent him to me alone...?
If that's the case, I won't let your feelings go to waste!
I'll bring it to em!
I Overlay the Level Four Gagaga Gardna and Tasuke Knight!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Number 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
It's Hope!
He did it!
N-No way!
A Number?!
That kid has a Number!?
Number 39!?
Hope, endure it!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
A Number...?
This thing's become far more interesting!
Calm down, Gauche!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Moonlit Papillon!
Wait, Droite!
I already told you he's mine!
I can't allow that!
Now that we know he possesses a Number, this has become a Duel for Mr. Heartland!
You're such a killjoy!
I Overlay the Level Four Phantom Butterfly Assassin Swallowtail and Moonlit Papillon!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Photon Butterfly Assassin!
Photon!?
I've never seen such a Monster.
This Monster is...
...the same type of Monsters Kaito used!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Number 38: Connect the Hope Together!
Hope Sword Mars Slash!!"
What? Photon Monsters just like Kaito?
Did you say Kaito?!
How do you know Kaito?
Just give it up!
Running away is useless!
I will force you to remember our mission.
Why are you asking?!
It's obvious that I Dueled him!
It was quite a tiring match, too.
What!?
You fought Kaito on even ground?!
Why did Kaito fight this kid?
Could it be...
What Mr. Heartland told us about...?
That Original Number who came to this world from the Astral World?
Hey! Are you telling me this kid has the Original with him?!
If not, how can you explain someone like him fighting Kaito evenly?
So that's the mood, is it?
Since you seem to know the Original...
Kid, I'll be taking that Number back!
Let's begin the Number hunting!
Photon Butterfly Assassin's Monster Effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it switches a Defense Mode Monster into Attack Mode,
and its Attack Power goes down by 600!
Hope is in Attack Mode!?
Regardless of whether you have the spirit to fortify your defense, it won't work against us!
Then I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Berserk Scales!
This raises the Attack Power of one Monster by 1000 points until the end of this turn!
An Attack Power of 3100!?
Now the difference in their Attack Power is 1200 points.
Even if the Number won't be destroyed, you'll still take damage!
Which means, once I take this attack...
Go, Photon Butterfly Assassin!
Attack Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Butterfly Distortion!
Yuma!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope's Monster Effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it negates one Monster's attack!
Moon Barrier!
I'm saved!
With this I end my turn.
The Monster that has used Berserk Scales' effect has its Attack Power returned to normal with 1000 more points decreased.
But by doing this, we now know Aspiring Emperor - Hope's effect.
Gauche!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Allow me to show you some real spirit!
My turn! Draw!
I release the Level Four Blade Bouncer to Advance Summon the Level Six Phantom Bouncer!
Two Level Six Monsters!?
I Overlay the Level Six Hammer Rush Bouncer and Phantom Bouncer!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Photon Streak Bouncer!
An Attack Power of 2700!?
Now it's over!
Photon Streak Bouncer attacks Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Take this! Streak Strike!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope's Monster Effect activates!
Moon Barrier!
You fell for it!
What!?
Photon Streak Bouncer's effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it negates the opponent's Xyz Monster's effect and deals 1000 points of damage!
So he wanted me to use Hope's effect for this!?
So instead of you taking 800 points, you'll take an additional 1000 points on top of it!
This is over!
Yuma?
Now I've got you, Astral.
You're done for.
Go, Photon Streak Bouncer!
Streak Break!!
Trap activate! Damage Diet!
It halves all damage done to me during this turn!
Yuma!
Not done yet! Since Hope's effect has been negated, the battle resumes!
Do it, Photon Streak Bouncer!
Yuma's about to lose!
Now the Original Number belongs to me!
Trap, activate! Half Unbreak!
The Monster that has used this effect can't be destroyed by battle this turn!
And the damage to the player is halved!
So you managed to withstand it.
But now Hope's Overlay Units and your set cards are gone.
Stand up.
Then surrender and hand us your Number.
If you do that, you'll no longer have to suffer.
Stop kidding me!
As if I'm gonna surrender to people like you!
Y-Yuma...
That's right.
If I lose this Duel, I'm not the only one affected. He'll disappear!
I won't let such a thing happen!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Card Car D!
By releasing this card during the turn the card is Summoned,
I can draw two cards from my deck!
Please give me some cards to turn the tables!
Double Up Chance and Bi-Tension?
These cards are...
No, think about it...
Just think. There has to be a way.
There's gotta be a chance here...
Something...!
What's wrong!?
My, my. So he finally gave up?
Yuma...
So he gave up?
Guess I'll finish you off as well.
Yuma...
It's useless...
Astral... I'm...
Don't give up!
This isn't how you Duel, Yuma!
That's right!
No matter how much you failed, no matter how much you were laughed at... You never gave up, Yuma!
Don't give up until the very end!
Bring it to em'!
Kotori... Tokunosuke...
That's right, huh? The match isn't over yet.
I can't let myself give up!
I'll win no matter what it takes!
I'll bring it to em'!
Yuma, I can feel it.
You're bringing it to em'!
What is this?
My body's been paralyzed!
This is Yuma and I's...
It's the power of our bonds!
Bonds, you say!?
Yuma...!
You're... Astral!
I've kept you waiting.
What is that?
Astral!
It's Astral!
I see! He's The Original!
It's not like I needed you or anything!
I could've beaten those guys by myself!
And you just had to vanish when I needed to feel your presence!
You went off somewhere!
Both of them against Yuma...
The pieces to victory are gathered!
Your battle wasn't useless.
Astral...
Yuma... Let's win.
Right!
Here I go! First I activate the effect of Overlay Eater in the Graveyard!
I activate the effect of Overlay Eater in my Graveyard!
Overlay Eater?
He sent it to the Graveyard to activate the effect of Gagaga Gardna before!
I Banish this card in my Graveyard from the game!
It absorbs one of the opponent's Xyz Monster's Overlay Units,
and makes it my own Xyz Monster's Overlay Unit!
Now Photon Streak Bouncer's effect has been stopped!
Even if you're that fired up, it's way too late!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope, attack Photon Butterfly Assassin!
Even so, it's only 800 points of damage!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope's Monster Effect activates!
It negates one Monster's attack!
Negating your own attack!?
From my hand, I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Double Up Chance!
If a Monster's attack was negated, that Monster can attack once more with its Attack Power doubled!
Hope's Attack Power doubled!
But it's still not enough.
Then, from my hand I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Bi-Tension!
If a Monster attacks more than once, its Attack Power is doubled once more!
7600 Attack Points?!
What!?
Let's go, Yuma!
Right!
Hope Sword Mars Slash!!
Trap, activate! Bouncer Guard!
It switches a Monster's Attack Target to a Monster with "Bouncer" in its name!
You did it!
He won, Yuma won!
That was amazing!
In that situation, he managed to do a counter-attack!
Astral really is a Dueling genius after all!
Listen, you...
Why did you defend me?
Heh, why?
I was just in the mood to.
Am I wrong?
But Astral really is something else.
Hey kid!
As promised, we'll forget about your cheating friend.
But you better remember that I'm gonna beat you next time!
Along with the Original Number!
Interesting! I'll be your opponent anytime!
I like that spirit of yours.
Well, what's done is done.
The rest is gonna be a breeze for me!
Found you!
How dare you trick us!
Return my Heart Piece!
Hold it right there!
Let's go, everyone!
That was really harsh!
G-Gone!
My Heart Pieces... are gone!
Droite, don't report what happened today to Mr. Heartland!
What?
I'll defeat that Original!
Before Kaito does!
Fine then...
It's gone...
Please let him have dropped my Heart Piece somewhere!
Cleaning, Cleaning...
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Some dogs appeared out of nowhere and stole my Heart Pieces!
If I don't get 'em back, I'll be disqualified from the Duel Carnival!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Fated Showdown! Cat-chan VS Dog-chan"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!