Yuma...
C'mon, Yuma!
Gonna bring it...
Geez!
What's your problem?!
Class ended a while ago.
Oh, really?
Goodness...
Sweet! It's "Bring it to 'em" time!
And don’t forget to check out the notification via mails that the teacher sent to the parents!
What notification?
Geez, this Saturday is parents’ day!
Yo, Kotori, which of your parents's are showing up for parents’ day?
Uhh... oh, I'm sorry, Yuma.
Never mind... never mind!
There's no need to make a big fuss about it.
I don’t mind.
On Saturday then...
That parent's day really is annoying.
Yuma, what is parents’ day?
Our parents will come to school to see our lecture,
in order to see how we do in studying.
But both of your parents...
That’s okay. As long as a relative shows up, it’s all good.
I still have my grandma and older sister!
I'm home!
Huh?
Grandma, I'm home!
Oh, welcome back!
U- umm...
What do you think of this Kimono?
I have a class reunion this Saturday...
...then I will be wearing this.
Saturday...?
I wonder if Tome-san and Okiku-san are doing well...
...and what about my first love Gochizu-san?
Sis!
No way, I already gave you money.
No, it’s NOT that!
Then what is it?
I'm busy uploading the news.
Ah, Tetsuko! Huh?
Ahh! I totally forgot the class reunion... is this Saturday?
Yeah, I'll definitely go!
I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone!
Hm? Huh? Yuma?
Morning, Kotori!
Morning!
Who will come for today’s parents’ day?!
My mom.
My papa insisted that he will go...
What a coincidence, same with me.
My dad will come as well!
Today we have PE?
Jumping blocks if I remember right?
Right, so we all can watch Tsukumo-kun 'bringin' it to em', right?
My dad said he wants to see it too...!
Shoot! I'm late, I'm late!
Geez, what are you doing!
S-Sis?!
Why are you staring at me?
It seems nice dressing does help. There is no doubt about it.
Huh? Granny, you look pretty as well!
Is that so?
I guess my heart is still as young as a maiden...
Hey, Yuma!?
Today is Saturday, why are you still going to school?
Emm... I guess...
Don’t tell me that you're going to make up your lessons!?
It’s not like that! I'm going!
Hey!
Geez... Hurry up and change the light!
Yuma, why didn't you tell them about the parents’ day?
Because I didn't want to bother them...
Sis and granny are looking forward to today so much!
Is that so?
Yeah! Plus... I'm no longer a kid!
I don’t need to have my family visting my lecture every single time.
Good, looks like I can still make it!
I'll bring it to...
No-...No-... gone... it's gone... it's gone, it's gone!
What’s wrong?
It’s not here! I lost the Emperor’s Key!
Wha- what?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Yuma, did you really lose it?
"Numbers 19:
The Promised "Bring It To 'Em"
If it’s true, then you must find it!
That key is very important to me!
You are so annoying, I know!
That is the treasure my dad left me.
From your father?
The key was previously held by Yuma’s father, and that thing is inside of it.
Does this mean... that there is some connection between his father and me?!
Yuma!
Hm?
What kind of person is your father?!
My dad?
Oh, I guess he was a strange person...
He absolutely hates the word “boring"
Most important of all, my dad is the one who taught me how to 'bring it to 'em'!
What’s wrong, Yuma!
Come on, get up, Yuma!
It’s impossible! I can't climb any higher!
'Bring it to 'em!', Yuma!
Geez, that’s absolutely unfair!
Dad only bought Yuma along with him!
He did mention something like “men’s talk”...
What does that mean?
How stupid!
I wish I were a boy sometimes...
Then how about we just forget about those stubborn men for a moment...
...and us girls will make something delicious today?
Really, mom?
Great! I love mom the most!
Then how about some Italian dishes!
Hey Akari, you haven’t put on your shoes!
The sun has set.
What’s wrong?
Something happened in school?
Are you a fool?
How can you duel with those half-baked skills?
Shut up! I will become the duel champion!
I already said it’s impossible!
I will definitely, definitely become the duel champion!!
Nothing really...
Really?
Just...
Just?
I... don’t wanna go to school anymore.
Why?
Because... school is boring...
Yuma...
Yuma, do you know about the multi-dimension world?
What's that?
Although it looks like there is only one world...
...this universe actually made of different integrated worlds.
This world is made of 2 worlds connected  together.
One of them is a world full of Hope.
and the other one has no hope, a boring world without anything.
Somehow these 2 worlds are connected to each other.
Really, is that true?
That’s right.
This side is the hopeful world which full of adventures and romance.
All kinds of challenges are waiting here for you.
But right now... you are staying inside the boring world.
As long as you are still inside that boring world,...
... you will only have negative thoughts about everything.
Then how can I get to the another world?
That’s easy!
Just keep your goals in your heart and stay determined.
Goals?
Anything!!
For example, do something good every day,
or even say that you want to become a champion fast!
Fast, huh...
Yuma, what is your goal?
My... my goal... my goal is...
to become the duel champion one day.
That’s a great goal you got.
But every time I say that, people laugh at me and treat me like a stupid kid.
You don’t have to worry about that.
You think so?
If you do, you won't get any closer to your goal.
If you go for your goals with confidence, you won't even have time to notice these people.
Your challenge will be continuous.
Say goodbye to the thoughts of this “boring world”.
Then you can definitely find the world full of hope!
Yuma, challenge yourself endlessly.
Then your heart will always stay excited.
Alright, let's duel!
let daddy teach ya something!
Umm - here?
Looks fine to me!
And tomorrow we will continue to climb and duel again!
Duel champion...
Yes... I bet my dad believed that I could become one someday, for sure.
So if I give up half way, it's same as me betraying my dad.
Here it comes, Yuma!
I overlay my LV 4 Gogogo Golem and Ganbara Knight!
And construct overlay network with these two monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Whoops, there aren't any Xyz monsters in my deck!
Dad!
Dad?
What?
Dad, what is your goal?
Mine?
My goal is simply reach the end of the world!
What’s so funny about that?
Because - you know - what do you mean world’s end?
Are you stupid, dad?
Earth is round, how can there be an end!
Actually...you're right.
Geez, dad!
But when I recall that moment now... I might've been the one who was wrong.
What do you mean?
My dad only once talked to me about...
...the “world’s end”.
What was that...just now?
Darling!
Mirai..
Kazuma! No!
Don’t give up hope!
Preserve my hope!
My hope is, that you survive!
I'll...be back.
Kazuma!
KAZUMA!
Maybe dad saw something at that time
Where am I?
Don’t tell me...
... that this is world’s end?
A week after the incident, dad was rescued miraculously.
Dad!
Father!
It’s nothing, don’t worry about it.
Okay...
Father! I'm so glad... I'm really glad...
I'm sure...
... he must have seen something.
What do you think, he saw?
The world’s end.
The world’s... end?
My dad said there are many other worlds besides this world.
My dad definitely saw something back then, something that connects this world and the other worlds.
The connection between this world and the different world,
don’t tell me that’s the power of Emperor’s Key?
That’s right!
Back then I...
I activate the Magic card, Fire Soul!
Now it’s my win!
You can never become a Duel Champion!
Shut up! I can definitely be one.
Then try to beat me for once and I'll believe you.
That’s right, that’s right!
Yeah, is it too tough for a little kid?
Because he's just a little kid!
I... I will...
'Bring it to 'em!
Dad!
'Bring it to 'em, Yuma!
Bring it...?
''Bring it to 'em" means challenging with,
a heart that will never give up!
Move forward, Yuma!
That Emperor’s Key will give you power!
Emperor’s Key...
That’s right, I'll never give up!
I'll bring it to 'em!
That’s it about my dad...
He did say he would teach me dueling though...
In conclusion -
How breath-taking~ura!
There is nothing like the mature beauty of Mizuki-san!
This must be Kotori's hidden side~ura!
I get it, mom!
DNA as well can be ...
... terror ~ura
Yuma-kun still isn't here?
Yuma...
In the end we had to go back home.
But it was all worth it!
Oh! I found it! The Emperor’s Key!
Dad - Mom, I'll be back soon.
We haven't met in a long time!
Haru-san, it’s so nice to see you're so well!
You are welcome...
I believe my Kotori and Yuma are classmates, aren't they?
That’s true, Kotori often plays at my house.
Right, thank you so much for caring!
Yone-san, how about you come over for a bit as well?
I did buy some very good tea recently!
So...
what are we talking about again?
Indeed it’s about Yuma and Kotori....
Right, aren't they classmates now?
Kotori-chan often comes to my house to play.
Right, thank you so much for caring!
What were we talking about again?
Tetsuko, long time no see!
It’s been a long time!
Yuma always give Tetsuo plenty of trouble.
It’s Tetsuo who gives you guys trouble!
Are you quite busy?
I guess...
To be a free reporter is very tough!
So Haru-san is the one who went to school?
Eh?
Isn’t today the parents’ day?
...Tetsuo told me so.
He...
WWhat’s the matter?
Sorry, I got an emergency!
Akari!?
He...
... must've thought about our feelings.
Dad...
Akari.
Wha- what’s up with that serious face all of sudden?
You have to watch over Yuma’s duels...
One day, his duels will trigger something big...
Eh? What do you mean?
You'll understand one day.
Why is it all Yuma-this, Yuma-that!
Akari, you're the big sister, so it can’t be helped.
What are you talking about?
As his older sister, you'll have to spend more time with him....
Yuma will have to rely on you more.
One day, we will have to leave you two.
Geez, I don’t get it, sounds like I'm on the losing side!
Yuma!
Eh... um... uh...
Hurry up to your seat.
I'm sorry...
Up next is Mizuki and the class representative.
Yes!
Do your best, Takashi!
Kotori-chan FIGHT!!
In conclusion, I will do my best!
In the end no one from Yuma’s family is here.
Yuma...
Yuma!
Sis and grandma, why are you guys...?
Why didn't you tell us about this?
That’s right, do you honestly think we would be happy leaving you alone?
Sis, grandma...
Yuma, "bring it to 'em", right?
Go!
Yeah!
Alright, I'll challenge 20 jumping blocks at once!
What’s wrong, Yuma?!
They're watching us...
Dad... mom...!
I see. Feels like they can see me too..
Go, Yuma! - Good luck!
Yuma might be able to jump over that today!
That’s right!
Do your best, Yuma!
Observation #14: "Yuma, it looks like you are loved by all."
Go, Yuma!
Sure!
I'll bring it to 'em!
A Big Announcement for everyone who is watching this show!
The First Monster Popularity Voting begins!
Decide who is number one among these 13 monsters!
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!