The World Duel Carnival has finally started!
A Duel Champion will be named here in Heartland City among Duelists from all around the world in a fierce battle!
And naturally, that winner's gonna be me!
Here goes! I'm gonna bring it-
Who the heck're you?!
Okay! This ball has chosen you!
Let's Duel!
The heck's with that ball?
This is my partner.
This ball's perplexity allows for good quality lifts
and it's always able to think up strategies for my deck!
A ball of cards?
Fight me with the Heart Piece on the line!
Alright, I'm looking forward to it!
I'll take you on!
I'm Yuma Tsukumo, and you are?
It's Kakeru Kunitachi!
Kakeru Kunitachi?
You know him?
Where have I heard about him?
It's about to start!
Now, let's kick-off!
Alrght! I'll bring it to em'!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR vision - link established.
-Duel!!
I'll have the first move!
My turn, draw!
I set a Monster in Reverse Defense Mode and end my turn!
You've set Gogogo Golem.
I was expecting you to Summon a Monster in Attack Mode on first impulse and battle
without stopping to properly gauge your enemy's deck and battle tactics.
Looks like you've improved a bit.
Shut up! Stop lecturing and watch me!
I got no clue as to who you're referring to, but I'll be shutting you up in no time.
I'll show you the strength of my Soccer Deck.
Here I go!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Field Magic, Dream Pitch!
W-What the hell is this!?
What is this?
C-Cat, I can't believe this!
We suddenly became commentators for a soccer match!
To summarize, this is the effect of the Field Magic, Dream Pitch!
Amazing!
That's not all!
The Field Magic, Dream Pitch can switch a face-down Defense Monster to face-up Defense Mode!
What!?
Then I Summon Captain Wing from my hand!
1100 Attack Points?
An attack like that won't affect Gogogo Golem!
I activate the Magic Card, Killer Pass!
Take this, Captain Wing!
Now for this turn, If Captain Wing fights a Monster with higher Defense Points than his Attack Points,
It's Attack Points are doubled!
Whether it's doubled or tripled, Gogogo Golem has an effect that prevents it from being destroyed once per turn!
Too naive!
Due to Killer Pass, The battled Monster's Monster Effect is negated!
What!?
Go, Captain Wing!
Ultra Bullet Shoot!!
But why? Even if you beat my Defense Mode Monster, my Life Points shouldn't have been damaged!
Captain Wing has an effect that deals damage to the opponent when its Attack Power is higher than the opponent's Defense Power!
Damn it...! This guy might be really strong...!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Hang in there, Yuma!
The Duel has just started!
Fight!!
"Numbers 27: WDC Kick-Off!
Fire Striker Kakeru"
The battle begins now!
Yuma, Bring it to em'!
That's right!
Alright, here I go!
My turn, draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
Go, Gagaga Magician! Attack Captain Wing!
This is good! Gagaga Magician's Attack Power is 1500!
Captain Wing's Attack Power returned back to normal!
It's settled!
Goooaaaal!!
You did it, Yuma!
This goal is canceled!
What, canceled?
Meo-why?
It's a Trap Card!
A Trap?
That's right, I activated the Trap Card, Offside Trap!
An offside?
If a Monster on my field is destroyed,
this card negates the Monster's destruction and all Battle Damage, and the turn is forced to end.
F-Forced to end?
No way!
Observation #15...
"In Soccer, your turn ends very abruptly."
T-This is no time for your observations!
Now then, it's about time I got serious!
My turn, draw!
I Summon Striker Top!
He Summoned a Level Five Monster without release?
That's not even possible!
Since the Field Magic Dream Pitch is activated, I can Summon Striker Top without release!
You gotta be kidding!
Go, Striker Top!
Attack Gagaga Magician!
Now your goal is wide open!
Hit him, Captain Wing! Direct attack!
Yuma!
I can't watch this!
It's not done yet!
I activate the Magic Card, Eye Contact!
With it's effect, I can return one Offside Trap from the Graveyard to my hand!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
What should I do?
If he uses Offside Trap again...
My attack will be negated again and my turn will be forced to end!
Hey, why're you napping?!
I am not napping.
Do you remember anything about soccer?
God, you're so unreliable!
God, what the heck should I do?!
No matter how long you think, it's useless.
You won't find a blind spot in my Soccer Deck!
In other words, you aren't going to win!
Look here!
Those guys are...
They're from the Soccer Representative Team...
The "Giant Strikers"...
Kazuto and Hide!
Why are they here?
That's right, I just remembered!
Kakeru Kunitachi...
To summarize, he's the younger brother of Kazuto and Hide!
That's right... Their dream-like consistent team plays has earned them fame all over the world!
The three sons of the Kunitachi family!
For real?
You're that famous soccer player?
So what!?
I don't care about my older brothers!
"Team play"? What a joke!
The three of us end up getting in each other's way while we try to play at once!
That's why I chose Dueling.
Duels are the best battles!
Because when you're on the field, you're the only person you can trust!
Watch closely!
I'm gonna become Duel Champion with my own strength!
You're wrong about that, Kakeru!
Dueling is also about team plays!
Team plays?
Even now, you aren't alone.
You're out there fighting alongside your friends, aren't you?
My friends?
Right! Captain Wing and Striker Top...
Those Monsters are your friends, aren't they?
I always believe in the Monsters I fight alongside.
Me and my Monsters are a single team!
A team... you said?
Let's do this, Yuma.
It's our turn.
Yup!
Wait, did you remember something about soccer?
I did. And Yuma, you helped me think up a good idea.
Let's win!
We can't afford to lose in a place like this.
You said it!
Okay, let's go!
My turn! Draw!
I...
Summon Zubaba Buster!
I'm the one Summoning it!
I Summon Zubaba Buster!
And use the Resurrection of the Dead Magic Card to Special Summon Gogogo Golem!
Gogogo Golem?
It's a team play, Yuma.
Just trust me.
Well fine...
I'll then activate the Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead!
I Special Summon Gogogo Golem from the Graveyard in Defense Mode!
Summon all the Monsters you want!
You'll never break through my Trap!
If he activates that again...
Use Cross Attack, Yuma.
Activate the Cross Attack Magic Card from your hand.
That's it!
I activate the Magic Card, Cross Attack!
When you have at least two Monsters on your side of the field with the same Attack Power,
you can attack the opponent player directly!
He scored a goal on me...?
Good job! You scored your first goal!
That settles it!
Team Yuma managed to lower Kakeru's Life Points!
Shit! He figured out Offside Trap can't be activated against direct attacks?
This isn't over yet!
When Zubaba Buster damages the opponent during an attack,
it can destroy a Monster on the field with higher Attack Points!
When using this effect, Zubaba Buster's Attack Power falls 500 points...
...but it's well worth it to destroy a Monster.
I can use this!
I then activate the Quick-Play Magic, Runaway Explosion!
When a Monster is destroyed by an effect, the opponent is dealt 500 points of damage!
He finally made it a draw!
He caught up to him!
Good going, Yuma!
Did ya see? That was my team playing!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Let's not get cocky now, Yuma Tsukumo!
Captain Wing was nothing more than a throw-away Monster with 1500 Attack Points!
Destroying that worthless card gains you nothing!
You're still saying stuff like that?
You need to believe in your Monsters, your friends!
Useless guys like them aren't my friends!
Over here!
No way!
What are you doing?
God are you useless!
Just pass the ball to me right away!
That little...
Damn... I'll do it myself!
Over here!
Kakeru, pass to me!
As if I could trust any of you!
I'll settle this myself!
That's Kazuto and Hide's brother?
What a difference compared to his brothers!
I heard he hurt his leg or something. I bet he just sucked from the start.
You okay, Kakeru?
Shut up!
We lost because of you fools!
God! You're all worthless!
You're the worthless one, Kakeru!
Soccer isn't a one man show!
If you can't figure that out, get the hell off this field!
I threw away soccer on that day.
And I swore to myself.
I swore to settle things with my brothers one day.
And I've chosen Dueling to accomplish that goal!
I'll become the best in the world of Dueling!
Be honest with yourself, Kakeru!
You know it deep down, don't you?
You wouldn't have built such a strong Soccer Deck if you didn't, after all.
That's your all-star team right there, bro!
Kakeru, you really love soccer, don't you?
Shut it! I don't care about soccer!
It's fine! Just like what you like!
I like Dueling!
So fight alongside your friends until the very end!
My friends?
Team?
I.... you guys...
I...
My turn! Draw!
I believe in you!
I Summon Defender Libero!
If there's a Dream Pitch on my field, this Monster's level becomes five!
I then activate the Magic Card, Team Play!
C'mon! You actually had a card like that from the start!
This is no time to be happy.
If you have two Monsters on the field with the same level and type,
you can Special Summon one Monster from your Graveyard with the same type.
I'll bring back Captain Wing!
The Monster Special Summoned with this effect increases its level by one!
Now he's got three Level Five Monsters!
That means...!
I Overlay the Level Five Striker Top, Defender Libero, and Captain Wing!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
It's your turn, Fantasista Dieci!
It's got 2600 Attack Points?!
To summarize, he won't make it out if he gets attacked by that!
Go! Attack Zubaba Buster!
Yuma, use your Trap Card!
I'll use Zubaba Buster as a target to activate the Trap Card, Half Unbreak!
Now Zubaba Buster won't be destroyed because of this effect!
Overhead Drive Shoot!!
And Half Unbreak's effect halves the damage the player takes!
Even at the cost of his own Life, for his Monster...
You protected your friend?
But it's not over yet!
I activate Fantasista's effect!
I detach an Overlay Unit so he can attack your Monster with the highest Attack Power again!
Gogogo Golem can't be destroyed in battle once per turn!
Then the second strike will end it!
I detach the final Overlay Unit!
Now for the third attack!
Zubaba Buster's the only one left!
Go, Fantasista!
Overhead Drive Shoot!!
I've still got the effect of Half Unbreak!
Yuma!
You barely made it out of that one.
But you've only got 100 points left.
This ends in the next turn!
I'll end my turn.
Don't you worry, Kotori.
Fighting against such a strong opponent is great! The Duel Carnival is the best!
You still think you can win?
I still have the Offside Trap on my side of the field.
I will win because I'll believe in my friends until the very end!
Here goes!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Girl!
1000 Attack Points?
Why bother playing that Monster?
No, it's a Level Three...
Go, Yuma!
Summon a new Xyz Monster!
Right!
I Overlay the Level Three Zubaba Buster and the Level Three Gagaga Girl!
Combine!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come, "Wandering Guitarist"!
This is my new friend!
Strummin' Fiend Itchy Rhythm!
And I activate the Equipment Magic, Giant King!
I equip it to Itchy Rhythm!
This card's effect prevents the opposing player from activating Magic and Traps until the End Phase of the turn!
Dammit! Now I can't use Offside Trap!
Then, when the Monster equipped with Giant King attacks,
if my Life Points are lower than my opponent's, the opponent's Monster has its Attack Power halved!
Its Attack Power was halved?!
Then I activate the effect of Itchy Rhythm!
I can detach one of its Overlay Units when it battles another Xyz Monster
in order to double its Attack Power!
Take the match, Itchy Rhythm!
GOAL!!
Team Yuma made a complete turnaround in the very last moment!
He did it!
Yuma won!
We won, Yuma.
Yup!
'Coz I had to borrow a bit of your power!
Y-You...
It's been so long since I got so consumed while playing soccer.
Soccer really is fun!
"Soccer" is...?
Ain't it?
Yeah!
I really do love soccer the best!
It was you who brought me back to my senses!
If you feel that way, why don't you come back and give it another shot, Kakeru?
Come back to our field!
Brother!
I think you finally understand what we were trying to tell you back then.
What you told me back then...?
That soccer isn't a one man show?
Right!
Good for you, Kakeru!
Yeah! I need to hurry and catch up to my brothers!
I'm gonna give soccer my all!
Me too! I'm gonna give it my all to become Duel Champion!
This belongs to you.
Yes! I got my first piece!
I'll win my next fight as well!
I don't care who the opponent is! Bring it on!
I'm gonna bring it to you!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
My second opponent in the Duel Carnival is an awesome guy with a tiny body wielding humongous Monsters!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Construction Site Duel! Destroy the Construction-Equipment Deck!!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!