It you approach what is inside this door,
you will obtain a new power.
Zexal!
What?
I WILL BRING IT TO 'EM!
I WILL CONSTRUCT OVERLAY NETWORK WITH MYSELF AND YUMA!
XYZ CHANGE ZEXAL!!!
GO, ZEXAL WEAPON, UNICORN SLASH!
YUMA!!!
Yuma...
Yuma... Tsukumo...
Kaito!
Haruto... Just wait...
One day I'll settle thing with those guys.
I'm late, late, late, LATE!
Wait a sec, Yuma.
What is it? I gotta hurry!
When you came back last night, you were messed up.
You don't have any relation with the destruction of that building last night, now do you?
M-Me?
There's no way I could have anything to do with it...
What a strange incident... Even its owner, Heartland, declared the cause is unknown.
I'm late, LATE!!
Yuma!
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
What happened that was so bad?
I see... So your older sister...
But it’s great that we got both the Emperor’s Key and Shark’s soul back.
Oh, along with you.
But I was a bit shaken as well.
I can’t believe he actually managed to enter the Emperor’s Key.
Numbers Hunter Kaito…
He's the one responsible for all those shocking incidents.
Who in the world is he?
Speaking of Kaito, he's a frightful guy!
But… at least there is one thing we are clear on.
He is able to control the Numbers at will.
All the Numbers Duelists we fought in Duels before were somehow affected by Numbers.
But nothing has happened to him... to Kaito.
Maybe he is using a power not of this world.
What do you mean by that?
I don't know.
But, the Galaxy Eyes he uses...
The light surrounding that monster might be the same as the one from my world.
Why is he gathering the Numbers in the first place?
The Numbers contain your memories...
Now that you think of it, it's to terminate my existence.
Terminate?
That's right.
When my memory returns, something bad may happen.
Anyway, what I know now is...
His real concern is the existence of his younger brother, Haruto.
To save my brother, I sold my soul to the devil.
So the one in that photo... was Haruto?
Damn it, I'm late!
Those clouds are...
Heya, Kotori!
Forget, "heya!"
Shit, we're late!
Gosh, it's all your fault, Yuma!
I was worried to death yesterday, and I overslept today.
Oh yeah, Astral...
You're responsible as well!
Are you here?
I'm late now...
C'mon, Calm down...
But, I'm glad you're safe, Astral.
It’s not this side…
Say something?!
Well... nothing.
Yuma!
The heck? You guys're late, too?
We were too excited, and we couldn't fell asleep like that!
To summarize, we're exhausted!
Thanks for yesterday, everyone!
Good morning.
C-Cat-chan...
I was so happy yesterday…
That so?
So you aren't gonna tell me anything~ura-yo?
Tokunosuke...
Mind sharing the details~ura?
No, we were quite busy…
We are too late!
I'm not done talking here~ura!
This is...
This can't be...
That's right, time has stopped.
Then Kaito is...
No, it's different, this is...
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Dr. Faker-sama,
What in the world just happened?
The Astral World created enormous resonance with another world,
and they kept stacking in our world, so I temporarily stopped time.
"Numbers 25: Time's Coming:
The Three Suns Appear"
What will happen?
No need to worry.
Within a few hours, that resonance will pass our world, and everything will back to normal.
But we are quite certain that these two worlds are getting closer and closer.
We don’t have much time left before entering the final phase.
Before that happens, the Astral World must…
Look, Yuma.
What is going on with this?
There are three suns.
One of those suns is my world.
I cant believe this is happening.
It's here, right?
Yes.
We’ve reached the place that was listed in their memory.
The memory of their Duels begins here.
These are Astral's memories...?
Come, call to me.
"Numbers".
What in the...?!
Power is swelling up inside me...
Come, Numbers 17!
Leviath Dragon!
Numbers?!
Stand.
Let's win.
With this, all the conditions are met.
What?
Take a look at your Extra Deck.
Number 39... Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
This is... a Numbers?!
Correct. That's the power I've entrusted to you.
I'm gonna bring it to you!
I Overlay my Level Four Gagaga Magician and Ganbara Knight!
Come forth! Numbers 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!!
That is the only trump card which is capable of bringing down Leviath Dragon, Aspiring Emperor - Hope.
It's over. Yuma lost...
That can't be!
Going by that attitude of yours, have you also given up something important to you?!
Have you abandoned something that was precious to you?!
I for one never give up and will keep bringing it to 'em!
I'll show you what I mean!
Bring it to 'em, Hope!
Attack Leviath Dragon!
Hey! Astral... Hey!
What's wrong?
My head... I feel pain in my head!
Someone is looking at my memories!
Yuma, someone came to the place in our memories where we Dueled before...
Hey, wait!
Over there, the place where the third Numbers appeared.
I construct the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
A Xyz Monster using three overlays?!
Show yourself!
Numbers 34!
Computer Beast Terabyte!
Astral...
Why are you running away from me?
There must be some reason why the sun in my world has appeared.
Is someone over there?
No, but someone did before…
Wait, Astral!
This is the place we Dueled Tokunosuke.
Right.
He took away Numbers and caused my loss of consciousness.
And he plotted against you in that Duel.
I left the Baby Tragon you asked me to protect and used it as a counterattack.
Prepare yourself~ura!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Uratra C~ura!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope was taken!
Baby Tragon's effect activates!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope attacks directly!
Go, Hope Sword Slash!
Alright, it's settled!
This is the memory of the fourth Numbers.
-Duel!
Then I Overlay the three Level One Trions!
The three monsters will open the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Numbers 83 Galaxy Queen!
Another Numbers appeared!
Galaxy Queen?
Now the pieces for victory are gathered!
Let's go!
I'll bring it to em'!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope attacks Galaxy Queen!
Hope Sword Slash!
The attacked monster will be switched!
Thats right, when Kotori was kidnapped,
I had a Duel with Cat-chan!
Yuma has acknowledged me!
Now, Twin Tail Cat Lady, approach Yuma!
Direct Attack!
I… Yuma… I always…
Go, Baby Tragon!
Baby Stream!
Cat…!
Meo-why~!!!?
This is were I tag dueled with Shark.
Thats right.
The place were we got back the fifth and sixth Numbers.
I promised I wouldn't use the Numbers and lost to Shark.
For my own sake, I fought him once again!
I overlay the level 5 Punch Flamesaurus and Bontan Lavasaurus!
The 2 monsters will open the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear No. 61!
Volcasaurus!
Two level 4 monsters?
Appear, No. 19 Freezerdon!
This is where I dueled Kaito.
That's right.
The Numbers Hunter Kaito.
Faced with his overwhelming strength,
We Dueled in vain to lose.
I'll take away your soul!
Go, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Astral!
This is... Over...
This duel is canceled!
But we weren't whining about that.
In the Duel Lodge, Grandpa Rokujuro taught us something important.
Be consumed kid, along with your light and friends!
I overlay the level 5 Armored Ninja Earth and Armored Ninja Flame!
Come, Numbers 12!
Armored Ninja Crimson Shadow!
Then I fought the guy called Jin,
and attained the new power of Hope Ray.
Xyz Summon! Appear, Numbers 16!
The Ruler of Color!
Shock Ruler!
It can't be!
Appear Numbers 11! The one with the all seeing eye, Big Eye!
Your my.. Precious friend, Astral!
I'm afraid too.
But we'll find hope by not giving up!
Let's bring it to em'!
Yuma...
I will win, for you... no for your friends!
You...
Let's win, Yuma!
Astral!
Let's go!
My turn, draw!
The material of a new way to victory is all gathered here!
This is...
The power of hope, the one who can truly change light,
Chaos Numbers 39!
Chaos Xyz Change!
Appear now, Chaos Numbers 39!
Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray's effect activates!
Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray, by using one of its Overlay Units,
It's attack power goes up by 500 points!
I use all 3 of the Overlay Units!
Hope Ray's attack power goes up!
Overlay Charge!
No way!
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
Attack Big Eye!
Hope Blade Chaos Slash!
And Obomi became our new friend.
This is the memory of his last No.
What is this?
Astral...
Destroy it, I'll destroy everything!
What is this!?
You can't run anymore!
This is my "bringing it to em"!
Hope Sword Slash!
No way, for me to...!
Yuma, take this!
Yeah!
As I thought, Kaito.
Gosh!
Are the two of you okay?
What are you doing~ura-yo?!
Huh? Yuma has...
We'll settle this at the World Duel Carnival!
I'm looking forward to it!
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
World Duel Carnival has started!
Speak of which, I still didn’t get the Heart Piece which is required for the participation in the tournament!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
Start, World Duel Carnival! (WDC)
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!