Under Grandma's orders, we went to a place far away from the town.
A Duel Lodge!?
But a wise old man trained in the
art of Duel Training was waiting for us!
And me and the old man has a statue duel with the legendary monsters.
But for some reason, I've become a Monster!
I think I may have just learned something...
But now I have to win against the old man's disciple in a duel!
I'll fight too, Yuma.
I won't forgive anyone who insults the old man, even if he's a fellow disciple!
I'll bring it to em'!
I set 2 cards face-down and end my turn!
Me and my monsters no... my friends will definitely win against you!
Something a kid carved by light would say.
I see. My master taught you that.
Then let me show you the gap between light and darkness!
The darkness overcomes the light!
Hang in there, Yuma!
But this duel is kinda scary!
He's being consumed by the darkness more and more...
Here I go!
My turn, draw!
By decreasing it's attack power by 500 points,
I Summon this monster!
Come! Dododo Warrior!
Filling up your field, are you?
If you had released Gagaga Magician and summoned Dododo Warrior,
It's attack power would've been higher than Blade Heart's.
Why did Yuma decrease Dododo Warrior's attack power, instead of using Gagaga Magician?
I'm sure Yuma has...
Yuma, are you still trying to protect you monsters?
Do you have any problem with that!?
Nope.
Here I go!
From my hand I activate the Magic Card, Instant Blow of Friendship!
If a monster on my field battles,
none of us take the damage, but it destroys the opponent's monster!
Dododo Warrior attacks Armored Ninja Brave Heart!
Go! Dododo Axe!!
Permanent Trap open!
Armored Ninjitsu Arts: Freeze Lock!
If a "Ninja" is on my field,
It ends the opponent's monster's attack,
and as long as this Permanent Trap exists,
your monsters can't change their battle positions.
So that's how it is?
Not yet!
I can't afford to lose this duel!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
" Numbers 16: The Deadliest Ninja Arts!
The Most Terrifying Ninja!"
My turn, draw!
From my hand I activate Spy Attack!
By sending a monster from my hand to the cemetery,
I can destroy a set card on your field!
Armored Ninja Aqua!
Putting your own life on the line, invade enemy territory!
Eradicate his set card!
He sacrifices his monsters for just one chance to win.
That's how he duels.
This card is...
Yuma...
Oh Yuma, so your already dueling here?
Roku-san, did you teach him?
Haru-san!
It's been a while!
His sister too!?
Just as I thought, you do duel, Yuma!
Sister!?
Yuma, your gonna get...
P-Please calm down.
That child is attempting to surpass himself.
The person he's been up until now.
Just believe in him.
That's your duty.
Sister...
Keep focusing, Yuma!
So you've got a crowd to witness your death?
Then I'm going to show them your death!
Blade Heart attacks Gagaga Magician!
Sudden Rapid...
Blade Strike!!
Strike all standing in your way!
By detaching an Overlay Unit,
It can attack the opponent's monster once more!
Blade Heart attacks Dododo Warrior!
Your face-down card is Gagaga Back.
By losing 600 points of your life,
It has an effect to revive a monster.
Are you still trying to protect your monsters at all costs!?
600 for just 1?
Is there any meaning in reviving the monster?
Yuma...
Let this revival damage the fool even more!
Permanent Trap open! Armored Ninjitsu Arts: Last Mist!
If I have a "Ninja", all ll Special Summoned monsters on the opponent's field have their attack power halved!
Come on, save your friends!
Even knowing you're only increasing your terrible situation!
Yuma, ignore him.
Stick to your own thoughts.
Fight with your own feelings!
Look closely at what your teacher has taught you.
There must be a secret method to win beyond it.
That is what I wish to see.
Astral...
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Gagaga Back!
This card, if Gagaga Magician was destroyed by battle,
It will revive with it's monster friend that was destroyed by battle!
But, for each monster revived I take 600 points of damage!
Yuma!
His life is at 300...
Yuma...
Then, with Armored Ninjitsu Arts: Rust Mist's effect,
All Special Summoned monsters on the opponent's field will have their attack power halved!
With this I end my turn.
Why do you care so much about your monster? Even though their attack powers are almost gone, and your life is depleting.
Do you think you can trust the monsters?
I will believe in my friends.
Once my feelings connect to the monsters'!
They will save me for sure!
What do you mean by connected?
The monsters will save you?
The monsters are not your friends!
They are just servants of the duelists!
I had about all I could stand of that stupid nonsense about "heart"!
Duels are ruled by darkness and fear!
You're Wrong!
That's not what dueling is about!
Act arrogant and boast all you like.
Your life is only at 300...
If your life reaches 0, and your friends don't save your till then,
You lose.
I will believe in my monsters no... my friends!
My turn, draw!
Alright, it came!
I activate the Magic Card, Gagaga Bolt!
If I have a "Gagaga" monster on my side, I can destroy a card on the opponent's field!
I destroy Armored Ninja Blade Heart!
What!?
Then I attack directly with Gagaga Magician!
Then Dododo Warrior attacks directly!
GO!
Won't let you!
From my cemetery I activate Armored Ninja Aqua's effect!
By excluding this card it negated a monster's direct attack!
Answer me my friends!
When Dododo Warrior attacks,
The opponent's Magic, Trap, and monster's effects are negated!.
What!?
Now the effects of Rust Mist and Aqua are gone!
So I can attack directly!
Go, Dododo Warrior!
Dododo Axe!
What!?
I did it!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Did you see me?
Our feelings have reached our friends!
We aren't the only ones who are fighting in this duel!
My friends have answered me!
That's what my master, Old Man Rokujuro taught me!
Give me a break!
The old man taught you? Yeah right!
I have surpassed my master and that teaching
I don't have any friends, and I don't trust anyone!
I fight alone!
And I win alone!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Magic Card...!
Armored Ninjitsu Arts: Gold Conversion!
I destroy every card with "Armored Ninjitsu Arts" in it's name!
He's destroying his own traps?
Then I draw 2 cards from my deck!
What are you trying to do?
If there's a monster on the opponent's field,
I can Special Summon Armored Ninja Earth!
This is strange...
Then I activate the Magic Card, Armored Ninjitsu Arts: Undead Return!
I can Special Summon a "Ninja" monster that's in my cemetery!
Come, Armored Ninja Flame!
When Flame is successfully summoned, his level goes up by 1.
He has a No.!
No way!
Take this, kid!
And your "master" and his "light" along with you!
I overlay the level 5 Armored Ninja Earth and Armored Ninja Flame!
These two monsters will construct the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Come, No. 12!
Armored Ninja Crimson Shadow!
This monsters is my true power!
The darkness inside the darkness!
Crimson Shadow engulf him in darkness!
A-A Numbers!
To come this far for the No. to come out...
Damn it, he even has a No.!
This monster is a great source of Yamikawa's darkness.
Yuma...
Take on the strongest Ninja attack!
Crimson Shadow attacks Gagaga Magician!
T-This is bad!
Yuma, the Trap Card!
That's right!
Trap Card open, Guts Guard!
With this card, the attacking monster can't attack any other monster except the one that's targeted!
I change the attack from Gagaga Magician to Dododo Warrior!
And the monster targeted by the attack can't be destroyed!
What persistence, with this I end my turn.
I'm saved!
But If I'm attacked next time...
Put yourself together, Yuma!
This time he's not dueling with full spirit.
He might be hungry.
Hey!
What's the matter, kid? Is it already over!?
Where's the power of your friends that you believed in?
Yuma, remember that...
You and the monsters have the same feelings.
Your teacher's words!
Stop!
Please stop!
If you know the monster's feelings they will answer you.
Those emotions will truly make the monsters move.
The monster's feelings?
Right now...
The monsters are...
That's right.
I don't care if it's a No.!
Me and my friends will get out of this trouble!
Yuma!
It's your Duel Meal!
Thanks a lot!
Thank you, Kotori!
I'll bring it to em'!
My turn, draw!
It came, It came, it came!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic Decrease!
This card can decrease a monster's level by 2!
I decrease Dododo Warrior's level from 6 to 4!
I overlay the level 4 Gagaga Magician and Dododo Warrior!
The 2 monsters will open the overlay network.
Xyz Summon!
Come, No. 39 Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Alright!
Do you see it now Yuma, the key to victory?
Yup!
Aspiring Emperor Hope attacks Crimson Shadow!
Hope Blade Slash!!
You did it, Hope!
The darkness shall reign!
Crimson Shadow's effect activates!
By detaching an Overlay Unit,
I negate Crimson Shadow's destruction!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Revenge Attack!
If a monster on our field couldn't destroy the opponent's monster in battle, Revenge Attack can be activated!
Hope's attack power goes up by 1000 and can battle once again!
What!?
What is this light?
This is Aspiring Emperor Hope's strength.
The Light Of Hope... Will banish the Darkness!
Hope Sword Slash!!
The darkness has...
Yuma!
So how's that!?
Seems like Yuma's duel is always depending on his trumps!
So I was right about sending him to you.
He is a quick learner.
That child learned his strength and the fate that surrounds it.
I was obviously going to win!
What are you talking about? That was a close call.
Hey!
About him...
Move away, kid!
Can't you see it?
This statue's wound?
The old man gave his all to fix it after you attacked it!
This monster is your friend.
Your important friend!
I... sought strength and power...
But I couldn't see that in the darkness!
The darkness is gone.
The rest is up to you.
Master!
Yamikawa wants to continue training again.
Let's fight again!
This time with your monsters, no...your friends!
Yeah.
So you duel after all.
I guess I have no choice.
Just don't overdo it.
Alright!
Yuma...
This is the Duel Lodge's Hidden Deck.
This deck is most suited to be with you.
I bet this deck will respond to your feelings.
Is that fine?
Yeah...
This is amazing!
Now you'll make an impact in the World Duel Carnival with this deck!
Yeah!
Yuma, do you plan on participating?
Now I can beat any number of guys!
Right, Astral?
He's not here.
Looks like Yuma has improved.
But can I....
But can I win...?
Against that Kaito?
Time to start the duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
How many cards are required in your deck?
20, 30, or 40?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
"Numbers Club"?
Yeah! We're gonna investigate the secrets of the Numbers!
I'm worried about Yuma!
Sorry, but you're going to have to give up on your friends.
Forget that!
This is... fear?
I don't need your strength anymore!
I'll save everyone with my own hands!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The All-Seeing Seer: The Terrifying Fortuneteller – Jin"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer's 40!
You need to have at least 40 cards in your deck.
But by adding other cards you like, you can increase your deck all the way up to 60 cards!