Huh?! Shark is going be a card bandit with those punks?
It's best not to get involved with Shark anymore.
That's not it!
It's not only for Shark! This battle is about myself as well!
I have to win this duel, and awake Shark once and for all!!
Be careful, Yuma. Something is wrong in this duel.
You are so annoying! Let's go! I'm bringin' it to 'em!!
It destroys the opponent's monster and inflicts that monster's ATK as damage to the opponent.
This is the power of our Numbers, Volcasaurus, known as Mag-Max!
Yuma.
If this continues...we're in trouble.
But now, Volcasaurus has used up all of its Overlay Units.
It can no longer activate Mag-Max, its Monster Effect.
Is that so?! Nice, the real game is just about to get started!
Hmph! What do you mean just getting started?
Anyway, Ryouga, you're first one to go!
I attack Ryouga directly with the 2500 Attack Power Volcasaurus!!
Shark!
Trap, activate!
Zeus' Breath!
This card can negate one monster's attack.
Tch! So you set that kind of card, huh...?
Phew, you saved us.
Saved, you think?
Your field is wide open!
We will finish you off in the next turn.
I set two cards face-down and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!!
I summon Goblindbergh!
When this card is successfully Summoned,
I can Special Summon one LV 4 or lower monster from my hand.
I Special Summon the LV 4 Gagaga Magician!
There are two LV 4 Monsters...?!
Wait, Yuma!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
I Overlay my Level Four Gagaga Magician and Goblindbergh!
I use these two monsters to construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, NO.39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!
Awesome!! It's Hope!
Gee... Geez! In the end, Yuma still needs to rely on Numbers!
Here you are, Numbers...
We've been waiting for you.
Permanent Trap, activate! Avalanche!!
When this card is activated, the Summoned Xyz monster cannot declare an attack!
Hope...
Hope is frozen!!
Additionally, when that Xyz monster activates its Monster Effect,
the player will receive 500 points of damage!
No way! Now I can't use Hope's effect.
A Trap Card specifically designed for battling Xyz monsters!
What a reckless summon.
I set two cards face-down and end my turn!
If we're able to seal the Numbers, we'll win for sure. Let's finish them off!
My turn, draw!!
I switch its battle position, so Mince Icebergdon is now in attack position!
It's over, Ryouga!
I attack Ryouga directly with Mince Icebergdon!
Ready to get crushed!!
I activate Aspiring Emperor - Hope's effect!
It can negate one monster's attack!
Impossible!
Did you forget the effect of Permanent Trap, Avalanche?
You will receive 500 damage!
I said we are friends!!
Rune Barrier!!
Then taste the effect of Avalanche!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Yuma, entrusted with a single card from Ryouga..-->
<--Counter attack with a super powerful monster!
Yuma!!
"Numbers 12: Union of Hope -
Armored Exceed Activate!"
Don't tell me Yuma summoned Hope because he wants to protect Shark?
That guy... did those unnecessary things again!
Such beautiful friendship!
How nice, you got a good friend there, then here's another one!!
I attack Ryouga directly with Resent Blizzardon!
I activate Aspiring Emperor - Hope's effect!
Rune Barrier!!
Yuma... you...
Darn it!
What's wrong? It doesn't matter if you continue to sleep like that.
Shut up! I just had a little rest!
The real game is about to get started!!
It seems you still don't understand.
...understanding how powerful we are!
I activate the Trap card, Volcash!!
I use this card's effect to switch Kaio's monster, Resent Blizzardon, to defense position!
Why would he purposely change his partner's monster to defense position?
Nice one, Big bro!
Thanks to you, I can activate the Magic card in my hand, The Alert Ice Cave!!
This card can increase the level of one defense position monster on my field by 1!
How...!!
I increase Resent Blizzardon's LV from 4 to 5!!
There are two LV5 monsters!!
I overlay LV5 Mince Icebergdon and Resent Blizzardon!!
I construct Overlay network with these two monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, NO. 19 Freezerdon!!!
The second Numbers!
I activate Freezerdon's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
it can resurrect all Overlay Units of my partner's Xyz monster!
What?!
Resurrect Overlay Units?
The Overlay Units are back! Now it can use Mag-Max again!
Those guys.
I set two cards face-down, and end my turn!
No one can defeat us in a tag duel!
There are something strange about this duel.
So they did use tricks after all!
Tricks?
Hoo? What did ya say?
Stop playing dumb!! Using those despicable tricks.
What's he mean by "tricks"?
He said tricks!
Which means they cheated!
Cheated... Which means they dishonored the Duel!
I expect no less from those punks!!
Those guys... they knew what cards were in each other's decks,
in what particular order.
It's quite possible that they even altered the auto shuffling function of their Duel Disks as well!
Really? So that's why they had all LV 5 monsters at that time. which seemed like a coincidence!
That time too, when he used that Trap Card to purposely switch his partner's monster to defense position,
and then using a Magic card to raise its level for a Xyz summon.
In other words, they knew the cards they both had,
and what cards they will draw next.
If so, they are no longer qualified as duelists!!
True Duelist would never use these tricks!
What do you mean using tricks? Stop assuming stuff!
Speaking of tricks, didn't you do the same in the National Tournament?
Champion candidate my foot!!
You're nothing but a bastard who peeked at his opponent's deck in the resting room before the Final!
It's the Final of Duel Monsters National Tournament!
The strong champion favorite, contestant Kamishiro Ryouga, is going up steadily!
Win... I have to win...
Just what kind of Duel they will bring to us?
That guy's deck.
The Final is reaching its conclusion!
Both contestants aren't giving an inch!
I can win... just a bit more!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Set card? Don't tell me in this situation, that card is...
If so, I can win!
My turn, Dra...
For this duel, because of contestant Kamishiro Ryouga's inappropriate behavior, he will be disqualified!
Contestant Kamishiro violated the rule by checking at opponent's deck!
Because of that, you were banished from the Duel Stage forever!
I'm terrified of losing.
A champion favorite actually afraid of losing? How ugly!
What a hopeless guy he is.
DON'T LAUGH!
What's so darn funny?
What's so funny about having a fear of losing?
I'm afraid of losing as well. Every single moment when I think of losing, I was engulfed by fear.
That's why I used my Numbers!
I said I was doing this to help Shark, but I was just afraid of losing!
I was lying!
Yuma.
But because of this, I decided to never lie in a duel ever again!!
It must be the same for Shark. That's why Shark's duel, is for real!
No matter what kind of despicable tricks the opponents use, we will win fair and square!
That's our Dueling!
What are you babbling about?
There's only one frozen Numbers on your field. What use does it have?
Yuma... let's win this duel once and for all!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Xyz Gift, from my hand!
If there are two or more Xyz monsters on the field, I can draw two cards!
I summon Spike Sunfish!!
Then I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Surfacing!
I can special summon one Water-Type Monster from my graveyard in face-up defense position!
Come, Big Jaws!
This is...
I overlay the LV3 Spike Sunfish and Big Jaws!
I construct the Overlay Network with these two monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Black Ray Lancer!!
Black Ray Lancer!!
I activate Black Ray Lancer's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can negate Volcasaurus's effect until the end Phase!
What?!
Now the Numbers can be defeated!
But Volcasaurus still has the higher ATK!
How naive, Rikuo! I activate the effect of Spike Sunfish!
When this card was sent to the graveyard, Volcasaurus's ATK is reduced by 500!!
It's ATK is 2000. Now Black Ray Lancer has more Attack Power!
He actually made a breakthrough in this situation.
I attack Volcasaurus with Black Ray Lancer! Go, Black Spear!
Pff! Trap, activate! Compensation Exchange!
While this card negates the attack, the player will receive damage equal to Volcasaurus's ATK!
That guy took the hit instead!
I am responsible for offense while Kaio specializes in defense.
That's the way of our battle!
Trap, activate! The Scorching Depths! Volca Abyss!
When my partner receives effect damage, I can check my opponent's hand,
and if there is a Monster Card, that card is returned to the deck!
Let me confirm your hand!
My hand?
Because he wants to prevent you from summoning monsters in the next turn.
Ahh! My card!
Gogogo Golem and Resurrection of the Dead...
Resurrection of the Dead, eh? Not a card he will likely use.
Alright, return the monster card to your deck!
Gogogo Golem.
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Now it's over for you!
My turn, draw!
Ryouga, you're the first to go!
I activate the effect of Volcasaurus!
It destroys one monster the opponent controls and inflicts damage equal to that monster's ATK!
I destroy Black Ray Lancer and inflict its 2100 ATK as damage to Ryouga!
Shark!
Take this! Mag-Max!!
Take this, Ryouga!
Trap, activate! Damage Diet!
During this turn, the effect damage will be halved.
I target Volcasaurus and activate the Trap Card, Hate Crevice!!
When a monster I control would be destroyed by a card effect,
it can destroy one monster my opponent controls instead, and inflict its ATK as damage to the controller!
So you wanna to perish together?
Trap, activate! Compulsory Change!
I switch the trap target to Freezadon!
Kaio!
Nice, Kaio is down!
How dare you do that to my little brother... Don't even think for a minute you'll go back alive!!
I activate the effect of Volcasaurus!
I destroy Hope! Take this! Mag-Max!!
Damage Diet!
Playing smart, huh? I attack Ryouga directly with Volcasaurus!
I activate a Trap! Last Entrust!
This card and end the Battle Phase,
and give one card from my hand to the opponent!
Yuma!
Me? The opponents include me as well?
Yes.
That card is...
Useless Struggle!
I activate the Continuous Magic Card, Twin Volcano!!
During my Standby Phase, it inflicts 500 damage to the opponent!
When I send this card to the graveyard, I can inflict additional 500 damage!
In other words...
That's right, when his turn comes... both of your Lives will be Zero.
That way it will be our victory!
Prepare yourselves!
Don't give up. We still have a chance to win.
My turn, draw!!
Our chance to win...
If it's you, then you will notice it!
Can you understand his considerations?
All I can do for now is summon Hope using Resurrection of the Dead!
Huh... Armored Xyz... the card that Shark gave me... right!
Resurrection of the Dead can also resurrect a monster from the opponent's Cemetery.
I activate the Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead, from my hand!
Is he going to Special Summon Hope?
I special summon Black Ray Lancer from Shark's graveyard!
Why would you choose the Black Ray Lancer with lower ATK?
You are an amateur after all!
Don't be so sure about that!
What?!
I activate a Magic card from hand, Armored Xyz!!
Armored Xyz?
I gave him a card that is specifically designed for Xyz monsters.
This card allows me to select one Xyz monster in my graveyard,
and equip it to a monster on my field!
Come forth, Aspiring Emperor -  Hope!
I equip Aspiring Emperor - Hope to Black Ray Lancer!
Hmph! Even if its ATK becomes 2500,
did you forget the fact that Numbers can only be defeated by Numbers?
It can be defeated!
What?!
Due to Armored Xyz's effect, Black Ray Lancer can be treated as Hope!
In other words, it can be treated as a pseudo-Numbers!
Pseudo Numbers you say?
Then Volcasaurus...
Go! I attack Volcasaurus with Black Ray Lancer!
Plus, thanks to Armored Xyz, by sending Hope to the Graveyard...
Black Ray Lancer can attack twice in a row!
I send Hope to the graveyard.
Go, Black Ray Lancer, attack Rikuo directly!
Im... Impossible!
BLACK SPEAR!!
They won!
Nice one, Yuma!!
Observation #12... That is your Dueling.
What on Earth happened to us?
Why would we dare to steal cards?
Shark!
Run!!
What's up with those guys?
Don't you ever come back!!
Tetsuo...
I'm sorry, I lied to you, so please forgive me!!
Huh... what the...
It's completely fine. Speaking of which, how about we duel?
Sounds nice!
You mean now?
Shark...
That... oh right, Armored Xyz,
I'll give that card back to you!
That card is yours now.
Looks like our no-good duelist did improve a bit.
What do you mean no-good?
See ya!
Shark.
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
When you activate Trap Cards, do you activate it from your hand or after setting it?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
There is someone else who can use Numbers besides me?
Hmph! I can beat him in a Duel anyway.
What...? Time has stopped!
You're... a Numbers Hunter!
Yuma, this man is extremely dangerous!
Hurry up and Run!
Even you... No... he is the strongest one I have battled so far.
If you said that, then I'm all fired up!!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Hunter of Souls, Numbers Pursuer Appears!!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is... you activate it after setting. You need preparation to set traps.
Prior to activation, you have to set it first!
No.19 - Freezerdon!-->
<---It will revive overlay units!