I started a Duel with the Charlie, owner of Number 7, the card with the strongest luck!
Plus the location is a rampaged monorail which has lost control.
If this continues, we'll...
Mayumi-chan.
It’s almost time for your surgery.
Yeah...
Don’t worry, it will be over while you're still asleep.
But my uncle still hasn't...
Yuma…
Alright, Yuma. Let our Carnival begin!
Gotcha, here I come! My turn, draw!
I'll set a Monster in face-down Defense Position! And set one more card, ending my turn!
Is he really planning to win with luck alone?
My turn, draw!
I activate the Continuous Magic, Trading Game!
Let's start out small. Let me test my luck a bit!
This card allows me to toss a die once per turn, and if I tossed a six, my current Life will increase five times!
However, if I get another value, my Life will return to the value prior to activation!
As if you'll get a six that easily!
No. He managed to roll five consecutive sixes in the previous Duel. The odds of the next one being 6 is 1/46656.
Behold…
It’s definitely impossible!
There!
S-Six?! He got it again?!
Five times 4000 is 20000!
So long as the sun is round, my luck won't end!
Shut up! The sun set a long time ago, darn it!
Right, which means nothing can stop my fortune.
I Summon Majestic Jester!
I attack the Monster in face-down Defense Position with Majestic Jester!
He attacked with a zero Attack Power Monster?!
Desperate Mime!!
Gogogo Golem’s DEF is 1500. You're the one who’s taking damage!
What a pity, Yuma. I activate the effect of Majestic Jester!
More dice?!
Allow me to utilize this extraordinary luck to its fullest!
When Majestic Jester declares an attack, if I tossed a six, it destroys a Monster my opponent controls.
If I got other values, then this card is destroyed and says his goodbye.
The probability of another consecutive six is 1/129936.
L-Like heck he will!
Here I come!
Here!
It can't be!
Impossible!
Bingo! I destroy Gogogo Golem!
I set one card, and end my turn!
If this continues, we will…
Fret not! We're standing next to the world's luckiest good luck charm, after all!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Charlie...! Charlie!
He completely disappeared after that, and no one knew where he went. That idiot!
"Number 32: The Insurmountable Luck!
Number 7, Lucky Stripes!"
My turn, draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
In that case, I'll win with luck as well!
I activate Magic Card, Monster Slot!
I Banish one Monster in my Graveyard who has same level as Gagaga Magician!
And I card allows me to draw one card from my deck, if the drawn Monster has same level as those 2 Monsters, I can special summon it to my field!
But if it doesn’t match, the drawn Monster and targeted card will be Banished!
You're taking too many risks!
You are so annoying!
If I get it, I'll have enough materials for a Rank 4 Xyz Summon!
It seems you still don’t understand. I already absorbed your luck, so there's nothing left for you to use!
Gimme a break! C'mon, my good fortune!
Draw!
No way~!
I already told you! You can't surpass my luck!
Darn! I end my turn!
If this continues, our chances of defeating him will trickle down to zero percent...
Say what?! What the heck are you going on about?!
Don't you get it, Yuma?
The luck attached to my cards is absolute.
Your father, Kazuma-san, was once my idol who greatly inspired me. I used to think he has everything.
But there was one thing he lacked, and that was luck.
What?
If only he had slightly better luck...
It had nothing to do with luck!
There are some critical moments in a person's life where they can't afford to lose.
That’s right, even it means they have to win by relying on luck!
Here I come! My turn, draw!
Alright, here goes! The Continuous Magic, Trade Game! If I hit the jack pot, my Life will increase 5 fold!
It won’t come again!
A-Again?!
He rolled a six!
Life is Carnival! Now my Life is 100000!!!
100000 Life?? How can we ever beat that Life?
I activate the Magic Card, Release Change!
By releasing one Monster on my field, I can Special Summon one Monster with the same level!
I release the Level One Majestic Jester, and Special Summon Diceslot Seven with the same level!
Then I activate the Magic Card, Monster Slot!
Damn! It's the same as me!
That’s right. What will happen if I do it?
I target the Level One Diceslot Seven!
I remove the Level One Majestic Jester from my Graveyard!
Now, if I draw a Level One Monster, I can Special Summon that Monster!
Alright, here it comes! I Special Summon Diceslot Seven!
You gotta be kidding me!
Next, I Normal Summon the third Diceslot Seven!
We're in trouble, Yuma!
Diceslot Seven can raise its level according tot the tossed value until the End Phase!
Please, give me three sixes!
The odds of getting three sixes is 1/362790000!
Stop it! I don’t want to hear that!
Let’s finish this once and for all!
There it is!
Something so unreal... actually happened.
The level of all three Diceslot Sevens goes from one to seven!
I Overlay the three Level Seven Diceslot Sevens!
I build the Overlay Network with the three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth! Number 7! Lucky Stripe!
There it is!
The Number!
It's here, here, here, here!
LIFE IS CARNIVAL!
Darn it!
As I said, as long as the sun remains as one, whole unit...
...my good fortune won’t end!
Kotori-chan!
Akari-san?
Listen carefully, there's only five minutes left before this monorail reaches its destination.
That means...
Don't worry, I'll handle it somehow.
Yuma! We're close to the destination!
What?!
Here I come, Yuma!
I activate Lucky Stripe’s effect!
When this Monster battles, by detaching one Overlay Unit, I roll a die!
And after the battle concludes, Lucky Stripe's Attack Power will increase by its original Attack Power times the number rolled on the die.
Alright, here I go!
It’s six! Lucky Stripe’s original Attack Power is 700, so times six, it’s 4200!
4200?!
I attack you directly with Lucky Stripe!
Super Lucky Nova!!
Yuma, use the Trap!
Understood!
Trap Card, open! Clever Scheme!
When I'm about to receive a direct attack, by sending one Monster Card from my hand to the Graveyard,
this card reduces the Battle Damage equal to the Attack of the sent Monster!
I send Zubaba Knight to the Graveyard!
Yuma!
Oh, a Trap Card? Impressive indeed!
I end my turn.
Damn it!
Hey, can't you do anything?!
If his fortune really is flawless, then there really is nothing we can do about it.
You can’t be serious…
Hey! Yuma! What are you sulking about?
Sis!
Akari?
Charlie! Just you wait! I will get there to give you a good beating!
You're as passionate as ever! If it's a kiss you're after, I'd be glad to oblige!
Yuma, I guess you were crushed by Lucky Stripe, the card Charlie stole, Right?
I need to tell you something regarding that card!
When the sun splits in two, its power will be carried away with the wind.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
It's a rumor that talks about how to take the luck away from that card.
Take the luck away?
That's what I've been saying!
Life is Carnival!
It means my luck won't disappear as long as the sun is round and whole!
Two suns...?
And that's what makes this card's fortune absolute!
We don’t have much time left!
C'mon, Yuma. It's probably about the right time for you to be surrendering.
As if! I... I'll never give up!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Ganbara Knight!
When a Level Four Monster is Summoned successfully, I can Special summon Shadow Lizard from my hand!
All right, I overlay the Level Four Shadow Lizard and Ganbara Knight!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
I use Aspiring Emperor - Hope to attack Lucky Seven!
Permanent Trap, activate! Dice Crisis!
By tossing a die, if I get a six, this card makes the Attack Power of one Monster my opponent controls zero! I then gain control of it!
Ole!
It won’t show up!
Please, don’t show up!
Sorry to disappoint. I got a six again!
Now Hope belongs to me!
Hope…
I set one card and end my turn.
We're pretty close to the final stop.
Allow me to finish to this Duel. After all, you can’t win anyway. Everything is fruitless in front of my strong luck!
You're pissing me off with this “luck, luck” talk!!
It doesn't matter whether you have luck or not! All that matters is that a person tries their best in a fight! That's how Dueling should be!
Just like my Dad taught me!
Yuma…
My Dad never relied on luck! He always opened the path with his own strength! And I'll do the same!
I will not give up!
I get it. Then allow mew to finish this once and for all. My turn!
Yuma!
Right!
Hold on! Trap Card, open!
Command of Sword!
When there is a Light-Attribute Warrior-Type Monster on my side of field, I can activate this effect in my opponent’s Draw Phase!
Now draw your card!
If the drawn card is a magic or trap, I can either destroy the drawn card, or destroy one Magic or Trap card on the field.
Is that’s so? Your goal is to destroy Dice Crisis, and get Hope back!
Draw it, Charlie!
Draw!
The card I drew is Sun’s Scale!
By tossing a die once per turn, if I get a six, all Monsters on my opponent’s field will be destroyed.
Even you get back your Hope, my victory won’t change! As long as the sun is still round!
The sun...!
I target Dice Crisis…
Yuma, the sun!
Split the sun!
The sun?
As long as the sun is round and whole...?
I get it! So you mean...!
I can’t believe such thing could happen in a Duel!
According to the effect of Command of Sword, the selected warrior, Hope!
Cut the sun from the Magic Card, the Scale of Sun!
I-It can't be...!
Go, Hope!
Hope Sword Slash!!
The sun... became two!
Wait! The luck…really…
That light is...
Don’t tell me the card’s power…
How could that happen?!
Because Scale of Sun was destroyed, you will receive 500 points of damage!
How can my luck disappear?!
I activate the effect of Trade Game!
If I roll a six, my Life will increase 5 fold! Otherwise it will return to its original value.
One?!
So my fortune... really did vanish?
I end my turn...
Yuma, do it now!
Alright, my turn, draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Come Back!
It will recover one of my Monsters on my opponent’s field!
Come back, my Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!!
Chaos Xyz Change!
Now show your self, Chaos Numbers 39!
The messenger who used the power of Hope to turn chaos into light! Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray…
I activate the effect of Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it gains 500 Attack Points!
Overlay Charge!
And for every Overlay Unit detached, the opponent’s Monster’s Attack Power will decrease by 1000!
Go! I attack Lucky Stripe with Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!!
Alright, I win!
Yuma!
The final stop!
We can’t make it!
Sis!
Akari's gonna bring it to ya!!
Are two of you all right?
Yup!
Yes!
Thank goodness.
Right, where’s Charlie?
My luck… My luck has disappeared…
I'm so sorry, Mayumi...
Who's that?!
A..Akari!
Who's this woman named Mayumi?
Mayumi!
Uncle!
Sorry I'm late!
I brought those magic words with me! "Bring it to 'em", Mayumi!
Bring it to 'em?
Yeah, do your best!
Okay!
Plus, I will give this card to you as your lucky charm.
Thanks! I'll bring it to 'em and do my best!
The card...
Maybe its luck came back when it changed ownership!
It’s going to be alright, the surgery will definitely be a success.
I heard that girl's surgery comes with great difficulty.
So I... wanted to give my luck to her... along with that card.
Charlie…
- Even so, there was no need to do something like-
- Akari!
Please tell Yuma for me that, "You're a splendid successor to Kazuma-san's spirit of bringin' it to 'em."
That, and...
Thanks for your help, Akari.
Ouch, that hurt.
See you later! I hope you can dress a bit more casual the next time we meet.
Okay! The day's finally over!
Yup! I'm hungry now!
Will she really return the Number to us?
It'll be fine!
No, I think we need to be more concerned about this! Hey! Yuma!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
It's the guy Shark's trying to get revenge on, IV!
He started a Duel with Tetsuo and the class rep!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Tag Duel of Hell! The Evil Hero, IV"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!