The Duel Carnival Semi-Finals have finally begun!
My opponent is Shark!
However, Shark’s heart was manipulated by Tron, which made him believe I was responsible for his sister's injury!
Open your eyes, Shark! You were deceived!
It's out.
Shark’s Number!
Yuma!
What the heck is a Number?
I ain't never even heard of a Number before!
He said Number… I've never seen that kind of thing!
What is that?
What on Earth is that Monster?
So that’s Shark’s Number.
It looks quite strong!
Yuma…
Oh~! What a fearsome Monster that is!
But it’s incredible. I have to get my hands on it!
Though you said that,
you must be off somewhere overjoyed at this sight.
But only for now, of course.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Go! Shark Drake, attack Gogogo Ghost!
"Number 62: Shark's Back!
The Bonds Bounded By Bringin' it to 'Em!"
Depth Bite!!
Here comes another one, Yuma!
I know!
I activate Shark Drake’s effect!
When it destroys a Monster by battle,
by detaching one Overlay Unit,
it decreases the destroyed Gogogo Ghost’s Attack Power by 1000 points, and Special Summons it to Yuma’s field!
Why would he Summon Yuma’s Monster back to his field?
In order to attack once again!
You only have 900 Life left.
After I destroy Gogogo Ghost again, you're finished!
Go, Shark Drake! Bite Gogogo Ghost and Yuma to pieces!
Yuma!
Now Yuma will lose!
N-No way...
What?!
Gogogo Ghost and Gogogo Golem have…
…swapped!
Look! Yuma's Life hasn't changed at all!
Wh-Why? Why would Gogogo Golem…
Thanks to Gogogo Ghost’s Monster Effect!
When Gogogo Ghost is Special Summoned, it can Special Summon Gogogo Golem from the Graveyard as well!
Additionally, when this effect is used, Gogogo Ghost is changed to Defense Position!
Therefore, even if it was destroyed by Shark Drake, the damage I receive is still zero!
Desperate struggle for your life. I end my turn!
That was amazing, Yuma!
Beautiful tactics!
It must be thanks to Astral!
Yuma is the one doing the fighting, so I won’t allow you to say something like that!
Yuma, do your best!
Hmmm, that wasn't half bad.
Dr. Faker: Numbers can only be defeated by Numbers.
In order to win, Yuma Tsukumo has no choice but to Summon his own Number; the partition of that Original!
Yuma, use Hope! If you don't Summon Hope,
there is no way we can win!
I know that! But I only have Gogogo Golem on my field. If I can just get another Level Four Monster…
My turn! Draw!
Darn it! It’s not a Monster Card!
Don’t panic, Yuma!
Of course I'm panicking! If I don’t save him as soon as possible, he'll become Tron’s victim as well!
Wake up, Shark! If you still have a shred of your true heart, try to remember our Duels!
Our Duels?
That’s right! My first Duel ever with you was the battle that gambled mine and Tetsuo’s decks!
Plus you and I had a Tag Duel before, too!
Looks like our no-good Duelist improved a bit.
I was really excited when you said that to me. Because I could tell that our hearts had finally connected!
In order to protect this,
you Dueled with Kaito, and that made he happy!
With Dueling, we've continuously strengthened our bonds! Isn't that right, Shark?
Hmph! How boring.
I have no idea about things like friends or bonds,
but none of those things matter to me!
Now the only thing supporting me
is my heart of vengeance towards you!
Bravo! Nice, very nice! You're the best!
Shark…
I am here to defeat you in order to avenge my younger sister.
So what’s your purpose here?
Didn't you come here to defeat me?
Spare me from your almighty speech and just come at me! Your turn has already started!
I know! If that’s what you want, I'll just have to deliver my thoughts through Dueling!
I switch Gogogo Golem from Defense Position to Attack Position!
Then I activate Quick-Play Magic, Golden Form!
This card, when a Monster is switched from Defense Position to Attack Position, doubles that Monster's Attack Power until my next turn!
Oh, how amazing this shiny sight is!
It is indeed Golden Burning!
What is Yuma thinking? Even if he managed to power-up Gogogo Golem…
To summarize, it still cannot defeat the Number!
Yuma…
Yeah, I know.
But even if I can’t defeat his Number, I'll still charge from head-on and deliver my feelings to Shark!
That’s all I can do for now.
Go, Gogogo Golem, attack Shark Drake! Great Cannon!
Wake up, Shark! Hurry and get a hold of yourself!
It's a hit! Yuma’s super-heavy strike was effective! Now Yuma and Shark are tied at 900 Life!
Realizing he can't defeat my Number, he starts depleting my Life? But it ends now.
I set one card and end my turn!
My turn, draw!
Yuma, this time I will finish you off completely...
...in order to avenge my sister and pay you back!
Here it comes, Yuma!
What’s that? What’s happening?
His body is glowing!
I use Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake as Xyz Material to Chaos Xyz Change!
Show yourself, Chaos Number 32!
Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake Vice!
Wh-What in the world?!
Ch…Chaos Number?!
That’s…
It finally appeared!
His Chaos Number…
Chaos Number…
Under the current situation, we are overwhelmingly disadvantaged!
Here I go! I activate Shark Drake Vice’s Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it Banishes one “Shark” Monster in the Graveyard.
I choose Spear Shark! And Gogogo Golem loses Attack Power equal to its 1600 Attack Power!
Go, Spear Shark! Pierce it!
This is bad, Yuma!
Yuma: I got it! I activate the Permanent Trap, Power Changer Barrier!
By decreasing Gogogo Golem’s Attack Power by 600...
...this card can negate Shark Drake Vice's effect!
He just blocked that!
But Shark Drake Vice still has Overlay Units left!
It will strike again!
Understood!
Then I will let you taste that once again!
By detaching an Overlay Unit, it Banishes a Monster in the Graveyard!
I select Two-Head Shark! And Gogogo Golem’s Attack Power loses this card’s 1200 Attack Power!
Ram him, Two-Head Shark!
Then I activate Power Changer Barrier’s effect again! It negates that Monster Effect!
It’s not over yet! I still have one Overlay Unit left!
I choose Shark Drake in my Graveyard! Letting Gogogo Golem’s Attack Power lose its 2800 Attack Power! Take this!
Defend it! Power Changer Barrier!
He finally managed to power up its Attack Power to 3600, but now he decreased it to 1800 with his own hands.
Plus, now Yuma only has 900 Life left. Does he even know what he’s doing?
It’s useless. The difference between Shark Drake Vice and Gogogo Golem’s Attack Power is 1000.
If this attack connects, it’s over!
Do it, Shark Drake Vice! Attack Gogogo Golem!
Depth Chaos Bite!!
Trap, activate! Half Unbreak!
Thanks to this effect, Gogogo Golem will not be destroyed, and my damage is halved!
What persistence. But when my next turn comes, you will fall into Hell completely!
I set one card and end my turn!
That’s right, it’s over when the next turn comes. Over for good.
With that card I gave Ryoga as a present, Yuma Tsukumo will be eliminated!
Power Change Barrier saved us.
We only have 400 Life left. Let’s settle it during this turn!
I know!
I…I…I believe in myself and my own deck!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!
Draw!!
Got it! I Summon Gagaga Magician!
I Overlay the Level Four Gagaga Magician and Gogogo Golem!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
It's time to show yourself, Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor- Hope!
You fool! Even if you managed to Summon Hope now, it can't defeat Shark Drake Vice with its 2500 Attack Power!
All you can do is pitifully struggle with
the conviction of eventual defeat!
You're wrong!
Hope won't die! Neither will your Number!
I wish to save you, and of course I don’t want lose either!
I desire to become the champion of the Duel Carnival, and finally settle the score with Tron and Dr. Faker.
But even if I win, I would feel worse losing you!
Therefore, I… I will save you using whatever method necessary!
I will release you from Tron’s curse!
Here I come, Shark! I attack Shark Drake Vice with Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Hope Sword Slash!
So in the end, you still run out of ideas and solely charge head on?
Fight back! Depth Chaos Bite!
I detach one Overlay Unit, and activate Hope’s effect! It negates a Monster’s attack!
He actually negated Hope’s attack?
Now, Yuma!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Bonds of Rival!
When my Monster’s attack is negated, I can equip this card to the battling Monster my opponent controls, and I gain that Monster’s control!
Im…impossible!
Latch on to me, Shark Drake Vice! Leave Shark alone and come to my side!
Yuma took Shark’s Number…
...away?!
But that way, Yuma will…
Take it back, Shark! Your true heart!
Yuma Tsukumo, I'll remember you.
Obviously because we're friends!
Don't get involved with me anymore...
Something about revenge...
We'll settle things in the Finals!
I don’t want to see that!
Y-Yuma... It wasn't Yuma... who hurt my little sister...
Tron was the one who hurt my sister!
I've been controlled by the Number this entire time!
Yuma!
Shark!
Yuma sure is suffering, isn't he?
Tron!
At this rate, it’ll be his turn to be manipulated by the Number. What will you do, Ryoga?
He has redeemed you from agony,
and now he is suffering in your place.
Yuma!
Tron: You wish to save him, yes? Assuming you are one of his friends, too.
What should I do?
It seems you have recalled it. That’s right, just use that Trap Card. Use Medallion Catastrophe!
Medallion…Catastrophe…
Yuma...! Yuma!
At this rate...
It’s alright! Pretty soon Ryoga will come and save you!
Tron…
Thanks to your effort of stealing Shark Drake Vice, that Trap Card on Ryoga’s field, Medallion Catastrophe, can be activated now.
When the opponent gains control of your Monster, this card can destroy all Monsters with Attack Power equal to or lower than that Monster's.
In other words, both Shark Drake Vice and Aspiring Emperor - Hope will be destroyed.
WHAT?! Even Hope too…
Tron(to Shark): That way Yuma can escape from the curse of the Number, too.
However, the total of the destroyed Monsters’ Attack Power, in other words, 5300 damage, will be inflicted to him.
That way victory will be yours. I gave that card to you because I knew something like this would happen. A sure-kill Trap, that is.
If Hope is destroyed, then Astral, too…
Is…is there any other way?
Right! Traplin! By releasing one Permanent Trap on the field, it can be Special Summoned.
If I use this effect to destroy Bonds of Rival…
That’s right, Shark Drake Vice would return to Shark, and Hope and I will be saved.
But he will be controlled by the Number, no, Tron again.
That’s right. Alright, which side will you choose? Ryoga or Astral?
Tron!
You decide, Yuma.
Astral…
There is nothing more I can do under these circumstances. This is your Duel. You will do the thinking and make the decisions.
But I can't... I can't choose between you and Shark!
Shark: Yuma!
If you don’t save him as soon as possible, he will only suffer more and more.
So do it, Ryoga. Activate Medallion Catastrophe.
Be it Shark Drake Vice, Aspiring Emperor - Hope, along with Yuma Tsukumo... Bury them together!
Yuma!
I can't choose... I just can't choose! Because to me, both you and Shark are very important... friends!
Yuma…
That set card is the one I set from the very beginning. I…
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Marine Snow Seal!
I Banish Shark Drake Vice!
I will receive 1000 points of damage as the price!
Shark!!
The…The winner is…Contestant Yuma Tsukumo…
Yuma…
Get a hold of yourself, Shark! Hey!
In order to save us, you…
Yuma, during the Duel, I could always hear your voice.
That heart of yours that never gives up, your "Bring it to 'Em", has saved me from Tron.
Thank you. Also, please, defeat Tron! You can definitely do it!
So that’s friendship and bonds?
Just when will you get enough out of getting in my way, Yuma!?
Oh well. I will finish off Yuma Tsukumo nice and slowly later... with my own hands!
He is the one who saved my life.
Right. I didn't win this Duel. He gave victory to me.
Additionally, you were entrusted his feelings.
Right, I'll inherit all of Shark's feelings and definitely win!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Using the power of the Heraldry Beasts, Tron is pushing Kaito into a corner.
But Kaito has strategies that may be superior to his.
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"A Horrifying Dark Strategy!
Tron's True Colors Revealed!?"
What?! Tron's mask is...!