Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
III!!
IV, are you ready for your punishment?!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
You did it, Kaito!
Yuma won!
Kaito-sama!
Impossible... For me to...
For me to lose...!
Kaito!
Hey, Kaito!
Kaito-sama!
Haruto... Where is Haruto?
Where is he?!
Hell if I know that.
Then I'll just ask your rotten souls directly!
What?!
I can't retrieve their Numbers!
Wh-What the?
That's...
Astral!
I'm fine.
Pointless.
We're protected by these crests.
Remember that!
We'll give you back the pain you gave us double!
Wh-What the?
H-He disappeared!
Yuma Tsukumo...
III...
Let's go home now.
Wait!
Where is Haruto?!
Give Haruto back!
They both... disappeared.
Haruto...
Haruto is right up here.
Haruto!
You're...!
You're the guy from before!
I will grant Haruto-sama's wish.
Hey, hold up a minute!
Let's go.
- How dare you... How dare you trick-
- Move!
Why?! Why are you...?!
Haruto!
Haruto...
Haruto-sama!
What did... What did you do to Haruto?!
Do not worry. He is still alive.
But he used up all of his power.
Yes, he gave the remainder of his power to you.
What?
This time I'll protect my brother!
It can't be... I did this to Haruto?
What did you do to Haruto?!
Yuma Tsukumo... You are Kazuma-san's son, right?
Huh? How do you know my dad?!
Your dad is alive.
In the Astral World.
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
"Number 44: The Forked Paths of Destiny!
Yuma Abandons Dueling!"
Dad... might still be alive?
What do you mean by that?! Hey!
Dad... My dad's alive?!
Hey, wait up!
What do you mean that my father is in the Astral World?!
What do you mean by that?!
Hey... Astral World's the place you come from, right?
Why would my dad be there?
I'm not sure...
My memories are...
Then if we collect the Numbers and get your memories back... then...
Haruto... He's sick.
Kaito, you're a pitiful soldier working for Haruto's sake.
To save my brother, I sold my soul to the devil.
Then...
Haruto... won't recover.
But if Haruto gets better...
My mission is to destroy the Astral World.
And if my dad's really in Astral World...
God, I don't know!
What the heck should I do?!
That's right!
That's right! My dad might still be alive!
My dad!
Dad!
Y-Yuma!
Calm down!
This mood ain't like you!
Move.
No can do. You can't take a single step beyond this point.
I will protect Haruto.
I won't let you guys do whatever you like with him!
Knock it off, Kaito.
Even if you stand by Haruto's side, you can't do a thing.
You have no choice but to leave this to Mr. Heartland for now.
You know this.
Kaito, why didn't you tell us that Yuma Tsukumo was working with the Original Number?
You know about that?
Pretty much.
I'm the one hunting him.
Funny you should say that.
You got along well during that Tag Duel, didn't you?
You had a nice mood going and everything!
He's my prey.
I'm the one who will defeat him!
Everyone holding a Number is my enemy.
If you stand before me as a hindrance, I'll consider you my enemy.
Haruto! Oh, Haruto!
I'm sorry! I'm responsible for all of this!
Haruto!
Your grief and sadness is much appreciated, Faker-sama.
Mr. Heartland, who stole Haruto's power?!
According to Kaito's report, it was the doing of a group of people wielding special crests.
Crests?
These people will eventually show themselves again during the Duel Carnival.
Very well. Let's take those people apart!
And we will take Haruto's power back from them!
With pleasure.
Yuma, are you serious?
Yeah!
I've got no choice but to go to Astral World and find my dad with my own two hands.
Then the Numbers...
You don't care about the Numbers?
It's not like I don't care about them.
But Dad... Dad might be alive.
That's why, for now I...
For now, you'll have to cut me some slack!
What's with that getup of yours?
Running away from home?
I am not running away from home!
Sis, don't get too surprised!
You're about to say Dad might still be alive, right?
Eh?
I heard about it from Kotori-chan.
So you're trying to find Dad and bring him home?
You're a true blue fool, you know that?
Dad said he found the top of the world, right?
Then I'll go to the top of the world and find Dad there!
Later!
Hold it, Yuma!
Whether it's the top of the world or the Astral World, I'm definitely gonna find you!
Wait for me, Dad!
If that's the case, what about the Duel Carnival?
The heck?
I'm right up here.
Been some time, wouldn't ya say?
Grandpa Rokujuro!
Yuma, are you... abandoning Dueling?
No...
When I heard my cute little disciple was trying his best and standing up challenge after challenge,
I decided to leave the mountain.
And here I am.
But I had no idea such a thing happened.
I'm glad you understand!
Well then, I'm off.
Hold your horses.
Huh?
Yuma, wanna do this?
Sorry Gramps, but I don't really feel like Dueling right now...
I am your master!
You will not abandon Dueling that easily!
If you insist on leaving, you'll do it only after defeating me!
I understand.
I accept!
I apologize Yuma, but I'm not going to help you out during this Duel.
Sure, I'll be able to handle this all on my own!
Come!
Let's go, Gramps!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Haruto's power is beginning to awaken inside me.
My turn! Draw!
Yes! She's here!
I Summon Gagaga Girl!
Heck yeah! Now I've got five Monsters on my field!
Gramps only has one face-down Monster!
This turn will decide it!
Gagaga Girl, attack his face-down Monster!
Gagaga Formation!
Go on, everyone!
Trap Card, open!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
My Monsters were all... wiped out!
When fighting a match, you must also be sure to notice your opponent's set cards.
Hmph! But I've still got the advantage here!
Turn end!
Hm, then I guess it's my turn.
Draw.
Hm, finally here.
I Flip Summon Queen's Knight!
Then I Normal Summon King's Knight!
King, Queen...
It can't be...
This ain't over yet!
When both Queen and King Knight are on the field, I can play the Jack card on the field from my deck!
Come forth, Jack's Knight!
Three Monsters all at once!
I knew it...
It's a three-Monster-for-one combo.
And here we have this!
I activate the Fusion Magic Card from my hand!
I fuse together the three royal knights!
Come forth, Imperial Knight!
I Summon the ultimate Fusion warrior, Arcana Knight Joker!
3800 Attack Points!
You gotta be kidding me!
The tables have turned!
Go, Arcana Knight Joker!
Direct Attack Yuma!
Yuma!
Darn it! Let's play another round!
Guts!!
Huh?
Why are you in such a rush, Yuma?
As you are now, you couldn't even defeat me!
As you are now, you can't see a thing!
B-But... I just don't know what to do.
Do I choose Astral or Haruto?
I can't possibly decide something like that!
So...
You tried to run.
You planned to use searching for your father as an excuse.
I ran away...
Abandoning your rivals and your friends...
You abandoned your family and even your partner.
Your partner must feel the same.
Yuma, look at your feet carefully.
Your feet are strongly rooted in Dueling.
So use Dueling as your guide.
And take your first step from there toward your goal.
Your father is certain to be there.
Because Dueling is the bond that connects you to him!
Gramps...
I... I...
I really do love Dueling!
I love it!
Incredible! This is incredible!
I can't believe it's so difficult to gain control over it, even with the power of the crest in my hands!
Faker, it's almost time...
I'll blow you all the way to the Parallel Universe with the very same power you desired!
Just wait... Just you wait!
Gramps, all I can do now is win in the Duel Carnival.
That's right, Yuma.
If you win the Carnival, Mr. Heartland will gladly do whatever you want.
Hey, Gramps. Who exactly is this Mr. Heartland guy?
What do you mean? Just as the name implies, he's Heartland's symbol and is quite popular with the kids.
I know all that.
I know he's a symbol and that he's popular.
That's not what I mean!
If there's an outer there's an inner.
Wherever you find light, you're bound to find a shadow.
Well, that's the best way to describe it.
Shadow?
Mr. Heartland... You could say the one hiding behind him is the mastermind.
Mastermind?
What's that mean?
He's the one and only scientist called a genius in this decade.
Dr. Faker.
And he's the mastermind?
He's a man surrounded by mystery.
He may be living right now or already dead.
It's rumored that Dr. Faker was the one who created Heartland City.
That Faker...
He was the last one to guide Kazuma.
Your dad and this man called Faker...
And if he's connected to Mr. Heartland, that means...
If I step toward him, my father might be there.
In order to ensure it, I need to continue winning in the Duel Carnival.
What?
That boy from earlier?
Yes. Yuma Tsukumo holds the Original Number.
Yuma... Tsukumo?
Related to Kazuma Tsukumo?
Yes.
It can't...
That can't be possible...
That was the messenger from Astral World...
Yuma Tsukumo...
If you're going to put that card in, you don't need the other one.
Shut up, will ya?! If I want it in, it's in! It's in!
Then you'd be better off replacing it with that Trap.
That one... Which one?
The one right there.
That.
Astral, let's win.
Naturally.
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Did you say Robin?!
That Robin is participating in the Duel Carnival?!
And he's up against Gauche of the Operation Committee!
It's Dimensional ESPer Robin's friends!
Such an awesome, awesome Duel!
Both Robin and Gauche are intense!
That Gauche's Monsters...
No, I've seen that face before...
Robin hasn't given up yet!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"A Nemesis Shows Up Late! Robin VS Gauche"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The WDC, lasting several days, is finally in its final day!
Just one more Heart Piece and my set is complete!
I'm bringing it right to the tournament finals!