It's the Duel Carnival Final!
I started my Duel with Tron in the Sphere Field.
The both of us have Summoned three Numbers, and the real fight begins now!
I won't allow myself to lose!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!
To think you also called out three...
Seems you have some luck on your side.
It wasn't luck!
This is just how skilled I am!
We can win with this battle formation!
Pass right through him, Yuma!
Yeah!
I activate Leviath Dragon's effect!
I detach one of its Overlay Units to increase its Attack Power by 500 points!
Go, Leviath Dragon!
Attack Shining White Knight Illuminator!
Vice Stream!
Once again! Go on, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Attack Genome Heriter!
Hope Sword Slash!
But it's hardly anything to get too excited about.
I still have the 3000 Attack Power Acid Golem on my field!
I'm not done! I activate a Magic from my hand!
Xyz Triangle Force!
When I have three or more Xyz Monsters on my field,
I can destroy one card on my opponent's field!
Go! Destroy Acid Golem!
So you had that card in reserve, did you?
Tron! Now I've defeated all your Numbers!
I'm starting to think it'll actually happen!
Tron doesn't have any set cards or even a hand.
If he doesn't Summon a Monster on his next turn...
Yuma's gonna win!
Go for it, Yuma!
I end my turn now!
So bring it to me!
I'm starting to think you really believe you can defeat me.
Of course I do! For both III and Kaito,
I'm definitely gonna beat you!
You have three Numbers on your field.
It seems the battlefield is finally ready for me to get serious.
Wh-What?
This is my Destiny Draw!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!
Just kidding.
Here I go now! I activate the effect of the Heraldic Beast Unicorn in my Graveyard!
By Banishing this card from the Graveyard,
I can negate the effect of one Xyz Monster in the Graveyard...
...in order to Special Summon it!
Show yourself, Shining White Knight Illuminator!
Then I activate the effect of the other Heraldic Beast Unicorn in the Graveyard!
I'll Special Summon the Genome Heriter in my Graveyard the same way!
It's no use Summoning that Monster!
My Monsters have the higher Attack Points!
No, he didn't bring back the Monsters so he could attack with them.
Huh?
If attacking was his goal, he would have revived the 3000 Attack Power Acid Golem.
I activate the Magic Card, Reborn Medallion, from my hand!
This card revives a Level Four or lower Heraldic Beast from my Graveyard!
Revive! Heraldic Beast Bernard's Falcon!
I activate Bernard's Falcon's effect!
When this card appears on the field,
it can change all the Monsters on my field to the same level.
He's changing the levels of his Xyz Monsters?!
Now he has three Level Four Monsters on his field!
He can't be...
I Overlay Illuminator, Genome Heriter, and Bernard's Falcon!
I build the Overlay Network using these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 69!
Allow me to show you my real trump card!
God Medallion - Coat of Arms!
So that Number has finally appeared...
That's the Number that made quick work of Neo Galaxy-Eyes.
Yuma!
This is the Number that makes up the very essence of Tron's desire for revenge.
How it hurts.
Hatred pours out from within me and suffocates me!
I no longer need this mask.
After all, my Duel with you two will be the last one.
When it's all over, my memories...
...rather, anything and everything, will be stolen away.
I'll make an exception and show you...
...my true form!
Th-That is...
Byron...
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
H-His face...
Yes... While I wandered the threshold between the Parallel Worlds,
"Number 66: The Terrifying Duel!
Arise, Hero of Bond ZEXAL!"
I ended up with the form you see before you.
A heart of revenge is the only thing
that remains in this body of mine!
Tron... Does this mean your true form is a being not of this human planet?!
That AR is so freakin' cool!
I can't believe he even changed his appearance!
That's the Final for you!
They're wrong! That's no AR!
To summarize, that's his true form!
Yuma, run away...!
Guys, keep it together!
Who's going to root for Yuma if we don't?!
Go, Yuma!
Yuma! Astral! Have a look at my power!
This is the ultimate Number I've gotten my hands on!
And this guy has a very special effect.
Coat of Arms can't be destroyed by Card Effects,
and he negates the effects of all Monsters on the field!
He can then make their effects his own!
He can make the effects of other Monsters his own?!
That's right. No matter what Monster it may be,
they are completely helpless before Coat of Arms!
I'll show you that friendship and hope mean nothing!
Coat of Arms' effect activates!
God Medallion Hand!
Their Monster Effects were stolen!
Well, I guess I'll use them right away.
I activate Coat of Arm's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can use the stolen Leviath Dragon's effect!
Meaning Coat of Arm's Attack Power goes up 500 points!
Then I activate the effect of the Heraldic Beast Leo from my Graveyard!
When one of my Monster's Attack Power changes,
I can Banish this card and take the same amount of added Attack Power
and decrease the Attack Power of one of my opponent's Monsters!
Leviath Dragon's Attack Power was...!
Now, go do it! Bury Leviath Dragon!
Take this! God Rage!
The power of his Number is incredible.
Very interesting, Byron.
To think you would go this far to realize your desire for revenge!
How interesting!
A-Are you all right, Yuma?
Yeah, I'm hanging in there.
Hanging in there?
It's about time you give up.
Unlike the useless III, IV, and V, I'm invincible.
That's right. You can say this Coat of Arms represents the difference in strength between parent and child!
Between parent and child, huh?\
It is true that Monster is exactly like you!
What?
I understand completely now!
For III, IV, and even V...
They were great people! They were splendid!
They frantically supported you!
To the very end, all of them were worried about you!
And yet, why do such nice guys...
...have to throw everything away for someone like you?!
It's the natural thing for a parent and child to do for each other!
But that isn't right!
They believed in you!
That you'd return to them some day!
Yuma...
But why couldn't you be a little nicer to them after returning?!
Why'd you start pushing them to a dead end for something as boring as revenge?!
A child like you couldn't possibly understand...!
I do understand!
I understand how lonely it feels when your father goes missing!
Every one of them have been lonely since you went missing!
And they still gave it their best despite the tears it brought them!
Shut up! I won't let you sit here and...
III...
IV...
V...
Memories... of my family.
All of it... All of it, along with my face...
I won't give up on this Duel!
Until I deliver to you what they've all entrusted me with,
I won't ever give up!
Fine then. I'll let you fall prey to my Coat of Arms instantly.
I'll end my turn!
Let's go, Astral!
Yuma...
ZEXAL. If we want to beat him, we have no choice but to use ZEXAL.
Yuma, this Sphere Field is a psuedo-space created to mimic the Parallel Worlds.
It's the same as the Empreror's Key.
We can use ZEXAL here.
However, there are countless people watching this Duel.
It doesn't matter what they think!
As long as it lets me deliver their feelings to him.
Let's do it, Astral!
Come along with me, Yuma!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
I will...
...along with me!
Overlay!
In the moment two distant souls cross over, the legendary power will come forth!
Xyz Change!
ZEXAL!
D-Did he say ZEXAL...?
- What the heck is that?
- He transformed!
That's the power of Yuma and Astral's bond!
W-Why's he doing it when everyone's watching?
To summarize, I wonder myself...
C-Cat...
Maybe they all think it's just AR.
Wow, Yuma looks really cool right now!
He looks like a real hero, doesn't he?
I know, right!
He's so cool!
Yeah! That's a genuine hero!
Hey, Tokunosuke, stop that!
That's ZEXAL! It's our hero who protects Heartland!
And his name's ZEXAL, or not!
ZEXALornot?
Ah! So he's called ZEXALornot?!
I like it!
ZEXALornot!
Um, no... When I said "or not"...
ZEXALornot! ZEXAlornot! ZEXALornot!
W-We might... have a huge misunderstanding
on our hands here... or not.
ZEXALornot! ZEXALornot! ZEXALornot!
Well... Guess it's okay.
Amazing... So many people are cheering for Yuma and Astral.
ZEXALornot! ZEXALornot! ZEXALornot!
I can't believe you were hiding that combination ability of yours this whole time.
Did they say "ZEXALornot"...?
Don't worry about the tiny details.
Just focus on the Duel.
R-Right... I know.
My turn! Draw!
Yuma! Let's Chaos Xyz Change!
Right! I use Aspiring Emperor - Hope as Xyz Material in order to Xyz Change!
Show yourself, Chaos Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
So Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray makes an appearance.
But it's useless. I activate Coat of Arm's effect!
God Medallion Hand!
Hope Ray, I'll steal all of your Monster Effects!
I won't let you! I activate a Magic Card!
Seven Store!
By releasing one of our Xyz Monsters, Seven Store allows us to draw another card!
I select Terror-byte!
And when the Monster is released, for the number of Overlay Units it had,
I can draw another card!
Terror-byte had two Overlay Units attached to it.
So I can now draw three times!
Everything is inevitable in the strongest Duelist's Dueling!
Even the cards they draw can be created by the Duelist!
Let's go, Astral!
All light, give me power!
Gather into my right hand and illuminate a path toward hope!
Shining Draw!
The ZEXAL Weapon's here!
Coat of Arms can negate the effects of its opponent's Monsters and absorb them.
But you can't steal the effect of
the ZEXAL Weapon treated as an Equip!
I see. Very well thought out.
I equip ZEXAL Weapon - Lightning Blade!
This ZEXAL Weapon does not need to be Summoned on the field.
Instead it can be directly equipped to Hope Ray, and it gains 1200 Attack Points!
Then, when this card is equipped,
Magic and Trap Cards we control cannot be destroyed!
Go, Hope Ray!
Among the effects snatched by Coat of Arms,
it doesn't have the power to evade this one!
Hope Sword Lightning Blade!
You're mine!
That's it... I've been waiting for this attack!
I activate Coat of Arm's effect!
When the opponent attacks,
by detaching one Overlay Unit,
this card can destroy one card on the field!
I select Aspiring Emperor - Hppe Ray and destroy it!
What?!
Allow me to show you...
...the original power of the god!
Go, Coat of Arms!
God Slaughter!
I activate the effect of Lightning Blade!
When the Monster equipped with it is destroyed in battle,
I can return ZEXAL Weapon to my hand
in order to negate its destruction!
More of your tricks.
But the battle still continues, you know.
Either way, your little hope play ends here!
Take him down, Coat of Arms!
Crush Hope Way into nothing!
I activate Rescueleton Pig’s effect from my Graveyard!
From the Graveyard?!
When a Monster on our field would be destroyed,
by Banishing Rescueleton Pig from the Graveyard,
it negates the destruction and makes the damage zero!
You saved me, Rescueleton!
Stop fooling around!
I can't believe you had that Monster set up in your Graveyard.
I equip Hope Ray once again with ZEXAL Xyz Change- Weapon Change!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
You sure are persistent. I expected no less for Kazuma's son.
You're the splitting image of that dull man.
I won't ever give up!
Tron! I swear to collect everyone's feelings and send them to you!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
In the Final of the W.D.C.,
this prolonged battle is finally about to end!
And the true goal of the Sphere Field is finally revealed!
Yuma, we can't allow ourselves to lose this battle!
The ZEXAL Weapon was...!
Everything rides on this final draw!
Take our all-new attack!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Believe in Victory! The Final Shining Draw!"
What is going on?!
Just when we finally reveal our cool-looking form,
why'd Tokunosuke have to go name it ZEXALornot?!
The Warrior of Love and Justice, ZEXALornot.
The Warrior of Victory and Courage, ZEXALornot.
Hey, you shouldn't like it!