You're completely surrounded!
Give up any meaningless struggle and surrender! Come down now!
Oh my… I can’t believe the security guard is actually this strict.
That's Heartland's authority alright.
But to think those policemen in Heartland would got so worked up for a single card…
But if this card really possesses that legendary power...
An emergency call from the Heartland Police Station?
I can smell big news coming my way!
Heartland Museum?
So it is an incident!
He's...
Yo!
You've become quite the woman since I last saw you!
It's been a long time, Akari.
Charlie...
Mind your own business!
Was that your doing? During that chaos in the gallery, what on Earth did you steal?
You're quite sharp!
I have something I need delivered today no matter what.
But you see, I got into some trouble.
What are you babbling about?!
Hurry up and turn yourself into the police!
Please don’t say something so heartless!
Hey, would you lend me Kazuma-san’s motorcycle?
His motorcycle?
You must treasure it even now, huh?
Why should I lend it to someone like you?
C'mon, think about or past relationship! I'm begging here!
Oh yeah, I'm a bit hungry. Bring me something to eat, okay?
Who said I'd-
And that's that.
I'll be waiting for 30 minutes over at the plaza in front of the train station.
Don’t forget your make-up!
Wait...! Charlie!
Damn him...
To hell with our past relationship...!
See you later, young lady.
Charlie...
Who am I kidding here?!
I swear I'm gonna pummel him into the ground!
I'm gonna bring it to em' in top form today!
Wait up, Yuma!
Alright, let’s fight one more time today!
You shouldn't let your guard down. The opponents you'll face next all won the first round.
I know!
But, Dueling means fighting against strong gu-
S-Sis?
Yuma, where are you now?
Huh? Somewhere near the train station.
That's perfect, then.
That man should be waiting for me in front of train station. Catch him for me.
Who the heck is that old guy?
I'm very busy right now. Can’t you go yourself?
I'm busy right now too, you know!
Just get going already!
Yes!
Listen! Don't you dare let him get away until I get there, understood?!
Sis is using me again!
Who is this guy?
I don't know.
But If I don't go, I feel like something bad's gonna happen to me!
A Duel?
I activate the effect of Submersible Carrier Aero Shark!
Go! Air Torpedo!!
Shark!
4000 to nothing!
You gotta be kidding me!
Shark is amazing alright!
Shark!
Yuma?
So you did enter the WDC.
I just entered to take care of a situation.
Situation?
When I fulfill my purpose, I'll withdraw from this tournament!
A-And what is that?
The guy I once lost to in National Championship has appeared.
He... IV, lured me into his trap!
He even got innocent people involved!
IV?
His trap?
I'll pay him back!
Yuma, don’t get involved with me.
Shark...
During the preliminary of the World Duel Carnival,
strong Duelists began intense Duels, betting their Heart Pieces on the line!
I will definitely collect 5 Heart Pieces and advance to the Finals as well!
I'll bring it to em'!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
"Number 31: His Name is Charlie!
The Man with the Strongest Luck in History"
Photon Hand!!
The Numbers have been retrieved safely.
Confirmed!
That Shark...
What in the world happened?
Yuma.
Hey, Yuma!
He's over there.
Found him!
Old man!
I'm Yuma Tsukumo!
Tsukumo?
You...
You came to capture me?
That's your sister alright.
That's right.
I'm really busy with the Duel Carnival.
You're in the Duel Carnival?
In that case, care to Duel me?
Duel?
Yeah.
I just wanna test this card's luck.
Hey, you in the hat over there!
You look to be a Duelist.
Then bet your Heart Piece and Duel me!
Interesting.
You're in the Duel Carnival?
Nope!
No. But Yuma, I'll let you witness a rare kind of Duel in this place.
Mr. Heartland, how's Kaito progressing?
There is no such thing as “losing” in his dictionary.
I see.
Among the participants in the Duel Carnival, about 50% of them were already eliminated.
Numbers were flowing to the hands of the strong Duelists, as we expected.
You mean everything is going according to our plan?
I expect that the messenger from the Astral World is here to exact revenge against us.
But after coming to this world, his memories were scattered across the world as 99 Number cards.
This is a rare chance for us!
We have to collect the cards before he recovers his memory, and annihilate the Astral World before he acquires that immense power!
As you wish.
Hey, Charlie!
Why are you betting my Heart Piece without my permission?
What if my Heart Piece is taken?!
I know!
Stop panicking.
But...
There are three Xyz Monsters on his field! What are you going to do?!
And there's a 3900 gap in their Life.
I know, right!
There’s absolutely no chance for a reversal!
I'm so stupid!
"Life is carnival"!
So long as the sun remains as one, my luck will never run out!
"Life is carnival"?
What's this? He still thinks he can win.
Here I go! My turn, draw!
Could it be?! I think it is!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Reload!
This card returns my hand to my deck!
And I draw new cards equal to the amount of cards I returned!
Here it is, here it is!
Huh? Did I screw up somewhere?
That’s what I’ve been saying all this time!
I activate the Magic Card, Triple Ace!
With this effect, If I have three Level One cards with the same name,
I can Special Summon all three!
I Special Summon three Dice Slot Sevens!
They got 100 Attack Points?
So you finally give up the Duel?
Nope! In fact, I'm quite confident.
Dice Slot Seven's effect activates!
Dice?
What the heck is he doing?
"Life is Carnival"!
They will gain levels equal to the number I roll on the dice!
All of them are six!
The probability of three dice all being six is 1/216.
Nice! Now the Level One Diceslot Seven all become Level Seven!
There are three Level Seven Monsters on his field.
Here it comes!
I can feel the wind of strong luck blowing!
I overlay my three Level Seven Diceslot Sevens!
We fuse together!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth! Number 7! Lucky Stripe!
Isn’t that…?
A Number?
So he's a Numbers user?
Then I activate the Magic Card, Dream Dice!
By tossing this die, if a six shows up, the Attack Power of all Monsters my opponent controls become zero!
However, if a number other than six shows up, my Monster’s Attack Power will become zero!
What?!
Six! He got six again!
Bingo!
Now all your Monster’s Attack Power will become zero!
Until now, the odds of getting consecutive sixes is 1/1296!
Go, Lucky Stripe!
I will take damage, but it'll be a mere 700!
Boy are you wrong.
I activate the effect of Lucky Stripe!
When this card battles, by detaching one Overlay Unit,
I can toss a die!
And during this turn, its Attack Power becomes the multiple of that value!
Here's the final blow! Kindly accept my good luck!
Now Lucky Stripe’s Attack Power is six times 700, 4200!
Impossible!
Just like the rumors said...
No, it's even stronger. This guy's something else.
As long as I have this, the surgery tomorrow...
I can’t believe it! He brought a huge reversal in one turn!
Indeed, that isn't your average Dueling.
What strong luck he has!
Until now, the odds of getting consecutive sixes was 1/7776.
You must be cheating! There's no way all of them were six!
What? What's happening?
Charlie McCoy! You are completely surrounded!!
Give up and surrender!
Whoops, looks like I overdid it a bit.
Put both of your hands on your head! Hurry up and abide!
Yeah, yeah.
But I told you before. You can't possibly catch me.
As long as I have this card, that is.
Be careful, everyone! I'm about to absorb all of your luck!
What? The Numbers!
My cards!
Yuma!
Yuma, run!
What are you doing? Run!
That’s…
- My cards!
- What happened?
Did ya see that?
I have the strongest luck.
That’s what I’ve been saying! I will absorb luck! I told you to be careful!
Life is Carnival!
So long as the sun remains as one, my luck will never run out!
Yuma, say sorry to your sister for me! Peace!
Give my cards back, you bastard!
Yuma!
What in the world is causing all this commotion?
Sis!
Where’s that guy?
He’s no longer here…
So Charlie really was behind all this.
But that damn guy...! I even brought the motorcycle and some rice balls with me...
So… the card he used was stolen from the gallery?
Most likely.
Supposedly, whoever owns that card will be instantly granted super luck.
Anyone who's owned this card in the past became instant millionaires or famous stars.
It’s like a card that will guide you to the lucky path.
Awesome...
Then who is that Charlie guy anyway?
He was Dad's classmate back in university.
Inspired by Dad, he started calling himself an adventurer, to the level of a treasure hunter.
A big fool always traveling around the world.
Just when I started thinking it'd been a while since I last saw him, he starts making such a mess of things...
Listen, Yuma! You better find him!
Of course! That guy has my cards, after all!
Bring it to 'im!!
Okay, we should get moving!
Do you have any clues?
We won't find him searching blindly in the dark.
Then what should we do?
He’s been saying "life is carnival" several times. I remember that from somewhere.
86th street, Area B?
Yeah. I saw it once when we were riding the monorail.
"Life is Carnival"?
That slogan was written on it.
Maybe that’s where he saw it as well.
Does it have anything to do with that guy?
I can't be certain...
Then we'll have to see it for ourselves!
Isn’t that the direction towards B Area?
The evacuation of passengers and staff is completed.
The monorail has stopped operating.
We already cornered the suspect!
This train won’t move! We won’t let you get away again!
Heartland Police are seriously persistent!
Though it'll be a bit of a problem if you forget I hold this card...
Please wait… wait, passenger!
No matter how many of you there are, you can’t stop me!
The monorail has started operation!
I lost control of the helicopter!
Now the train is carrying the suspect to the B Area!
Sis! I found him! He's currently on the monorail!
The monorail, you said?
I can’t believe you actually found me. But that's Kazuma-san's son for you.
Cut the smalltalk! Gimme my cards back!
Alright, calm down!
This monorail is currently not being controlled by the main quarter.
In other words, we are directly headed to their location.
What do you think? Care to have a Duel with me before we reach the station?
A Duel?
If you win, I'll give the cards back to you.
Yuma, we have to recollect the Numbers.
All right... Let's Duel!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Duel Target, locked on!
AR Vision - Link established.
Wait, Yuma!
Duel!!
What the hell are those idiots doing?
Is this really the time to be Dueling?
You're so loud! Who cares about the time and location?!
But if this train is really not being operated, who's controlling the breaks?!
Who cares who's controlling... the brakes?
Don’t be afraid, Yuma!
Life is Carnival!! Everything is based on luck!
Let’s enjoy this Duel!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Charlie, the man holding the card with the strongest luck, Number 7!
We are completely helpless if front of his miracle!
The chance of us winning this turn is zero.
His Life's at 10,000 points!?
Yuma! We're close to the destination!
I'll use everything I got in this Duel! That's what I learned from my Dad!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Insurmountable Luck! Number 7, Lucky Stripes!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Kotori, let me teach you how to Duel!
You teach me?
Let's see, first the deck-
Minimum 40 cards, 60 cards maximum.
Eh, about your opening hand...
Five cards!
Uh, in the very first turn...
You cannot declare an attack.
Kotori-sensei...