He who opens this door shall obtain a new power.
However, as the price for this power...
...you shall lose that which is most important to you.
That which is... most important to me?
Ouch...
That dream again...?
Oh, crap!
I'm late!
Late, late!
You read, Desk?
I'm requesting for you to clear a space
for the 3:00 delivery, understand?
I'm feeling pretty confident.
Big Sis Akari!
You could have woken me up, you know!
I'm busy with news delivery in the morning.
You're in middle school. Wake yourself up!
I'm heading out!
Ah, Yuma!
Have you eaten your breakfast yet?
I don't need breakfast!
I'm running late!
Wha-?!
What do you think you're doing, Grandma?!
Breakfast is the greatest energy source there is.
So go eat!
Understood! Will do!
Disposing.
Move it~!
Spinning~
My bad!
Yuma!
Tetsuo!
Time for our usual match!
Don't think you can...
...win against me that way!
- Let's do it!
I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Whamo!
Darn!
Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning.
My deck!
Cut it out, you guys!
Trash.
My deck is not trash!
Waste. Waste.
It's not a waste of a deck either!
No talent. No talent.
You guys're doing it on purpose!!
Hey, Kotori.
That's Yuma-kun, isn't it?
M-Maybe...
You're such an idiot!
That's impossible, dude!
There's no way you can jump 20 hurdles!
I'll fly right over a challenge this easy!
I'M GONNA BRING IT TO 'EM!
Are you all right, Yuma?
I brought it to 'em~
What a moron!
You can do it!
It's impossible!
No way he can pull that off!
I won't have the will to do this if I don't go all out!
I'm gonna bring it-
Yuma!
As the answer to this problem indicates,
the basis of your paper will be-
Geez... You really are a dummy!
It's a challenge!
I'm bringin' it!
Bringin' it to 'em!
So you say... but you didn't complete any of them!
You just don't get it, Kotori.
All that matters is that I bring it to 'em in another try!
As long as I never give up, I'll accomplish them one of these days.
No matter how many tries it takes.
'Coz I got this key of mine!
That's a memento of your father and your mother from one of their travels, right?
Yup! This key's gonna open the door to countless possibilities!
Oh?
Does it really have the power to do that?
Nope!
It doesn't?
But I feel like I can bring it to 'em
so long as I have this key with me!
Gonna bring it to 'em!!
But what really makes me want to
bring it to 'em most of all...
Got it!
Gonna do this!
Go on!
D-Gazer, set!
I'm gonna be the World Champion of Dueling!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
"Numbers 1:
"I'm Gonna Bring It to 'Em!"
Okay, who should I play with today?
So you can use more of your "willpower"?
Way to bring the tension down!
I just gotta bring it to 'em and one of these days, I'll overcome my losing streak!
Yuma, over there.
It's Tetsuo!
Yuma, look at Tetsuo-kun's opponent.
Shark!
Exceeds Summon!
When two Monsters of the same level
are on the field at the same time,
I can use those Monsters as material
to Exceeds Summon a Monster!
I Overlay the Level Three Skull Kraken and Big Jaws!
Exceeds Summon!
Come to me, Submersible Aero Shark!
Exceeds Summon?
Yeah! The strongest point of Exceeds Summoning is
that instead of going to the Graveyard, the Monsters used as material become Overlay Units
and act as supports for the Exceeds Monster.
I don't have even one Exceeds Monster on my own.
But they're really awesome, aren't they?!
Go, Aero Shark!
Direct Attack!!
Tetsuo...
As we agreed, I'll be taking this.
What do you think you're doing with Tetsuo's deck?
And who might you be?
I'm Yuma Tsukumo!
I'm this guy's classmate.
You obviously got no clue who it is you're talking to.
Oh, I know, all right.
He's the most notorious in this school.
Shark!
I'll give you that, at least.
But this is my legitimate reward.
What?
In that Duel just now, the two of us bet our decks.
Why would you do something like that?
These guys said I'm a poser Duelist with no talent and that I'd never get anywhere.
Then I'm just gonna beat this guy in a Duel and get your deck back!
Stupid! Shark-san is so skilled that he's already participated in tournaments.
He's no opponent any of you can defeat!
I know all that!
I'm also aiming to be the Duel Champion!
Did you just say the Duel Champion?
Do you have any clue just how far
one must go to be the Duel Champion?
Well...
I'm not quite sure...
Then don't talk so casually about it!
I-I can dream, can't I?!
"Dream", eh?
If you want me to return this deck, you'll have to offer me whatever's most important to you in its place.
What's most... precious to me...?
Wh-What do you think you're doing?!
Hmph. This appears to have considerable importance to you.
Give it!
Shall I use this to teach you the true meaning of the word "value"?
Only when you lose your precious something...
...do you realize its true worth!
How could you?!
Your precious something bas been shattered.
And now it's ancient history!
A pity it is, but I can't return the deck to you now.
That's dirty, Shark!
Stop it!
But I'll offer you a chance.
Since you were prattling about being the future Duel Champion, I'll challenge you to a Duel.
If you win, I'll give this deck back to you.
But if I win...
...your deck is mine!
This Sunday, at the plaza in front of the station.
If you want the deck back, be there.
He who opens this door shall obtain a new power.
However, as the price for this power...
...you shall lose that which is most important to you.
I just... can't...
Yuma, are you gonna try for the 20 hurdle jump again today?
Not today.
Yuma.
Yuma!
Ain't you gonna bring it to us?!
Maybe some other time.
C'mon! Cheer up already, Yuma!
I know...
But... it's like I can't work up the strength...
...now that my key's been broken.
I can't bring it to anyone...
Yuma.
Yuma!
Tetsuo!
Yuma, are you planning to go to the Duel tomorrow?
I... I suppose.
Don't go.
Huh?
You can't handle it.
You don't know that yet!
How can you beat Shark when you couldn't even beat me?!
Besides... This is all my fault, anyway.
I don't want to create any more debts.
You're misunderstanding.
Huh?
I'm not going there for you.
He broke what's important to me right before my eyes!
I can't just back out!
Neither my Dad or my Mom would run away!
I'm gonna fight him for me!
Yup!
Do what you want!
Guess I'll give you this.
You found it for me?!
I just happened to stumble upon it!
How the heck do you even use this card?
This is the deck Dad built.
If I can use it properly, I think it'll be pretty strong.
I'm headed out!
Yuma!
Wh-What is it, Grandma?
Here!
What is this?!
Take it with you.
You won't be at your best on an empty stomach.
I'll give you some credit for actually showing up.
But if you had run away with your tail between your legs, you could have at least saved your deck.
I'd rather quit being a Duelist than run away from jerks like you!
I just gotta do it!
I'm gonna bring it to you!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Duel Target: Lock-on!
Link between A and B has been established.
Duel!!
You can do it, Yuma!
Here I go!
My turn!
Draw!
The strongest Monster in my hand is...
I Summon Zubaba Knight!
I can't attack, since it's the first turn and all.
So I'll end my turn with that!
Hmph. So your card has 1600 Attack Points, does it?
And that's your strongest?
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Big Jaws!
It's got 1800 Attack Points?!
Zubaba Knight has 1600 Attack Points.
While Big Jaws has 1800.
Holding a battle while in Attack Position results in the one with lower Attack Power being destroyed,
and according to the rules, you receive damage.
You had a Monster stronger than Zubaba Knight in your hand?!
You should've played a small fry that weak in Defense Position.
Then again, even assuming you played a Monster more powerful,
it would have been meaningless.
I activate the Magic Card, Aqua Jet!
It raises the Attack Power of a Water-Attribute Monster by 1000 points until the End Phase of my turn.
There it is!
Shark-san's Magic Combo!
To battle!
Go, Big Jaws!
Big Mouth!!
Babaso!!
Zubaba!
I set one card face-down.
I end my turn.
Darn it!
You only reduced my Life by 1200 points!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
I'm counting on you, Gagaga Magician!
What?
An Attack Power of 1500 in Attack Mode?
What a huge miscalculation!
No, you're wrong!
I equip the Wonder Wand from my hand to Gagaga Magician!
The Monster equipped with Wonder Wand gains 500 Attack Points!
If you're gonna raise your Attack Points, I can also power up using Equipment Magic!
All right!
That means its Attack Power is greater than Big Jaws!
Go, Gagaga Magician!
Attack Big Jaws!
Way to completely disregard my set card!
Trap, activate!
A Trap Card?!
Zeus' Breath!
When my opponent's Monster attacks,
this card negates their attack!
Also, I can inflict 800 points of damage for every Water-Attribute Monster I have on the field!
My Big Jaws is a Water-Attribute Monster.
Meaning you will take 800 points of damage.
Shit!
That's right! I got a Trap Card!
Sweet!
I set one Trap Card face-down and end my turn!
Yuma, both Magic and Trap Cards can be set face-down.
But you shouldn't yell out which one it is!
Gosh! Get your act together!
What a loser!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Skull Kraken!
It's got 600 Attack Points.
Okay! He doesn't have a Monster with higher Attack Power than Gagaga Magician!
You think it'll be that easy?
I activate Skull Kraken's effect!
When Skull Kraken is Summoned, I can destroy one Magic or Trap Card on my opponent's field!
I destroy Wonder Wand!
What?!
Now Gagaga Magician's Attack Power has fallen below Big Jaws!
Shoot!
Eh?
Now Shark's gathered two Monsters on his field!
This is the same situation as when I Dueled against him!
He's planning to Exceeds Summon!
Yuma just can't win!
Yuma...
What's wrong?!
You seriously thought you could become Duel Champion with those clumsy skills?!
It's no use.
Without my key, I just can't...
With the key broken, I just can't get anything right!
If only my key wasn't broken...!
It's all because you keep clinging to that
thing that you can't win a Duel!
Say that again!
I just thought of something nice!
After I steal your deck from you,
I'll shatter that key beyond repair right before your eyes!
You bastard...!
Because you're the kind of guy who can't do a thing on his own!
Cut the crap!
I'm not like that!
No matter how many times I fail...
No matter how many times I'm laughed at...
I've always brought it to 'em, and that hasn't changed!
Because I am who I am and I believe in myself!
I haven't even come close to bringin' it to you!!
The key...!
Now, open the door!
Th-This place...!
Open the door.
Once you do, you will receive a new power.
However, as the price for this power...
...you shall lose that which is most important to you.
Now I'm really gonna bring it to 'em!
Ouch...
What the?!
Wh-What was that just now?
A dream?
No...
What's going on?
What in the...?!
Power is swelling up inside me...
Come, call to me.
"Numbers".
I Overlay my Level Three Big Jaws and Skull Kraken!
I construct the Overlay Network using these two Monsters!
Come, Numbers 17!
Revice Dragon!
Numbers?!
That's not the Monster he called when fighting against me!
Then... what is it?
I have no idea.
I've never heard of "Numbers" before.
I activate Revice Dragon's effect.
Once per turn, I can use its Overlay Units,
and raise Revice Dragon's Attack Power by 500 points!
What?!
Go, Revice Dragon!
Vice Stream!!
Yuma!
This match appears to be over.
It'll be decided in my next strike!
Ow...
Shit...
I guess I really can't...
Stand.
And win.
Who the heck are you?!
Let's begin the Duel!
Here's this week's question!
Among the many cards available, there are three types.
Magics and Traps.
And what's the last type?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
This weird dude suddenly appeared by my side!
It's my turn!
I can't afford to lose this Duel!
Next time on "Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal"!
"My Name Is Astral"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
And the answer is... it's a Monster!
You really need Monsters to have a passionate battle!
What Monster's gonna show up next week?
I can't wait!