So...
III, does that mean you wish to meet Yuma Tsukumo?
That's right. During that duel, we didn't lose to Kaito...
We lost to the strength of Yuma Tuskumo.
Just how can he manage to duel like that?
Just what is his power?
I want to confirm it with my own eyes.
That's fine, III.
Tron...
If you wish to do that, why not just meet him in person?
Isn't there anyone around to duel with me?
I'm begging you!
No?
Hey! You want to?
Nope.
Hmph. Then what about you? I mean YOU!
Aaoch! That hurts!
Alright, Yuma! Just calm yourself!
I know, but...
But I don't have enough Heart Pieces yet...
The preliminaries will be over today, you know.
Ah! If I don't hurry...
Wait, Yuma!
Wait! Geez...
Duel, duel!
Calm down, Yuma!
It's only natural for a duelist to want to duel.
This isn't the time to be saying that!
Hey! Are you alright? Hey!
Just what on earth is going on?
Shark...that Shark guy...
This is...
Horrible...
Don't tell me it's Shark!
Shark...
Hey, Shark! What on earth are you doing?
Hey! Wait... what's happening to you?
I'm simply going to continue fighting my way through the Duel Carnival.
You...?!
My only motivation right now is...
a heart full of revenge and hatred.
Shark...
Remember this, Yuma.
You are my foe as well.
Shark...
Wait! Shark!
Move!
No, I won't move!
You bastard...
If you have to go past me, Shark, you'll have to duel me!
A duel, you say?
Yes, that's right.
Let's finish this here and now!
Interesting...
In that case, I'll rip you to shreds with my own two hands!
Come, Shark!
Yuma, you shouldn't fight him carelessly!
Shut up! Just be silent!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Yuma is dueling with Shark?
During the duel before, his Number left a shred inside Shark's heart.
Shark's heart was contaminated by hatred.
Yuma, show me just how you plan to duel him.
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Go, Big Jaws! Attack Gagaga Magician!
Number 46: Fighting For His Family:
The Gentle Avenger, III"
Big Mouth!
Gagaga!
Then Attack directly! Go, Hammer Shark!
Trap card, open!
Tiny Resistance!
This card lowers the ATK of my opponent's monster equal
to the ATK of one LV4 or lower monster with 1000 or lower ATK which rests in my graveyard!
This attack... is nothing!
Oh? Then what about this guy?
I overlay the LV3 Big Jaws and Hammer Shark!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Submersible Carrier Aero Shark!
I activate Aero Shark's effect!
For every card in my hand it inflicts 400 points of damage to my opponent!
There are 3 cards in my hand! Take this! Air Torpedo!
Yuma!
Do you understand now, Yuma? Don't get involved with me...
Not yet... This isn't over yet...
Get more serious, Shark!
You bastard!
If you don't come at me, I will!
My turn, draw!
I summon Gogogo Giant!
I will end my turn like this.
What?!!
Why?
Why, Yuma?
You could have destroyed his monster if you attacked with Gogogo Giant!
Just what are you thinking?
It's alright, that's how I duel!
Yuma, you...!
What is with this duel...?
It was the same last time!
You duel differently than us, who duel for revenge.
But I...
Yuma, why would you duel like that?
Is it really all right to let III go?
Yuma Tsukumo has a different power than ours.
When meeting him, III's heart might be shaken.
It's fine. III is a kind child.
Kind?
Yes... which is why III will definitely come back.
That's the kind of kid he is.
Show yourself! Black Ray Lancer!
It's bad! Yuma!
Go, Black Ray Lancer!
Attack Gogogo Giant! Black Spear!
Sorry, Gogogo Giant!
Then I attack you directly with Aero Shark!
Take this! Big Eater!
Yuma!
Why are you playing to lose?
Not enough... It's not over yet, Shark!
Alright, come, let me take a look at your true strength!
Yuma... Don't tell me you...
Yes... that's right.
This duel...I...
I don't care about winning or losing!
Yuma...
Shark! Don't you hate me?
Then hit me with all of that hatred!
Come at me with all your might!
If that way can make your hatred disappear, then so be it!
You little...
Because of hatred, because of revenge...do you feel happy that way?!
Aren't you just a guy who just loves dueling?
But now, don't you hate dueling as well?
Seeing you act like that... I...
I don't want to see that!
Geez, what are you doing?
I- it can't be helped! I'm hungry!
Goodness... You're such a man.
What's wrong with that? That's why I am saying it can't be helped!
It made a sound by itself!
You don't have any delicacy at all!
What do you mean by delivery?!
You still don't get what I'm saying?
The power of the Numbers... has disappeared from Shark's heart!
Geez, you are such a fool!
What?!
I quit!
So idiotic!
Wait, Shark, wait! Hey!
Seeing an idiot like you, I'm losing my drive.
What do you mean 'idiot'?
Let's resume this duel during the Finals.
Hold it, Yuma!
That hurts!
What's wrong, Kotori?
What about the finals now?
If you happened to lose to Shark, wouldn't you have lost all of your heart pieces?
Huh? That..that's right!
I completely forgot that!
I won't criticize you for taking care of your friends,
but if you happened to lose that one, both the Numbers and my life would have disappeared.
Sorry! Everything is out of my whim and made me forgot about Numbers and such!
Isn't that your promise with your father?
'I will definitely become Duel Champion!'
No...but...even my own father, at that circumstance...
He would definitely stop that with all of his might!
Therefore, I think he will definitely forgive me!
For goodness sakes...
Yuma's father...?
So this person is Yuma's father.
This is...
Oh you...
Oh, um... I...
Excuse me... who can...
Duel with me...?
Grandma... what's wrong?
Hey you, what are you doing...?!
Yuma, awesome - Awesome!
This is a mask from the Aztecs!
Those are stone tools from 2,000 years ago!
That's the iron arrow heads made in Hittite.
Wow, a necklace from the Inca!
All of them are great no matter how you look at them!
Just like my favorite card.
Look!
Aztec Mask Golem...
That's right.
The deck I am using using is called OOParts.
OOParts are evidence of a connection between this world and different dimension!
In this world there are multiple dimensions overlapping each other!
And some people believe that OOParts come from there.
My father was devoting his studies toward this direction!
Ohhh! And my dad is an adventurer!
Everything here belongs to my dad!
Is that so? Your father must be a great person!
Ah...I guess...
This isn't the time to be talking about this!
Because of you guys, Haruto...
Sorry!
Huh?
I apologize about Haruto!
III...
But...that's the only thing I can do.
You...
Yuma, for revenge...
I fought until now relying on the power of hatred.
But after watching your duel,
I think a power besides hatred might exist as well.
Huh?
How can you got so worked up for others?
Just what is your power?
My...power?!
That's right.
I am different from you.
How can you fight like that?
My power... my...
I wouldn't know something that complicated!
Huh?
Anyway, it's called 'Bring it!'... 'Bring it to 'Em'!
'Bring it to 'Em'...
Yeah... A belief of never giving up regardless of the circumstances, and never forgetting to challenge yourself!
That's what my dad has taught me!
Your father...
Hey, Yuma! Lunch is ready!
Sis!
Kotori-chan and others can join us too.
I'm hungry!
Yuma! You should say 'Itadakimasu' first!
I... I know.
That is good.
Geez, you act like that every single time!
Hmph!
Whoa! It looks delicious!
Okay, you over there. Have a seat.
Ye.. yes.
Itadakimasu!
Whoa! This Duel Supper is great! One more!
Um...
Say 'Itadakimasu' first...
Itadakimasu...
Tea...Tea...Tea is ready!
Here. You suck.
I do not suck!
Shut up. You suck.
So hot!
Why do you suck so bad?
D-Don't you laugh!
Enough, Yuma, just eat quietly!
I know that!
But if I don't eat quickly and start to duel...
Talking about cards during meal time is forbidden!
No way!
Give my cards back, Sis!
No!
Just give them back!
I told you I won't!
Right, look, look Big Brother!
Aztec Mask Golem!
Father gave it to me!
It's not fair that only you got one! Give it!
C'mon! Give it back, Big Brother!
No!
C'mon, Big Brother!
Then come get it!
Geez!
He gave it to me!
Stop, you two!
You will get scolded when father gets back.
Tch, I know!
Yes...
Give it back, Big Brother.
Here.
Be good boys and I will teach you how to duel next time.
Wow...
Really?
Sure!
Big Brother...
I'm so close to five! I'm definitely gonna get 'em!
Can you really become Duel Champion?
Right. My family was once like that too.
I will! It'll be a breeze!
Don't get full of yourself.
III?
What's the matter?
You...
I'm sorry. Please excuse me!
Hey, III!
Wait, III!
Yuma, I finally understand after seeing your family.
Your power, your 'Bring it to 'Em'...
It is the power to protect the smiles of your family and friends!
But..I...my family is different from yours!
From the moment we sworn to battle for revenge,
the smile on my family's faces vanished!
But...when the revenge is over, everyone will definitely smile again!
But, Yuma! As long as you exist, our revenge will never happen!
Thus for my family,
I have to defeat you!
Why? Why did it turn out this way?
The same goes for Haruto!
That's our family's decision!
III!
I don't have any emotion other than hatred!
You're lying!
Yuma!
Tonight, I will be waiting for you over there!
It's a map.
What?
Let's finish this once and for all!
III!
III...
Welcome back, III.
Tron... I...
You don't need to say anything. I know.
You desire power, right? In order to defeat him?
Yes!
Yuma, he is very powerful!
Are you really going?
I know... but I...
...want to talk more with him.
I want to know his real feelings.
That's why I will duel with him.
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
During the preliminary of the Duel Carnival, the final battle with III has started.
Be careful, he is different than before.
He is a friend I once dueled with, so I will learn everything about him!
Don't get engulfed by the power of Evil!
Just....what on earth am I doing?
Why would I duel like that?
Next, time in Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal:
Yuma Gives Up!? The Stolen "Bring It To 'Em!"
Yuma, don't tell me you...
The monster we introduce this time is String Devil Muzumuzu Rhythm!
When this Xyz monster battles, you can double its ATK.
That icky rhythm makes me feel itchy!
(Muzumuzu = "Creepy", "Itchy")
This caper was a lot of work, my dear Watson.
(Gekimu = hard work)
That's Holmes!