Yuma... Is this really okay?
III, his conviction is for real.
We don't even know whether we will win for sure.
I know that!
But I want to know that guy's true feelings,
and I truly desire to have a real duel with him.
After all, you can learn everything from the opponent through dueling. Aren't you the one who said that?
Understood.
I won't say anything more.
But you only have 4 heart pieces so far,
so whether you can qualify for the Finals of the WDC all depends on this duel.
Yuma!
Everyone! All of you guys have come!
Of course!
Cat, isn't this the final battle?
I came to here just to see Yuma's face when he loses instantly!
To summarize, we can't miss this!
So you guys actually thought I would lose?!
Just kidding, that's not what we think!
We all expect you to win, Yuma-kun.
Huh?
Considering you already got this far... there's no doubt you're the strongest duelist among us!
Do your best!
You can definitely become the champion, cat!
Everyone...
Alright, let's go!
What's wrong, V?
You look quite distressed.
We can't afford to underestimate the power of the messenger from the Astral World.
No need to worry. III will win for sure.
Since he already acquired strength equivalent of the pain he just endured.
A power that strong?
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Number 47: Yuma Gives Up!?
The Stolen "Bring It To 'Em!""
Sorry for the wait, III!
Yuma, in order to defeat you, I just obtained a new power.
A new power?
Be careful, Yuma.
After the encounter with you and your family, I confirmed something
That I may have to defeat you in order to get back my family!
I just want to know your true feelings!
That's why I want to fight you!
We may become friends after the battle and able to learn everything from each other!
This is dueling!!
Everyone who stands on that side are all my friends who created bonds with me through dueling!!
Thus I strongly believe there must be such bond between you and me!
Let's go!
Come!
Duel disk, set!
D-gazer, set!
AR-Vision: link established.
Duel!!
I will go first!
My turn, draw!
After obtaining power from Tron, in my current state...
Astral, I can clearly see you!
You are the one who's been assisting Yuma all this time, right?
But even with you as my opponent, I won't lose!
I activate the Field Magic OOPart City Babylon!
That's...
What's this?
Here I come, Yuma!
I special summon the OOParts Monster Tula Guardian!
When there is a field Magic on my field, I can special summon this card from my hand!
Then I normal summon the OOParts Monster Golden Shuttle!
I activate Golden Shuttle's effect!
Once per turn, I can increase this monster's level by one!
Is it coming?!
I overlay the LV5 Tula Guardian and Golden Shuttle!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz summon!
Show yourself, No. 33!
OOParts Super Weapon Machu Mach!
He already summoned Machu Mach... that fast?
I set one card face-down, and end my turn.
Alright, try to beat me, Yuma! With your dueling!
To duel in order to hurt someone is not dueling at all!
That's not the 'Bring it to 'Em' my father has taught me!
'Bring it to 'Em'...
It's a shame that I won't allow you to use that!
Here I come, III!
My turn, draw!
Yes! Here goes!
Don't be so hasty, Yuma!
He already has Machu Mach on his field. The top priority right now is to build defense!
Plus that momentum of his...
seems quite different than before.
Anyway, you can't beat him by attacking recklessly!
I know that!
Alright, I set a monster in face-down defense position!
And set one card, ending my turn!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Magic card from my hand, Sarcophagus of Palanque!
When there is a card that includes "OOPart" in its card name on my field, I can draw 2 cards from my deck!
Then, during the turn I activated a normal Magic, I can special summon this monster from my hand!
Come forth, OOParts monster Aztec Mask Golem!
Ah... that's III's...
Just like my favorite card! See?
Aztec... Mask... Golem?
Go, Aztec Mask Golem!
Palanque Roar!
As I expected, it's Gogogo Golem!
If both of their ATK are 1500, then this battle is a draw.
Gogogo Golem won't be destroyed!
Plus, when Gogogo Golem is in defense position, once per turn, it cannot be destroyed by battle.
That way I can survive Machu Mach's attack as well!
My goal isn't battle at all!
I normal summon the OOParts monster Cabrera's Catapult!
A monster with zero ATK?!
I activate Cabrera's Catapult's effect!
By releasing one monster on my field,
During this turn, the ATK of one monster my opponent controls will become zero!
What...?!
Take the curse, Gogogo Golem!
Gogogo Golem!
It's getting troublesome. This combo is...
At this moment, I activate Machu Mach's effect!
Machu Mach's effect is, when a monster's ATK changes,
once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit,
the equal to the changed amount will be inflicted as damage to my opponent!
In other words 1800 damage!
Infinity Cannon!
Since Cabrera's Catapult just used its effect, it switched to Defense Position.
With this, I will end my turn.
Ah, it's no good!
It's... nothing at all!
This III guy, his duel is completely different than before! Just what happened...
But... if this is his ace, I got an idea!
This is my duel!
I want to win this with my own dueling!
Yuma...
My turn, draw!
I summon Gagaga Magician!
Activate the Equipment Magic!
Shut up, I know!
I activate the Equipment Magic Bound Wand!
Then once per turn, Gagaga Magician can become any level between 1 to 8!
Geez, I already said I know!
I change Gagaga Magician's level to 8!
Alright, Bound Wand's effect activates!
The equipped Spellcaster monster gains ATK equal to its level times 100!
Alright!! But won't that trigger Machu Mach's effect?
No. He won't use Machu Mach's last Overlay Unit for this small amount of damage.
Alright, Gagaga Magician, attack Cabrera's Catapult!
I already saw through your attack!
Trap activate! Costa Rican Stone Ball!
What?
This card can negate the opposing monster's attack!
And that monster cannot declare an attack during your next turn!
Gagaga Magician!
How's that, Astral?
Yuma, set the card.
Ah! Geez, it's all your fault!!
I set one card, and end my turn!
At this moment, Gagaga Magician's level returns to normal.
The ATK raised by Bound Wand's effect will go down as well!
My turn, draw!
I activate Field Spell OOParts Ancient City Babylon's effect!
Once per turn, by removing one OOParts monster in my graveyard,
I can special summon one OOParts monster with same level from my graveyard!
I banish Golden Shuttle!
Alright, pull Aztec Mask Golem out from graveyard!
I change Cabrera's Catapult to attack position!
And once again set Aztec Golem as ammunition!
You... III...
What happened to you?
Be quiet! It's fine as long as the monsters become my pawns!
You used to like OOParts so much... but look what you did to that monster!
I have changed.
No matter what kind of price I have to pay, I have to defeat you!
III...
I activate Cabrera's Catapult's effect!
This is bad!
Another combo with Machu Mach's effect would...
... would make Yuma only have 300 LP left!
On top of that, if he was attacked by Machu Mach...
To summarize, Yuma-kun would lose!
I was waiting for this moment!
Use Gagaga Rush, Yuma!
Ri... right! Trap activate, Gagaga Rush!
This card's effect is, when Gagaga Magician was targeted by an effect,
...it will negate its activation, and destroy it!
And inflict damage to my opponent equal to the ATK or DEF, whichever is higher, of the monster who used that effect!
What?!
Cabrera's DEF is 1800, eat this damage!
Nice!
Now their LP are even!
Good job!
Ah... Don't tell me you planned that since the beginning...
Now his duel is too fixated on winning, which sometimes can make him extra cautious,
Compared to a reckless guy like you, he is much easier to analyze in terms of strategies!
Sounds like you said something unnecessary...
We will win like this! Yuma!
Sure!
But, it won't be enough just like that.
I will let that guy find his true inner self through this duel!
Yuma's 'Bring it to 'Em'... and Astral's advanced tactics,
Are you telling me their combined power exceeds mine?
III, sacrificing OOPart's monster, that's not your dueling at all!
I have no idea what kind of power you did got, but you should at least duel in your own style!
You won't understand.
A happy person like you, surrounded with friends, would never understand...
...the true agony and pain I've felt... The feeling of having no one by your side...
III... ?!
I finally managed to find my family, but it's already falling apart!
Everything has become twisted!
But even so... I still wish to protect them!
Yuma, you annoy me! Your actions are an eyesore!
III!
Fall into the darkness!
Yuma!
What happened? The Lord's Key?!
To win against Yuma Tsukumo, having strong Numbers is by far not enough.
His father, Kazuma Tsukumo was a brave adventurer.
Such a person's son should not be underestimated.
The Power of the Crest I gave to III will take away the most precious things from Yuma...
Afterwards, what's waiting for him is... a world of despair.
I'll bring it to 'em!
Bring it to...
Bring it...
Bring...
What...
What was it?
Just what am I trying to say?
It seems I forgot the most important thing to me...
Come, climb up, Yuma!
That's impossible!
How can I climb on something this steep?!
No, you can climb on this! (**), Yuma!
Huh? What did he just say? What did you say, dad?
Dad!!
Dad!
Scary, so scary!
Hey... you don't want to challenge that, Tsukumo-kun?
I don't wanna... it's so scary!
How can I jump on something that high anyway?
But how would you know that without challenging it?
I know that... without doing it.
I can't do it... can't do it...
Nice! Perfect!
You are great, good job!
You sissy!
The card you were afraid of was nothing but an Equipment Magic card.
Oh my, what a boring duel!
To summarize, that was an unworthy duel!
Such a cowardly guy is a disgrace to duelists!
Scary... so scary!
Sorry.
Sorry... Sorry!
Scary... So scary... Everyone is looking down on me...
Geez...
- What an annoying guy he is... !
You would become a coward as well if you are trying to approach him...
- Such a disgrace of duelists!!
Scary... Scary!
Why would it be this scary?!
It's gone... Something important to me...
...has disappeared...
Hey, Yuma, hey!
Scary... so scary...
Why would I duel like this anyway...
- What happened, Yuma?!
Obviously it's impossible...
How can I possibly win...
Don't tell me... This all is the power of the crest?!
The 'Bring it to 'Em' has already disappeared from his heart, which means Yuma can no longer see you.
What?! Yuma! Don't be devoured by the evil power, Yuma!
Astral, I won't allow you to interfere!
What...?
This crest also has the power to seal you.
Astral, disappear!
Yuma, your 'Bring it to 'Em' has already disappeared from your memory,
As long as there is no 'Bring it to 'Em', you cannot see neither Astral nor the Lord's Key.
You are no longer a match for me!
Go, Machu Mach! Attack Gagaga Magician!
Yuma! Yuma!
Yuma! Yuma!!
Yuma, disappear within the darkness of despair!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Due to power of the crest, Yuma has lost his 'Bring it to 'Em'.
There is no more fighting spirit within his eyes,
and that heart of a challenger which vows never give up has also vanished.
Then even I too...
Remember it, Yuma!
I... I will surrender the duel...
This is... the last of my strength
Next time in Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
- Astral... dies?!
Yuma...
Don't give up...
The monster we're introducing this week is Drum Devil Tenten Tempo!
You can absorb the opponent's Overlay Units and use them as your own power!
I will use Tenten Tempo to give Yuma a test.
That's eas-
It's the same as three tens.
Wha?!