Come on, summon it! Your Numbers!
With these two monsters, I construct the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!!
Appear, Numbers 39, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!
Yuma used his Numbers?
That guy, but he promised he wouldn't use it...
Aero Shark, direct attack!!
Big Eater!!
Yuma lost...
Don't get involved with me again!
You're kidding...
Even after I used the Numbers...
I special summon UFO Turtle!
In that case, I'll use Gagaga Magician to attack UFO turtle!
Yuma-kun's personality, I just don't get him.
If I lost that badly, there's no way I can get back up so easily.
Ah? Attack power's gone up?
In summary, Yuma-kun is a person without any pride, right?
UFO Turtle, attack Gagaga Magician!
With this, he's lost 20 times in a row.
Damn it!
Heh, so you had a magic card too?
Alright, let's do it again!
You still feel like playing?
Of course!
I'm aiming to become the Duel Champion, afterall!
Now, come at me again!
I can't do this anymore.
What's with him?
Then class rep, you are next!
Eh?
Wait!
Wait up!
Tetsuo-kun!
I didn't think Yuma was that kind of person.
That duel...
He said he wouldn't use the Numbers...
Even if that's the case, that guy...
But, see, that's just because Yuma is an idiot...
I know he's an idiot!
Yuma is an idiot, and full of himself but...
But he never went around telling lies!
Tetsuo-kun!
Yuma...
Shark!
Why not play with us once in a while?
Boss, can't you do something about Shark?
He's always so arrogant...!
You just don't get it, Gingi.
Did you really believe we think of him as one of us?
That guy is pretty famous in the dueling business.
If we tame him to become a star in underground dueling,
We can just sit around and watch the cash flow in.
Plenty of easy money, see?
My turn, draw!!
Alright, let's go!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Shark, who went back to a world of evil..
The way to save him is through a Tag Duel!?
"Numbers 11: Yuma and Shark -
Scar-Ridden Tag Duel!"
Tetsuo!
Tetsuo, let’s duel today too!
I can't duel with you anymore.
That's weird!
What's with the stingy talk?
There are plenty of opponents besides you!
It's useless.
Right now, you can't win no matter who you duel with.
Normally, you would at least try to use childish strategies.
But right now, you're not even using those childish strategies.
Pointlessly, simply attacking over and over again...
What did you say?
You're irritated because of Shark.
Indeed he's an excellent duelist, very talented.
But that's not the only reason he won.
What do you mean by that?
He thoroughly studied your deck,
And saw through the Numbers' weakness.
But what do you know about him?
What do I know?
Maybe something happened to Shark then when he played in the National Duel Tournament.
I heard that's when Shark started turning bad...
Are you serious about this?
Of course we are.
There won't be a another chance like this.
There, look at that.
The centerpiece of today's exhibit,
This super rare deck has been lost for a very long time.
A few days ago, it was rediscovered by chance in another package shipped to the gallery.
And so the deck is now on exhibit.
Oh man! I want it so bad, this deck!
B-But isn't that dangerous?
If we rob the gallery and things like that..
That's gonna put us in jail..
Even if, so what!
Didn't you always go around saying these things?
That you wanna do something big!
T-That's true, but--
Don't worry about it.
We have these guys on our side.
Numbers...!
It's just as the boss said.
Ever since we got these, all our wish has been coming true.
There's no way they'll catch us!
We're protected by the power of these cards.
B-But boss...
What's your problem?
So you won't do it?
No, that's not...
What are you doing over here?
Since you heard all those, then give us a hand too.
Of course you're coming with us, right?
Yeah, no problem.
Alright then, it's decided.
We're going tonight.
Be prepared, you hear?
This is bad...
No matter what, this time..
It's all over...
Leave this town while you still can.
Huh?
I-I can run away?
But why?...
Hurry up and get outta here!
Hm..
Huh?
That's strange, I can't open it..
Checking something out?
Yuma at the library? What a rare sight.
Duel Monsters National Championships?
Yeah, just a little.
The Tarnished Champion Candidate, Kamishiro Ryouga?
Is this about shark?...
This is Shark's past...
Champion candidate Kamishiro Ryouga, disqualified from the nationals for spying on opponent's deck...
Shark...
Shark spying on opponent's deck, hard to believe...
Those are definitely not true!
But, at the library...
I understand.
That duel between me and Shark...
It's wasn't a duel from that kind of person!
My turn!
Now, summon it!
Appear, Black Ray Lancer!
Yuma...
It's you! The guy from Shark's place...
Shark is gonna be a card robber?
Yeah, boss was talking about attacking the gallery...
It's all because of that card!
Ever since boss got that card, they haven't been acting like themselves...
It's the Numbers!
And no doubt, they're planning to make Shark take the blame for all of it!
At this rate, that guy will...
Wait, Yuma!
That's enough, getting involved with Shark like that...
I have to go...
I have no choice but to go.
But why? Why go that far for Shark's sake?
You're wrong!
I'm not going for Shark's sake.
I'm going for my own sake!
I lied to myself.
Even though I said it was for getting Shark out,
But really, I wanted to win too.
I only wanted to win, so I ended up using the Numbers.
I don't want this!
I don't want it to end like this!
That Ginji, where did he run off to?
Just leave him.
But that bastard...!
Well, does it really matter?
We'll let this guy cover his part. Right?
Who the heck are you?
I won't let you get pass this point!
What did you say?
You're that stubborn kid from before.
Look, Yuma.
If you want to continue, then defeat me in a duel!
Duel, you say?
What are you planning?
If you guys win,
My Numbers card is yours to take!
So, he's betting his Numbers?
However, if I win, you'll leave the gallery alone!
That's the same as our cards.
Oh really? So this thing is called Numbers?
We've already gained this much power with just yours and mine..
If we can get that, we'll be invincible.
Now, come at me! Rikuo, Kaio!
You, are you thinking of fighting two on one?
Of course!
There's no way I'll let you become a card robber!
I already told you!
Don't get involved with me again.
How can I just leave you like this?
These guys, they're just using you, that's all!
But I already knew that.
However, I don't have anywhere left to belong.
You're wrong!
You place of belonging isn't something like this!
I'll never give up.
This time I'll break you off from them, you'll see!
You're pushing it too much! Why go this far?
Because we are friends, of course!
No way, I'm not going.
Tetsuo-kun!
It's true that Yuma lied.
But right now he's fighting for his life!
Are you okay with this?
You guys are friends!
Now, talking time is over.
If it's about the Numbers, then that's a different story.
This isn't two on one.
It'll be a three on one fight.
Right, Ryouga?
Fine by me!
Doesn't matter if it's two or three, come at me together!
Sorry, but I'll be siding with this guy.
What did you say?
You..! So you're betraying us?
Shark...
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just sick these guys' babysitting, that's all.
Interesting!
So you're challenging us to a tag duel?
What a bunch of idiots!
You clearly know what’s gonna happen right, Ryouga?
Let's go!
Duel disk, set !!
D-Gazer, set !!
AR Vision, link complete.
Duel !!
I'll take the first turn!
My turn!
Draw !!
I set a monster in defense position.
Then I set two cards face down, turn end.
Yuma, from the looks of things, these opponents are experts at tag duels.
Be careful.
I got it!
Alright next, my turn!
Draw !!
I summon Zubaba Knight!
Let's do this!
Attack the face down defense position monster!
Go, Zubaba Knight!
Wait, Yuma!
Eh?
In a tag duel, you can't attack until everyone's had a turn.
Is that so?
In that case, turn end.
Such an amateur?
This duel will be an easy win.
My turn.
Draw !!
I summon Resent Blizzardon!
Then I set two cards face down.
Turn end!
Against our invincible tag duel,
We'll make you regret you ever challenged us.
My turn!
Draw !!
I summon Big Jaws!
Next, I special summon Shark Sucker!
When there is another fish type monster on the field, I can special summoned this card from my hand.
There's two level 3 monsters.
Gonna go for it?
I overlay my level 3 Big Jaws and Shark Sucker!
With these two monsters, I construct the overlay network!
Exceed Summon !!
Appear, Submersible Warship -- Aero Shark!!
An Exceed Summon after just one turn!
Shark is indeed amazing!
I activate monster effect!
Once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit, I can inflict 400 damage to my opponent for every card in my hand!
I see.
Since there's no way to attack on the first turn,
He inflicted effect damage instead.
There's four cards in my hand.
Because of that, I inflict 1600 damage to Rikuo!
Alright, he did it!
Is that what you think?
Trap activate!
Blizzard Egg, Level 5!
With this card, when a player takes effect damage, they can special summon one level 5 monster from the hand.
However, if they can't special summon, that player takes 500 damage.
That's...
If Rikuo doesn't have a level 5 monster in his hand,
He'll end up taking 500 damage. A risky gamble.
Let's see, level 5, level 5...
I'll special summon level 5 monster, Bontan Lavasaurus!
Next is my turn!
Trap activate! Flame Egg, Level 5!
When a player takes effect damage, an ally can special summon one level 5 monster from the hand.
However if they can't special summon, that player takes 500 damage.
Again, the same move?
I special summon level 5 monster, Mince Icebergdon in defense position!
He had a level 5 monster as well?
You're kidding!
They special summoned two monsters at the same time!
You see? This is our perfect combination.
No one has ever beaten my brother and I in a tag duel!
What's this?
Their sense of total confidence...
This duel, something is not right!
Those guys, could they be..?
Let's go, Ryouga!
Trap activate, Staredown Level 5!
For every level 5 monster on our side of the field, you take 500 damage!
There's two level 5 monsters on our field.
Because of that, damage is 1000!
Take that, traitor!
Shark!
Hmph! Not such a big deal now, aren't you?
I set two cards face down, turn end!
W-What's going on? This duel..
No one is attacking,
But our life just keep on dropping...
Calm down, Yuma.
If you keep that up, we can't win this duel.
That's right...
This duel will decide me and Shark’s future.
We can't afford to lose!
My turn.
Draw !!
I change the face down defense position monster to attack position!
Show yourself, Punch Flamesaursus!
Tag duel?
Why is Yuma together with Shark?
I activate Punch Flamesaursus's flip effect!
This card's level is increased by one, to level 5!
I overlay my level 5 monsters, Punch Flamesaursus and Bontan Lavasaurus!
With these two monsters, I construct the Overlay network!
Exceed Summon !!
Appear, No. 61!
Volcasaurus !!
Numbers..!
This one, it's that guy's...
Numbers...
We did it, big bro!
This game is ours now.
Now let's show them our true terror.
I activate Volcasaurus's effect!
By detaching an overlay unit,
Destroy one of the opponent's monster, and inflict damage equal to its ATK to the player!
I'll destroy Aero Shark!
Mag-max !!
Now take Aero Shark's ATK, 1900 damage, Ryouga!
Shark !!
Is this really a good time to worry about others?
Next it's your turn!
I'll destroy Zubaba Knight!
Mag-max !!
Yuma!
W-What kind of power...
Do you see it now? Our power.
Your Numbers will be ours!
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
There are three kind of trap cards. Normal traps, counter traps. What's the other kind?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
This duel, something is not right.
No matter how they try to play dirty, we'll take our victory fair and square!
I am afraid of losing...
Don't make me laugh--!!
Yuma, go and win.
This card that Shark gave me...
If it's you, you'd notice this for sure!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"A Union of hope! Armored Exceed Activate!"
The answer is...continuous trap!
Using these three kinds of traps, you'll make your opponent speechless!
No.61 - Volcasaurus!
Inflicting destruction and effect damage, a powerful enemy!