Go, Hammer-Rush!
Direct Attack!
C'mon, stand up! This Duel ain't over yet!
I beg you! Please forgive me!
I'll never try to cheat again!
Stand up, you no good bastard!
That's enough already, Gauche.
Huh?
Our true job is to search for Numbers.
Looks like Droite's good spirit saved you.
Now disappear from Heartland City this instant!
Shitty bastard...
I overslept!
That's right, that's right!
It was back during the opening ceremony of the World Duel Carnival.
I'm off!
But after separating from Yuma and the others, I hid here to analyze the other Duelists.
And I ended up sleeping through the entire day!
I gotta start collecting Heart Pieces, or I ain't gonna make it into the finals!
Hold on.
It's already the second day of the tournament.
More than likely, only a ton of strong guys remain.
If I should lose a Duel and lose this thing in the process, it's all over.
I wonder what I should do.
I just thought up a good plan!
I did it! Now I've got four Heart Pieces!
You just need one more to advance to the finals.
No biggie!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Astral's gone.
Astral is?
Well, at least I get to Duel my way while he isn't around.
Numbers... My memories...
Just what in the world am I?
Darn!
Hey, Taichi! What're you doing?
Yuma! Kotori!
Have you seen Tokunosuke?
Tokunosuke?
He's so cruel!
Wow, you're participating in the Duel Carnival, Taichi?
Yup, and you better believe I'm after the championship.
If that's how you feel, I bet you gathered up a considerable amount of Heart Pieces.
No, not exactly... It's a bit pitiful, actually.
Oh?
Come this way!
Wh-What the heck?
Look here.
You collected that many?
Let me see your Heart Piece for a minute.
Hey!
What's the big deal? Give it back!
It's a match!
I'll be taking this Heart Piece.
Wha?
In return, you can pick all the Heart Pieces you want from this bag.
Huh?!
- Huh?!
So you're disqualified?!
Y-Yeah...
I mean, the Heart Pieces all have a specific pattern carved into their edges.
Otherwise they won't fit together.
But the Heart Pieces he gave me were fake!
They were candy!
- Candy?!
I thought they were suspicious looking, so I licked them and this happened.
Thanks to that, the edges are all stuck together.
This happened because you tried to get Heart Pieces improperly, you know!
You've got a point, but...
Can you please help me look for Tokunosuke?!
Guess there's no helping it.
What's the deal?!
It melted!
You're kiddin' me!
How dare he trick me!
Hold it!
Whoa!
What happened?
All the people in this place are so stupid they don't even realize the law that states there's a flip side to everything.
Thanks to them, I was able to gather four Heart Pieces without having to Duel even once.
Hmm?
Which means if I choose one of the pieces from inside this bag...
I can pass right to the finals!
Darn! Where the heck did that Tokunosuke go?!
I can't believe he's gathering Heart Pieces like this!
- If he's collected them, then...!
I'm done!
Here he is.
I collected all the Heart Pieces!
Oh, you already collected them?
Aren't you in high spirits?
Does that mean I'm the first one here?
Yippee! I'm the first one to advance to the finals!
I want you to lick it.
Huh? You talking about my Heart Pieces?
B-But Heart Pieces aren't made for licking.
A-And they're bound to be dirty after being in people's pockets.
Then should I grab your mouth and make you do it?
I'll lick it! I just need to lick it, right?
It melted!
Why did it melt?
Whoa! This is candy!
You lying, thieving little cheapskate! Screw you!
Ow, ow, ow...
What the hell are those supposed to be?!
I-It wasn't me! I-I was tricked!
Pipe down!
- Leg'go!
- Tokunosuke!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
I said to pipe down!
No way! I'm gonna start crying!
Tokunosuke!
Yuma-kun!
"Number 37: Disqualified from the W.D.C.!?
Heartland's Assassins Droite and Gauche"
What are you trying to do with Tokunosuke?!
Who the hell are you?
You're...
That noisy little boy from before.
So that was you?
I asked you what you plan to do with Tokunosuke!
He fabricated Heart Pieces!
As punishment, his deck will be confiscated!
He'll be disqualified and deprived of all future participation in the Duel Carnival for the rest of his life!
I'll make it so he can never Duel again before beating his ass right out of Heartland City!
H-Hang on a minute! You don't have to go that far!
"That far"?!
This pest's dishonored Dueling!
I cannot forgive him for that!
Spare me! I'll give you my deck or whatever you want!
Hey, hold it!
It's true that what Tokunosuke did may be unforgivable.
But that's no reason for you to go this far!
If this is an issue between Duelists, let's settle it with a Duel!
If you insist on taking Tokunosuke, Duel with me!
A Duel, you say?
Interesting! But I'm strong, you know!
Hmph, that's just fine!
You can both come at me at the same time!
Very well.
This Duel will be 2-on-1.
If you Duel against the both of us and manage to defeat the both of us, it's your win.
And we'll forget about what he did.
But if you end up losing, you will be required to take the punishment in his place.
No way!
How about it? You on board?
Hmph. Don't act like you've got the balls to fight when you're nothing but an incompetent Duelist not even worth talking to.
All right! I accept that Duel!
What?
Yuma-kun!
But if you lose and they take your deck, you won't be able to continue participating in the Carnival.
And Astral's still not here, right? It's way to reckless for you to fight both of them by yourself, Yuma!
Even so, I can't just abandon Tokunosuke, my friend!
Sounds interesting! I'll test out that spirit of yours!
Here I go! I won't let myself lose to the likes of you!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
It's no good. I can't remember anything past that.
And there's that miracle that saved Yuma and I during the Duel with Kaito.
What exactly is the "Power of ZeXal"?
Yuma's starting a Duel?
I have to get going.
It's been a long time, Astral!
You're...!
Number 96!
Why are you...?
You broke the seal?!
Yes, it was what we Numbers wanted!
"We"?
Let's hurry up and finish this, Gauche.
I know.
Astral's not here?!
God, this is so reckless!
There's no way Yuma can beat those two on his own!
Hey! Who do you think he's fighting for?!
Yuma-kun, you can do it!
Heck yeah! I'm good enough to handle these two on my own!
Here goes!
My turn! Draw!
I set a Monster in face-down Defense Mode!
I then set a card face-down and end my turn!
Heh! All that talk and you go and play on the defensive.
I can't afford to lose this Duel!
Why are the other Numbers giving you their strength?
I already told you. It's what all the Numbers want.
You want the same! The destruction of the world!
Destruction?
Impossible!
You're saying I want to destroy the world?!
If you didn't, how can you explain my being here?!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Phantom Butterfly Assassin Morpho!
I then set two cards and end my turn!
1200 Attack Points...!
You'll regret the spirit you had to challenge us to a match!
My turn! Draw!
I Special Summon Hammer-Rush Bouncer!
This card can be Special Summoned from my hand when my field is empty while my opponent controls a Monster, Magic, or Trap Card!
It's got 2300 Attack Points!
He Summoned a Level Six Monster right off the bat!
I end my turn with that.
Now come at us with everything you've got!
My opponents have a Monster with 1200 Attack Power and another with 2300 Attack Power.
And in my hand...
Okay! I decided which of you I'm gonna beat first!
My turn! Draw!
I switch my face-down Defense Mode Monster into face-up Attack Mode!
Show yourself, Rai Rider!
Hmph. It's got 1200 Attack Points.
What can that piss-poor Monster possibly do?
Hmph! Just you watch!
I'll then Summon Tasuke Knight!
Yes! If I destroy Morpho with Tasuke Knight and then Direct Attack with Rai Rider, I'll deal her great damage!
Go, Tasuke Knight! Attack Morpho!
Wave Pressure!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Scales of Subordination!
When an opposing Monster declares an attack,
this card can change this card into an Equipment Card and change the target's Battle Position from Attack to Defense Position!
What?!
Tasuke Knight's attack was stopped!
Looks like your spirit leads you to rush in and miscalculate!
I'll end my turn.
He can't win without Astral around after all!
Why won't Astral come out?!
C'mon, remember your mission, Astral!
Now! Come to our side, Astral!
Astral!!
What?!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Hope, does this mean you've decided to stand against us?
Fine then! I'll just start by absorbing you first!
Come out, Black Mist!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Phantom Butterfly Assassin Swallowtail!
And I activate the second effect of Scales of Subordination!
Once per turn, I can change the Battle Position of the Monster this card is equipped to.
I switch Tasuke Knight into Attack Mode!
So she's gonna attack him with her Phantom Butterfly Assassin?
But I'll only take 100 points of damage if you do attack him!
Naive.
I activate the Monster Effect of Phantom Butterfly Assassin Morph!
Once per turn, when an opponent's Monster changes its Battle Position, she can decrease its Attack and Defense Power by 1000 points!
Oh crap!
Tasuke Knight's Attack Power!
I use Phantom Butterfly Assassin Morph to attack Tasuke Knight!
Blue Scale Stream!
I then activate the Monster Effect of Phantom Butterfly Assassin Swallowtail!
When a Monster on the field inflicts Battle Damage other than this card,
one of my opponent's Monsters loses Attack Power equal to that damage.
Now even Rai Rider's Attack Power was decreased!
I then use Phantom Butterfly Assassin Swallowtail to attack Rai Rider!
Limit Scale Stream!
Yuma!
He's only got 2400 Life Points!
I can't believe he lost 1600 points in one go!
I thought you had more guts than this, but you turned out to be nothing but an incompetent Duelist with no spirit.
What a laugh!
That's my line! You sure you should be so happy about such a small amount of damage?!
This match is just beginning!
What?
I activate Rai Rider's Monster Effect!
The Monster who battles with this Monster can't battle during my opponent's next turn!
Hmph, and that's all your spirit can offer?
Your field's completely empty!
This ends on my turn!
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
Go, Black Mist!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Blade Bouncer!
I then Direct Attack with Hammer-Rush Bouncer!
If I control no Magic or Trap Cards when this card attacks,
the opposing player can't activate any of their Magic and Trap Cards!
In other words, no matter what card you set, you can't use any of them!
So that's why he hasn't set any cards?!
This is bad! If this attack goes through, Yuma-kun will be left with only 100 Life Points!
Go, Hammer-Rush Bouncer!
Destroy Knuckle!!
Yuma!
H-He was hit!
A spineless coward with nothing but talk.
All I need to do is finish you off with Blade Bouncer.
What?! 1600 Life?!
His Monster protected him!
Gagaga Gardna can be Special Summoned from my hand in Attack Mode when I receive a Direct Attack.
And by discarding a card from my hand, I can negate the battle!
At the same time Hammer-Rush Bouncer attacked directly,
he Special Summoned Gagaga Gardna to nullify the damage
and discarded a card from his hand to prevent Gagaga Gardna from being destroyed.
But you still take damage equal to the difference in the Monsters' Attack Points.
Gagaga Gardna has 1500 Attack Points.
I attack using the 1800 Attack Power Blade Bouncer!
Go! Straight Slash!!
Stop this!
I discard a card from my hand to activate Gagaga Gardna's Monster Effect!
Yuma!
He takes another 300 points of damage!
But now the battle's over and I managed to protect Gagaga Gardna.
Are you sure about that?
I activate Blade Bouncer's Monster Effect!
By discarding a card from my hand, this Monster can attack once again!
Once again?!
He's got four cards in his hand.
Even if he manages to endure this attack, he can still attack four more times?!
Go, Blade Bouncer! Attack Gagaga Gardna!
Straight Slash!!
Gagaga Gardna!
I discard a card from my hand to activate Gagaga Gardna's Monster Effect!
Yuma!
Now your hand is at zero.
Regardless of your spirit, you won't be able to use Gagaga Gardna's effect.
Just give up.
I activate Blade Bouncer's Monster Effect!
Go, Blade Bouncer!
Attack Gagaga Bouncer!
Straight Slash!!
Gagaga Gardna!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
I've been cornered in my Duel with Droite and Gauche while Astral's gone missing.
Please come back!
Are you off fighting somewhere?!
I can feel you bringing it to them!
If I lose this Duel, Astral's gonna disappear!
I won't let that happen!
This is our bond!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Connect the Hope Together! Hope Sword Mars Slash!!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Yuma, were you aware that mice sometimes crawl around your room late at night?
Are you serious?! I better call an exterminator!
What are you talking about? I've gathered up a bunch of talented Duelists.
I named them "Chuma"!
(Chuu: The sound mice make)
Am I supposed to get along with them?!