You want to participate in the Duel Carnival?
Yes. Please grant me this wish.
It's growing painful just watching.
Oh?
So your fighting spirit is fired up, is that it?
Then it cannot be helped.
Thank you very much.
But Gauche...
If you enter and you wind up losing...
...you know what the consequences are, right?
I understand.
I'll definitely make it to the finals and... that...
Your goal is Yuma Tsukumo.
Yeah.
But he has Numbers.
And he has the Original.
Do you have some sort of plan?
I don't have anything of the sort.
I just gotta fight with this!
Did you seal off the deck that Mr. Heartland gave you?
Yeah, I won't use something I borrowed!
I will fight with my own deck!
And defeating the Original Number is...
...the only way to beat him--Kaito!
Gauche...
Droite, what will you do?
Kaito will definitely win and make it to the finals.
To qualify for the finals, we will need to collect five Heart Pieces by the end of the day.
We can do it if we work together.
Yeah...
What's with Old Man Rokujuro?
He actually went home while I was asleep.
Come now, he was at peace of mind.
Yuma, will you keep moving forward on your own path?
The path I choose…
You're aiming to be World Duel Champion, right? You already got this far, so work until the last moment!
Sis…
Bing...
Yuma. Duel Lunch. Duel Lunch.
Oh?! Great stuff! Thanks, Obomi!
Do your best, Yuma.
You suck. Work hard. You suck. Work hard.
I do not suck!
Well, I'm off!
Morning, Yuma!
Kotori… Tetsuo… Everyone!
Whoa there.
What’s going on? Class Rep, are you alright?
Yes. Although I can’t say I am in perfect shape, to summa-
In other words, everyone from the Numbers Club got together!
We come here to cheer for you, Yuma!
You guys… I guess you can never go wrong with treasuring your friends!
Yuma seems pretty energetic, does’t he?
Yeah.
After many intense battles, the final day of the Duel Carnival finally begins!
Which of you warriors will manage to gather enough Heart Pieces?
Heart Burning!
Since you already got this far, you goal should aim all the way for the finals...no, winning it all!
Of course I will! No matter how strong the finalists are, I'm gonna win for sure!
H-Hey...
Yuma?
Gramps said I need to find my own path...
I've been thinking about this for a while, but I still haven't found an answer.
The path that permits you to save Kaito, Haruto, Shark, and your father.
You too, Astral! I don’t want to lose anyone!
Yuma…
Uhh…no… I meant... Right.
I'll find a path that makes all of us happy!
A path that will make us all happy?
As long as you become Duel Champion, I'll be happy!
Yeah, I'd be honored as well!
Me too!
You need Heart Pieces to qualify for the finals. How many do you have so far?
Right! I already got four Heart Pieces.
Okay, this is for Yuma!
Let’s go and find remaining Duelists!
If possible, the weak ones!
I doubt there'd be many weaklings left...
Even so, we got to find them! The weaklings!
Weaklings!
Hey now...
Let's go search!
Right!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
The remaining ones... the remaining ones...
Let's see... Weak duelists... weak...
Numbers 45: A Nemesis Shows Up Late!
Robin VS Gauche!
Tell me if you happen to find someone.
If possible, find a relatively weaker duelist for an opponent, please.
Weak duelists...
Guys like that should be hiding in this an alleyway.
He's that scary Operation Committee member!
H-Her too?!
Every single one of them turned out to be total newbs.
But now we have 3 Heart Pieces.
Those two...
I attack directly with Different Dimension Esper Star Robin!
Big Surprise Punch!!
Did you see that?
That was the big banquet of victory!
Please give me your autograph!
Hey guys, can I give out autographs later?
Out of the way!!
You look like you're not half bad.
So you are now a Duel Carnival participant, right?
Yep, as of today.
Me too.
I wasn't able to participate the
last two days since I was busy in the studio.
I really hope I can get the 4th Heart Piece from you.
Interesting. I'll give those words back to you.
Don't let your guard down.. He got three Heart Pieces in one day.
That's why I said it's interesting.
Even Robin appeared!
Here goes! I challenge you!
Duel Disk, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Tokunosuke!
Yuma!
Just what's going on here?
Kotori!
Sei! Sachi!
So you really did come here to cheer for Robin-sama!
Ah... It's Robin-sama!
Robin! I can't believe he's in the tournament too!
I'll Special Summon this guy in Defense mode!
Come forth, Ironhammer the Iron Giant!
Whoa! Awesome!
All of Robin's heroes are assembled on the field!
It's Different Dimension ESPer Star Robin and his friends!
Each one of them is an excellent monster...
Just recalling that match makes my heart throb with joy.
Yuma...
But Robin's opponent is no pushover!
Yeah. His opponent is Gauche.
But why's he fighting Robin?
It seems he resigned his position as an Operation Committee member in order to participate in the tournament.
Hey, take a good look at how I duel!
So he's in the tournament too...
Wait a sec, Gauche's monsters aren't the same ones we fought back then?
So he changed his deck for the WDC?
But in his current situation,
he's no match for Robin's heroes!
Go, Star Robin! Attack Spartas!
I'll give you a good look at the power of my Heroic Challenger Spartas!
Heroic Formation!
When my opponent's monster declares an attack,
these monsters can form the formation
and combine their Attack power!
Not good, Robin will be..
No, Robin's attack hasn't necessarily been sealed yet.
Not bad!
Trap card! Change! The Jet Iron!
By releasing the Robin family on the field...
...this card can Special Summon The Different Dimension Jet Iron...
...and its Attack power become the
grand total of the released monsters!
Come forth, Different Dimension Jet Iron!!
8000 attack points?
Go, Different Dimension Jet Iron!
Iron Phoenix!!
Trap, activate! Heroic Guard!
By releasing one Spartas, the damage I take will decrease by its Attack power!
I open another Trap card!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Heroic Revenge Sword!
This card can be activated when a 'Heroic Challenger' monster was destroyed.
When a monster equipped by this card battles,
It will destroy the monster which destroyed that Heroic Challenger!
And inflict damage to the player equal to its Attack power!
That means Robin will receive 8000 damage!?
Here comes the reversal!
I won't let that happen!
I activate Different Dimension Jet Iron's monster effect!
By releasing this card, I can call forth these 4 monsters from the Cemetery!
So that's your resort?!
Now Heroics Revenge Sword's effect will vanish.
That was an excellent counter. You're quite spirited.
You too.
Looks like I got a great opponent.
Since Gairuda was Special Summoned, I get to draw one card.
I end my turn.
Awesome! Awesome!!
Gauche's fighting style is so passionate and Robin's dueling is gorgeous!
They're both really amazing!
Man, I wanna duel too!
The remaining Spartas are chanting to me, asking me to avenge their comrade!
My turn! Draw!
I release Spartas to Advance summon!
Come forth, Heroic Challenger - War Hammer!!
Go, attack Beast Warrior Puman!
Oh-no! Robin is...!
Puman...
Since Puman was destroyed,
I'll be taking his burning spirit!
What?
I activate War Hammer's monster effect!
The monster it destroyed by battle becomes an equipment card
And War Hammer gains Attack power equal to the Attack power of the equipped monster!
Awesome! Is this Gauche's real strength?
He's a lot different than before.
I can't believe my comrade's power got taken away!
I set one card and end my turn!
The monsters on Robin's field are
no match of Gauche's War Hammer!
But look at his face!
Robin hasn't given up yet!
Even in a pinch, never give up.
Always believe in yourself...
That's the 'bring it to 'em' I learned from Yuma!
My turn! Draw!
From my hand, I activate the Magic card Galaxy Queen's Light!
With this card, by selecting one monster on my field,
all other monsters on my field will have the same level of the target monster until the end phase!
I choose my Level-10 Different Dimension ESPer Star Robin!
The mother of all galaxies, please give power to my heroes!
I overlay my Level-10 Robin family!
I build the Overlay Network with these 3 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth! Super Dimensional Robot!
Galaxy Destroyer!
5000 Attack power?!
Awesome, Robin- no, Fuya!
The way he duels is much different than before!
Indeed! Breaking his mother's spell
pushed him to a whole new level.
Interesting. Then I'll fight 'til the end as well!
But the moment you declare an attack, your monster is finished.
That trap card Gauche set must be the Trap Card Reactive Armor.
When the opposing monster attacks, that trap card can destroy almost any monster!
I activate Galaxy Destroyer' monster effect!
By detaching one overlay unit, it destroys all Magic and Trap cards on my opponent's field!
Galaxy Break!
What?!
War Hammer's Attack power now returns to 2100!
Go, Super Dimensional - Robot Galaxy Destroyer!
Attack War Hammer!
If this attack connects, Gauche is finished!
I send Heroic Challenger - Sword Shield
from my hand to the Cemetery!
When I receive 2000 or more damage by battle,
that damage is negated and my Life points become 100!
Awesome, he survived again!
He actually had such a card hidden in his hand?
I will end my turn!
Gauche's got 100 Life Points left!
There's no way Robin won't win this!
Well done, Robin-sama!
My turn! Draw!
Yes!
I summon Heroic Challenger - Double Lance!
This monster can be treated as 2 Xyz materials!
What?
That means...
I overlay the LV 4 Double Lance which is treated as 2 materials!
I build the Overlay Network with these two monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Heroic Champion - Excalibur!
He actually preformed a Xyz summon
in this dire situation?!
It can only attack when I have 500 Life points or less.
Here goes!!
I activate Excalibur's monster effect!
By detaching one overlay unit, its Attack power is doubled!
Its Attack power became 4000?!
But Robin's monster has 5000!
It's still far off, even after doubling!
I activate the Magic card from my hand, Heroic Chance!
Excalibur's Attack power is doubled again!
An Attack power of 8000?!
So that's his goal?!
Go, Excalibur!
Attack Galaxy Destroyer!
One-Sword Style Strike: Finishing Attack of True Sword!
Impossible!
Robin was...
...defeated.
Did I lose?
Robin!
Yuma.
That was really fun.
Yeah. I can tell by looking at you.
It's all thanks to you.
Wha-?
After the battle with you, I realized...
that dueling should be something you have fun with.
Fuya!
That was a good duel. I thank you.
Me as well. I am very happy to have dueled with you.
Did you really resign your
position as an Operation Committee member?
Yeah. In order to fight you.
Me?!
I'll definitely advance to the finals.
I'll be waiting.
Maybe he learned how to have fun dueling from you too.
Huh?!
It's strange. Everyone who dueled with you became happy.
Fuya-kun!
You possess that special ability,
The ability to make people happy through dueling.
Make people happy through dueling?
I hope you can make more people happy in the future!
Please keep winning for this cause!
Ahh! Robin-sama!
To make people happy through dueling...
That's right, that's the way!
Thank you, Robin!
From here on out, I'll continue to 'bring it to 'em'!
Yuma finally decided his own path...
Then... I will as well...
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
While Yuma is desperately searching for the last Heart Piece,
Shark appears before him all of the sudden.
He has a berserk attitude, much different from usual.
And another unexpected person appears in Yuma's sight as well.
Shark, duel with me!
Why are you losing on purpose?!
You're III! What are you doing here?!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Fighting for His Family: The Gentle Avenger, III!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
I would like to introduce to you Gauche's ace monster: Heroic Champion - Excalibur!
With its effect, it can double its attack power, so its a monster well worthy the name of "Champion".
Me too! I'm a champion at
eating quickly and getting up early!
We don't need that.
True...