O-Ow, ow! That hurts, Kotori!
You're late, you know!
You said you'd come with me after school today!
Ow, ow, ow! I know! I get it!
Wow! They're awesome!
So this is the gymnastics club, huh?!
It's an amazing club with so many young athletes dreaming big!
Sachi!
Ah! Kotori!
We came to cheer you on like promised!
Yeah! Thank you!
The tournament's coming up very soon, right?
You're definitely gonna win!
Wow, they are quite skilled.
Your leaps are a far cry away from theirs.
Wha-?!
Enough already!
Hey! Taiki!
That ain't-
Ouch!
Watch where you're going!
S-Say what?
Don't talk to me that way!
You have a problem with me?
Hold on, Taiki-kun!
What about practice?
Shut up! I just came here to drop out of the tournament!
What's that guy's problem?!
He's Taiki Kimura-kun.
He's the ace of this club.
That guy is?
Yeah... And during practice the other day...
All eyes are on Contestant Taiki Kimura!
If he conquers this bar, he'll win the tournament!
Now, here comes the result!
Oh no! He lost his balance and fell down!
Now Contestant Kimura has lost his shot at the championship!
Ever since then, he doesn't want to practice,
and he won't come to the club.
And here I was thinking he finally came after all this time...
I wonder if Taiki-kun really quit the gymnastics club.
Isn't that him...?
Hey! Taiki!
You from before...
I'm Yuma Tsukumo. You can call me Yuma.
And? What do you want?
Did you come to finish our little fight from before?
Yep. But we'll be fighting with this thing instead.
You want a Duel?
Forget that!
What the heck? You running away?
What?
Or maybe you're just scared you'll lose to me.
Yuma!
Don't get too full of yourself!
As if I'd lose to someone like you!
Cool! Then it's decided!
Here goes!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
I'll let you handle this Duel.
Okay!
Okay! I'm taking the first turn!
My turn! Draw!
Got it!
I set a Monster in Face-Down Defense Position!
Then I set three cards and end my turn!
He's going on the defense in the very first turn.
Could he be aiming for a counter or something?
Here goes! My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
Go, Gagaga Magician! Attack his face-down Monster!
What? You're still going to attack?
Come out, Muscle Gardna!
2000 Defense Points!
I then activate a Trap!
Underground Machine Gun!
You inflict 200 damage to your opponent for each card on your field and in your hand.
Huh? Then I...!
That's 1200 points of damage.
Are you some kind of idiot?
You keep charging at me without any results!
We won't know that until I try, right?!
What?!
I mean, it's better to have a good attitude about failing instead of being scared of it and not doing anything!
Scared of failing...?
I...
Now let's continue!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
A Monster Card!
And it's got 2000 Attack Points on top of it!
If I use this to destroy his Monster and...
...attack him directly with Muscle Gardna, I'll win!
I'll Summon Mist Valley-
The set card on his field...?
If that turns out to be a Counter Trap he's shooting for...
I...
...set one card and end my turn!
Why didn't he at least try to attack?
Okay! If you ain't gonna come, allow me!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Ganbara Knight!
Yuma!
I Overlay the Level Four Gagaga Magician and Ganbara Knight!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come out! Number 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Number?!
Be brought out his Number!
Why?!
Here I come, Taiki!
I don't care how strong your Monster is!
I have three set cards over here!
You won't take me down that easily!
Yeah! I bet!
Huh?
I just wanna challenge everything! It's how I bring it to 'em!
Bring it to 'em?
Bring it to 'em means to never give up no matter what happens!
It means to challenge without fear!
Challenge without fear...?
I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Go! Break right through!
Hope Sword Thunder Slash!!
Trap, activate!
Magic Cylinders!
What?!
This card negates the attack of an opposing Monster
and deals the Attack Power
of the Monster as damage to the opponent!
Let's go again!
Once again!
Why are you...?
Aren't you scared?
Aren't you scared of losing?!
I'm fine no matter how many times I lose!
After all, I love Dueling!
So I'll challenge you no matter how many times it takes!
I'll bring it to ya!
Bring it to me...?
I also love gymnastics so much that I don't want to lose to anyone!
Well said!
Huh?
That man's...!
I-I-It can't be...!
Is that, to summarize, the famous Olympic athlete, Contestant Kohei Uchimura?!
Hey, is the guy that amazing?
Taiki, I was worried and came to look for you.
Uchimura-san...
Thank you very much.
But I'm all right now!
I'm going to challenge more!
I'm going to bring it to 'em!
Hey, Yuma!
Let's Duel again some time!
See ya later, Yuma!
So I don't lose against him again...
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!