I couldn't even touch him...
Then as you wish!
Then I'll take away our soul!
Right now... I can't beat this guy.
I would have completely lost in that battle.
I'll take away your soul!
Go! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Photon Steam of-!
This Duel is interrupted!
If that Duel wasn't interrupted... I would've been annihilated.
Ouch...
Astral...
It's because you're always around me that why my soul was targeted...
I'm sorry...
Geez, what are you whining about!?
The only way to survive is to defeat Kaito, isn't that right?
Can we win?
That's why it's not "can we win", it's "we will win"!
This isn't only your problem anymore-
Yuma!
Kotori... Tetsuo...
The World Duel Carnival?
Yup, W.D.C. for short.
And it will be held in our Heartland.
Unbelievably strong Duelists from all over the world are gathered for this carnival!
That means him too...
Yuma...
Hey Yuma, what's the matter?
Yuma!
Grandma!
The truth is, I have to send you on a small errand!
T-These are...
I-I'm not free right now...
I wonder where my adorable, obedient grandson went to?
Right here! You're obedient grandson is right here!
How the heck is this a "small errand", Grandma?!
I can't walk anymore...
This isn't like you, Yuma.
Did you drop your "bringing it to em'" attitude?
What!? If I don't have what it takes to bring it to em', then what do I have left!
I'LL BRING IT TO EM'!
Alright!
Is there anybody here?
What an untidy place...
Yuma!
It's a monkey, a monkey, a MONKEY!
Right here, here, here!
That's no monkey. It's an old man?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
That was delicious, Kotori-chan.
Numbers 15
A Fight to the Death, The Duel Lodge: A Legendary Monster is Reborn!!
A little longer and I was going to starve!
I thank Haru-san very much!
Haru-san huh, What does my Grandma have to do with you?
Well I receive a lot of assistance from your caring grandma, Haru-san!
What's up with this old man?
I'm not an old man!
I'm the master of this Duel Lodge... Rokujuro!
Duel Lodge!?
You let Yuma go to the Duel Lodge!?
But why!?
I told you it would be dangerous for Yuma to Duel anymore!
Just look at Dad!
He's still too young...
I'm sure he can find his real purpose in Dueling.
Real purpose?
We can't go back!?
That's right. There's no path now, and besides until the day comes, your hearts are just too thin.
N-No way!
Well, you guys can sleep here.
But....
Sleep in such a place?
The one who works eats, no, maybe you should sleep...
Hey, wait a sec!
Tetsuo-kun, please put that over there.
Yeah.
Yuma, you shouldn't be slacking off!
Man, this is troublesome...
Why do we have to do the cleaning?
That old man...
Speaking of the old man, he went to this room.
B-B-Black Magician!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Amazing!
Red-Eyes, Neos...
Even Black Magician Girl!
The Legendary monsters are all here!
Amazing!
Geez, Yuma don't slack off-
W-What is this place?
Amazing!
Surprised?
Those statues are Duel Monsters that I put my soul into making!
In order to rise disciples, I had to make statues.
Disciples?
This Duel Lodge is a place to train Duelist to be winners.
Many formed Duelist were raised right here.
Amazing!
These Monster statues look as if they're about to move
They can move.
The statues can move?
Yeah, certainly in a Duel that is...
Would you like to contribute?
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
On both of our fields, the legendary stones have already been summoned.
I have The Blue-Eyes Statue Dragon, and The Red-Eyes Statue Dragon,
While you have Statue Black Magician, and Statue Black Magician Girl!
The decks we're using are the stone decks used in the Duel Lodge!
Our legendary stone monsters are all statues right now.
Their powers have been sealed and their attack power are 0.
Attacking is impossible.
What the hell? So they can't move after all.
They may move, they may not. It all depends on you.
Depends on Yuma?
I see, the duel is all relying on the player's strategy.
Yuma, the monsters on the field have an effect!
All the keys to your cards are within the deck.
The deck?
That's right!
Hey, what are you doing? You have the first move!
Alright, here I go!
My turn, draw!
This is...
I activate the Field Magic, B2 Zone!
The Field Magic, B2 Zone, is a card that releases the statue monsters from their effect!
Move now, monsters!
Alright!
I was able to awaken the Legendary Monsters!
Amazing, The Red-Eyes and The Blue-Eyes!
Alright! Go, Black Magician, attack Red-Eyes!
Black Magic!
Not too shabby.
I did it!
This is entertaining!
But, did you really make the monsters move just like that?
W-What are you saying!?
Bla-Magi just destroyed Red-Eyes!
The true duel begins now!
What?
This is...
What's that?
N-No way!
I'm the Bla--Magi!
I've become the monster!?
No way...
What does this mean!?
I've become the monster!
It's my turn!
I activate the Magic Card, Fusion!
I send the 3 Blue-Eyes from my field and hand to the cemetery!
Fuse now!
Come on, Fusion Summon!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Statue Dragon!
Ultimate Dragon attacks Bla-Magi Girl!
Ultimate Burst!!
Bla-Magi Girl!
Then from my hand I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Fusion Cancel!
The Fusion Monster returns to my extra deck, and I Special Summon the Fusion Material Monsters from my cemetery!
Be Reborn! The 3 Blue-Eyes!
S-Stop!
Please Stop!
That's right.
Facing this fear, anybody would be terrified. That's a natural thing.
Attack him!
What's wrong!?
It's the same for the monsters.
Monster's are always exposed to this fear!
Here I go! The 3 Blue-Eyes attack Bla-Magi no.. Yuma directly!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Yuma!
I was a bit too harsh there...
Just now.
You sensed the monster's fear.
That means you understood what they Monsters were feeling.
When you know the Monsters thoughts, they'll answer you.
Those thoughts made the monsters awaken from death.
If I know their thoughts, they'll answer me?
Even monsters sense fear...
And they can overcome it.
Hey, Yuma!
Hey Yuma! How long do you plan on staying here?
If you want to go back just go, I'll stay here a little longer.
Then I'll prepare the breakfast!
H-Hey!
What is this wound?
Who did such a horrible thing!?
Shouldn't it be repaired?
That boy truly has some character.
A shining character
Unlike that guy...
H-Hey!
I've returned...
Master...
I've returned, Master...
Yamakiwa, You've become unconscious because of the darkness.
Allow me to drag you down...
Inside the darkness...
Duel!!
W-Wait a sec, who are you!?
And your...?
Yuma...
O-Old man!
Run away, Yuma!
R-Run, you say?
Who in the world is this guy!?
He's my former disciple!
But why?
Why must you insist on seeking the darkness!?
The light is what makes you strong!
Can't you see that you're destroying yourself?!
What? What are you doing!?
I'll... Be back!
At that time I'll defeat you and...
I'll take the Hidden Deck within the Duel Lodge!
I won against you!
Where is the Hidden Deck within the Duel Lodge?
Do you think I'll hand it over?
What?
You still don't get it!?
Foolish one, who's heart is concurred by darkness!
Then I'll cut all of them!
Stop!
What are you doing!?
Who are you? And why are you interfering?
I'm... I'm... I'm the old man's disciple!
Yuma...
A disciple of that lousy old man?
Don't make me laugh...
I won't forgive anyone that disrespects my master!
Interesting, I'll drag you into the darkness too!
Duel-Disk set!
D-Gazer set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Hang in there, Yuma...
Yuma, I'll fight too.
Weren't you feeling down, just now?
I was taught something at this lodge too.
That's why I'm a disciple.
I'll have the first move!
My turn, draw!
I summon Gagaga Magician!
Then I set 1 card face-down and end my turn!
My turn... Draw!
I summon Armored Ninja Flame!
Then from my hand I activate the Magic Card, Armored Ninjutsu: Quick Teleport!
With this card, I can Special Summon a monster whose attack power is less than Armored Ninja Flame's!
Appear, Armored Ninja Air!
Due to Quick Teleport's effect, Flame and Air can't attack.
But...
Two level 4 monsters!
I overlay the level 4 Armored Ninja Flame and Armored Ninja Air!
These two monsters will construct the overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, Armored Ninja Blade Heart!
He already summoned a Xyz Monster!
This speed isn't just normal!
Armored Ninja Blade Heart attacks Gagaga Magician!
Permanent Trap open! Gagaga Shield!
This card becomes an equip card to a monster!
I equip it to Gagaga Magician!
Slice him down!
Sudden Rapid...
Blade Strike!!
Gagaga Shield, it protects Gagaga Magician from destruction for 2 times!
But, you'll still take the damage!
Then Armored Ninja Blade Heart, once per turn by detaching one overlay unit,
It can attack a monster once again!
Take the damage once more!
Yuma!
Idiot, even if you protect the monster you'll still take the damage!
The monsters are my friends!
My friends are fighting to overcome their fear!
That's why I'll protect my friends!
Friends, you say? What nonsense!
I'll cut those thoughts and your monsters and crush them!
Stop kidding me!
I'll never let you do such a thing!
Let's begin the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
In the start of the Duel, how many cards are in your hand?
4, 5, or maybe 6?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Yamikawa, the old man's previous disciple...
His skillful Ninja Deck has me cornered!
Someone who aims for victory, even at the sacrifice of his own Monsters... is that it?
This Duel's kinda scary for some reason!
Believe, Yuma!
Yeah! My Monster's are my friends, the ones I fight alongside!
I'll believe in those friends and protect them!
And I'll fight alongside them!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Deadliest Ninja Arts! The Most Terrifying Ninja!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer's five!
You draw the first five cards off the top of your deck into your hand.
Then the Duel starts!
Once you get to it, don't go forgetting to draw a card!