Due to the power of the Crest,
Yuma not only has lost his 'Bring it to 'Em',
but also his fighting spirit and challenger's determination to never give up!
Yuma, please believe in your power!
Believe in your bond with your friends!
Yuma...
Yuma!!
You don't even have any strength left for battle, Yuma?
So... so scary...
So scary...!
I set one card, and end my turn!
Come, come at me with all you've got, Yuma!
No... I don't wanna!
Why should I have to battle with those monsters anyway?
What just happened?
Something is strange...
Yuma-kun!
What are you doing? It's your turn!
Hey, Yuma, draw your card! Hurry up and draw your card!
My... my turn...
Draw.
I...
The duel...
I'll... surrender the duel.
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
"Number 48: Yuma Gives Up!?
The Stolen "Bring It To 'Em!""
I can't believe you would act this cowardly after losing your 'Bring it to 'Em'!
Huh? The 'Bring it to 'Em'?
What's going on here?
Yuma's 'Bring it to 'Em' and Astral were all sealed.
See for yourself!
Astral?!
He's really over there right now!
Yuma only has dread left, after losing the 'Bring it to 'Em' and Astral.
No way!
That's dirty, you jerk!
That's right, that's right!
That's just too much!
Say what you like!
Yuma, unfortunately I won't acknowledge your surrender!
I will defeat you for good, and seize everything from you!
How...how could that be?
Don't worry, I shall redeem you soon enough.
Prepare yourself, Yuma Tsukumo! You will lose here and now!
My turn, draw!
Shoot!
It's alright! Yuma still has Gogogo Golem!
I am not that naive!
I summon OOParts Monster Mud Golem Shakouki!
You mean Gogogo Golem in defense position won't be destroyed by battle?
But that's meaningless for me!
Go, Mud Golem Shakouki! Attack Gogogo Golem!
Jomon Laser!!
When this monster attacks a monster in Defense Position, it will inflict piercing damage to the player!
Then I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Heart of Stone!
When an OOParts Monster fails to destroy a monster my opponent controls by battle,
This card allows that monster to attack once again!
Mud Golem Shakouki, crush Gogogo Golem!
Jomon Laser!
Yuma!!
Now there is nothing left to defend you.
It's over, Yuma!
Go, Machu Mach!
Fire of Vril!
If he takes that face-on, to summarize, he will be finished!
Yuma!
This is... the last of...
...my strength!
Remember it!!
Bring it to 'Em!
What...what's this?
This card...
I special summon Gagaga Gardna!
What?!
That's right, Yuma-kun!
Gagaga Gardna can be special summoned from the hand when the player was attacked directly!
Yu...Yuma!!
Impossible... Why?!
Right, it must be Astral!
Astral, how dare you obstruct me!
Astral is...!
Just disappear!
Yuma! Don't give up!!
What's... this?
Astral!!
Now no one will be able to save you.
Yuma!
Please calm yourself!
To summarize, this is AR space. Even if Yuma-kun were to fall by some chance...
What are you talking about?
Did you forget where we are right now?!
That's right! We are...
... on the freeway that was built above the sea!
Yuma-kun!
Yuma, get a hold of yourself!
Why? You guys...
Isn't that obvious? We're friends!
Me...and you guys...are friends?
That's right!
Yuma...
We are...
...friends!
Hey, did you forget everything?
Aren't you a guy who never gives up?
Regardless of the hardship, you would always stand back up and face them bravely!
The Yuma I know is someone like that!
I am very brave...
...and you guys are my friends?
This little farce ends now.
I forgot you guys are here as well.
Cat?!
Yuma, I will seize everything from you!
It' useless, as long as you guys stay inside that place, he cannot hear you!
Darn! Our voices can't reach him, and Astral isn't here either!
Yuma...
I can't believe he would use something this despicable...
It'll be no good to fight that power all alone right now.
Yuma! Don't forget the most important thing!
What?!
Remember it, Yuma!
The thing I have taught you!
I'll...
I'll bring...
I'll bring it...
Yuma!
Take this!
Remember it...
...the thing I have taught you!
That's right...
...the thing I have forgotten is...
I'll Bring it to 'Em!
Yuma's...!
That's... impossible!
The power of Tron's Crest was negated?!
III!
I can't believe you would use that Crest Power this far!
Shut up! I will send you to where Astral is!
Astral?
Astral!
Where is Astral!?
Unfortunately, Astral no longer exists.
What do you mean?!
Just as I said. Astral was eliminated.
What did you say?
You're lying...
You should have seen it as well...
the moment he was exterminated.
It's a lie...
It's a lie!
It's a lie!!
That guy...he wouldn't leave me like this!
Hey, Kotori! Tetsuo!
Kotori... how can this be!?
You just can't accept it!
Astral was destroyed by the power of my Crest.
Astral...
I desire to protect my family. I will use whatever it takes to accomplish that!
Now, let's continue the duel!
I activate the effect of the Field Magic, OOParts City Babylon!
By banishing the OOParts Monster Aztec Mask Golem from my graveyard,
I special summon Cabrera's Catapult with the same level from there in Defense Position!
I will end my turn like this!
Yuma, you only have 400 Life left.
But I have Cabrera's Catapult and No. 33 Machu Mach on my field.
You have no chance of winning!
Alright, submit along with your 'Bring it to 'Em'!
Unforgivable...
III...
...absolutely unforgivable!
I'll Bring it to 'Em!
Draw!
Think well... Yuma.
Now... what should you do?
That's right, that guy still lives within my heart!
Remember, remember it!
Every sentence he ever said!
Yuma, I will teach you the knowledge of dueling...
Huh? Why would I let you teach me?
Because, one day, you will have to battle alone.
Me, alone?
That's right. I have no idea when will I vanish...
But you have a future and infinite possibilities.
Thus I wish to leave behind the proof of my existence...
...within your memory.
For his sake as well, I definitely won't give up!
First is the opponent's motive, no matter what kinds of strong decks they constructed.
As long as they fall into the pace you set, they cannot dominate the duel.
III's motive is the combo of Cabrera's Catapult and Machu Mach.
If that connects, I would lose!
See through your opponent's motive, and stop it!
Which means I have to destroy Cabrera's Catapult or Machu Mach!
This is...
Right, is this what you left for me?
Then just follow your own style...
...and 'Bring it to 'Em!
Here I go, Astral!
The memory of fighting with you will become my flesh - and my blood!
I activate the Equipment Magic, Gagaga Revenge!
This card can revive a Gagaga monster in my graveyard, and equip to that monster!
Revive, Gagaga Magician!
Then I summon Fulelf!
Once per turn, by sending one Monster from my hand to the graveyard,
Fulelf can add that monster's LV to its own!
I send LV2 Overlay Eater to the graveyard, and increase Fulelf's LV to 4!
Don't... don't tell me...
I overlay the LV 4 Gagaga Magician and Fulelf!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, No.39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!
How is that possible?
This is the last "hope" which Astral has left to me!
Hope, you say?
Don't tell me you still think such a thing exists?
Sure! Of course!
The imperishable Flame of Hope within my heart!
That is the 'Bring it to 'Em which Astral has left to me!
Yuma!!
I activate the effect of the Equipment Magic Gagaga Revenge!
When the equipped monster becomes a Xyz material,
that Xyz monster gains 300 ATK!
Go, Aspiring Emperor - Hope, attack Machu Mach!
Hope Sword Twin Blade Shoot!
Bring it to 'Em!
What?!
Even without Astral...what's going on here?
Here's the reason!
This is the power of Astral and me!
I will end my turn like this!
Unforgivable...unforgivable, Yuma!
Come at me, III!
My power isn't just Machu Mach!
My turn, draw!
I release Cabrera's Catapult to advance summon the OOParts monster Sol Monolith!
When Sol Monolith was successfully summoned, it can change the LV of other monsters on my field to six!
I change Mud Golem Shakouki's level to six!
I Overlay my LV 6 Sol Monolith and Mud Golem Shakouki!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
See for yourself. This is the new power I obtained from Tron!
Come forth, Number 6!
OOParts Monster...Atlantal!
A new Number...
I activate Atlantal's effect!
When this card is Xyz summoned successfully, it can equip a Number in my graveyard!
You want to equip Machu Mach?
Its ATK became 5000?!
It gained Machu Mach's ATK?!
Atlantal, attack Hope!
Divine Punishment!!
Dream on! I activate Hope's effect!
Moon Barrier!
Yes!
It's not over yet! Atlantal's power isn't just this!
I activate Atlantal's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it halves my opponent's LP!
Orichalcum Gate!
Yuma!
This time, I will definitely give you a fatal blow!
I...I won't let you do that!
I won't let you do that! I definitely won't give up!
That's Astral's and mine 'Bring it to 'Em'!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
III's new Number, Atlantal, with its overwhelming power, was striking at me relentlessly.
However during the midst of battle, the duel has progressed to an unexpected direction!
This is no longer AR! It's reality!!
If this continues...
I won't give up!
Even if Astral has vanished, he still lives inside my heart!!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The End of a Fierce Fight!
Hope Ray VS Atlanthal"
I'll bring it to 'em supersized!
Today I will introduce the Monster Brass Devil Mellowmellow Melody.
With its effect, you can eat a melon!
Brass Devil Mellowmellow Melody: By detaching a Xyz-Material, it can attack once again.
So, where is my melon?
Cut it out already.
Huh?