Who are you?!
I am Barian.
Barian?
Did you just say you're Barian?!
That's right. I came here in order to annihilate Astral World,
as the messenger from Barian World!
So that's Barian?
Barian...
See for yourself!
Heart-eartH Dragon's effect!
When this Monster with is destroyed while it has no Overlay Units,
It can be revived only once.
The resurrected Heart-eartH Dragon's Attack Power increases
by 1000 points for each card that has been Banished.
4000 Attack Points?!
Furthermore, when Heart-eartH Dragon is Special Summoned successfully,
all Monsters on my opponent's field are switched to Defense Mode!
Impossible...Neo Galaxy-Eyes was...
Kaito!
It's still too soon for you to collapse.
Here goes! It's my turn! Draw!
I activate a Continuous Spell, Barian's Gateway!
This turn, each time a card is sent to the Graveyard...
...you will receive 800 points of damage!
What!?
Not good! We only have 100 of our Life left...
And now you're doomed!
Go, Heart-eartH Dragon!
Attack Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
Heartbreak Cannon!
I activate a Trap! Photon Escape!
With this card, when a Photon Monster is attacked,
I can Banish that Monster and end the battle!
You still have some strength left to struggle,
But at this moment,
For every Banished card, Heart-eartH Dragon gains 1000 Attack Points!
5000 Attack Points?!
Haruto...
K-Kaito...
Barian!
If you've come here to take Haruto away, just try it!
I'll finish things here and now!
HARUTO!
Brother...
I activate Dimension Wanderer’s Monster Effect from my hand!
When a Monster is Banished, by sending this card from my hand to the Graveyard,
I can inflict damage to my opponent equal to the total Attack Points of the Banished Monsters!
The Monsters I target are Shark Drake Weiss and Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
Therefore, the total damage you receive is 7300 points!
That's amazing, Kaito!
So I still had something like this up his sleeve.
This is my final strike!
Ryouga!
Right!
Take this attack that transcends dimensions!
Go, Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
Go, Shark Drake Weiss!
Depth Chaos Bite!!
Hmph. Very nice move, Kaito.
I activate another effect of the Continuous Magic, Barian’s Gateway!
By sending this card to the Graveyard, I can negate the opposing Monster’s effect!
He managed to avoid my strike?
Hey, Kaito! Are you alright? Hey!
Sha-Shark!
I set one card and end my turn!
What a pity. Now you're the only one left, Yuma Tsukumo.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Your remaining Life is almost as good as gone.
Not to mention you don't have any Monsters on your field.
"Number 71: The Miraculous 'Bring it to 'Em'!
Open a Path to the Future, ZEXAL!"
Alright, Yuma Tsukumo,
Despair along with the Astral World!
You all can just vanish into the depth of darkness!
Darn it! Not in a place like this...!
Yuma... Brother...
Always for my sake... For me...
Wha...What's happening?!
Haruto...
This is...
Haruto... You...
Haruto… You little…
Don't tell me he's using the power of Barian I gave him…?!
Impossible! The Sphere Field is...
Yuma, do it now!
Go to Astral!
Kaito?
Yuma...
Let him see the power you share with Astral!
Shark...
Yuma... Yuma...
Astral!
Here I come!
Yuma!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Astral!
I Overlay with you!
I build the Overlay Network with the two of us!
When two distant souls intersect,
The generational force shall appear!
Xyz Change...!
ZEXAL!
That's...
The power Yuma and Astral share with each other!
ZEXAL!
So you are the force from Astral World, ZEXAL!
Barian! Even if you stand in our way,
The hope that shines within the darkness...
...will defeat you along with the Bring it to 'em that burns inside my chest!
My turn!
The strongest Duelists can even choose the cards they draw!
This is the card of our destiny!
SHINING DRAW!
I Summon ZEXAL Weapon - Ultimate Shield!
I activate Ultimate Shield’s effect!
When this card is Summoned,
By negating the effects of up to three Banished Xyz Monsters,
they can be Special Summoned in Defense Position!
What did you just say?!
Revive! Chaos Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Yuma, let's go!
Integrate our power as one!
Roar! Chaos Number 32!
Shark Drake Weiss!
Be reborn, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Additionally, because these three Banished Monsters have returned to the field,
Heart-eartH Dragon loses 3000 Attack Power!
Did you see? This is the true power of our combined strength!
You just keep screwing around!
But your end will not change!
Behold!
What?
The Sphere Field Cannon is...?!
Astral may have escaped,
but the Sphere Field Cannon already has enough energy.
You cannot stop it now, no matter what you do!
You can all just vanish together with the Astral World!
Go, Yuma!
We will leave everything to you!
Beat him down!
Right! I equip Hope Ray with Ultimate Shield!
With this, Hope Ray gains 2000 Defense Points!
Furthermore, I activate the Equip Magic, Xyz Unity, from my hand!
Thanks to this card’s effect,
Hope Ray is switched to Attack Position!
Then during this turn, Hope Ray gains Attack Points equal to the total Attack Power of
all Defense Position Monsters on my field!
Therefore, his Attack Power is now 9800!
What did you say?!
Go! Hope Ray!
It’s useless! Regardless of how much you may have raised his Attack Power,
Heart-eartH Dragon is able to negate the battle damage,
and bounce it back to all of you!
I activate another effect of the Xyz Unity Equip Magic!
I send Shark Drake Weiss to the Graveyard using this effect...
...allowing Hope Ray to attack once again...
...letting it attack you directly!
Dream on!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Barian's Battle Buster!
By Banishing a Barian card from my Graveyard, this card's effect
allows me to negate a Monster's attack up to twice per turn!
By Banishing Barian's Gateway,
I can negate your Direct Attack!
Tch, I'm not done!
I send Neo-Galaxy Eyes to the Graveyard to attack once more...
...giving you another Direct Attack!
How foolish! I activate the effect of the Permanent Trap, Barian’s Battle Buster!
Your Direct Attack is negated!
Then, by sending Barian’s Battle Buster to the Graveyard,
Monsters on the field are forced to battle!
Shoot! If Hope Ray battles as things are...
6800 damage will bounce back to us!
Now it's truly over!
Go to hell!
You think so?
What?!
I activate Ultimate Shield’s effect!
When this card is used as an Equip card, all Effect Damage is negated,
and this card gains Attack Power equal to that amount of damage!
Additionally, it negates all of Heart-eartH Dragon's effects!
Impossible... Impossible... IMPOSSIBLE!
Take this attack worth 16600 points!
Go, Hope Ray! Attack Heart-eartH Dragon and Barian!
Hope Sword Ultimate Slash!
Damn you... bastards!
Did you see that, Barian?! This is our bond!
Dad!
Haruto!
Yuma!
B-Brother...
You're fine now.
All of your nightmares have completely vanished.
Shark!
Kotori! Kotori!!
Orbital! How long do you plan to keep sleeping?!
Orbital Seven!
A-As you wish!
I...
Kaito.
Kaito!
Father! Father!!
Orbital, take care of Haruto!
Kaito-sama, you aren't...!
Brother! Brother!!
I will bring my dad back! I swear that I will!
Kotori, take care of everyone!
Huh?
You're going?
Yup.
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Where are you, Dad?
Dad!
K-Kaito...
Yuma?!
Why, Yuma Tskumo? Why are you helping me?
You may be detestable...
But you did your best to save Haruto.
Any good father would shrug it off with a,
"Can't be helped", and a smile.
You've done enough, Yuma.
I have committed far too many sins.
I should not be forgiven.
Dad!
That’s right.
You have indeed committed too many sins.
Tron!
Yuma...
YUMA!
Tron… Stop, Tron!
Your revenge is already over!
B-Byron...
I beg you, Bryon.
Kaito and the others have nothing to do with this.
Everything is my fault.
Dad!
Stop, Tron!
Tron!
This is the last... of my power!
It’s aright. It's gonna be alright!
Because Yuma always...
Huh? I...
Y-Yo, Kotori!
Yuma! Astral!
Dad! Brother!
Hey, what are you crying about?
Hey, Kotori!
Geez, you really are an idiot!
You always...always make me worry!
Byron...
Byron.
Faker.
I'm sorry, Byron.
Farewell, my friend.
To think you'd actually forgive me, Byron...
You are so reckless and keep pulling crazy stunts!
It couldn't be helped!
What do you mean “it couldn’t be helped”?!
How's his spirit holding up, Droite?
I already administered first aid, but we still must hurry, Gauche.
Gotcha!
I'm counting on you, Gauche, Droite.
I'm sorry. Everything is my fault.
It’s all due to me.
Forgive me, Haruto, Kaito.
Yuma, your heart that never gives up, and the trust you place in the bonds with your friends...
...has brought the light of hope back to everyone.
Thank you.
So I guess the Duel Carnival is over now.
No, it‘s still not over yet!
I still haven’t received my prize for winning the Duel Carnival!
Wa…wait… What are you saying at a time like this?!
The winner of the Duel Carnival is to be granted whatever wish they have.
And mine is for Kaito and his family to live together in happiness and in peace!
It's none of your business.
Wh-What?!
I said that it's none of your business.
Alright, alright, I got it!
In that case, here's my real wish!
Kaito, you and I still haven’t settled the score yet!
Duel with me!
I see. Interesting.
I guess we can call this the real Final.
Very well. I accept.
Yuma, Astral!
Great! I'm gonna bring it to ya!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The final round of the World Duel Carnival is finally over!
But the true Final still hasn't started!
Isn't that right, Kaito?
The time has come to settle the score with our battle!
His strength is far greater than before.
This Duel's making my chest throb with excitement!
Kaito... You aren't really...!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Ultimate Showdown Has Come!!
Yuma VS Kaito: The Other WDC Final!"
What do you mean you can't Duel?!
Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal powers up this October!
A new enemy has come from the Barian World!
The title will be "Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal II!"
It starts broadcasting October 7th, 5:30 PM!