Big sale, big sale! Today we got a sweet bargain on our candy!
Get whatever candy you want half price!
"Flaky-licious" lolipop and...
..."Fluffy-Fluffy Chocolate Takoyaki", soy sauce flavored.
All conversely the genuine article.
And half price to boot.
Be contrarily cautious, people!
'Coz this candy here has a hidden flip side!
Hiding?
Something he's not telling us?
Damn brat! You tryin' to nitpick inside my shop?!
Is what you're saying true, contrarily?
This world is filled with hidden truths.
Duel with me and conversely prove yourself!
Let's reverse!
The Permanent Trap, Uratra C!
Contractivate!
Th-That card...!
I reversely Special Summon Gurensaurus!
Learned a lesson, on the contrary?
This is how backwards society is.
As we contrarily agreed, I'll be taking this with me.
Everything has an opposite.
Candy sold at half price, for sure.
Whether your mother's in a good mood,
or there's no homework...
I keep telling you, It's true-
Upside down..?
That guy!
Everything, without a doubt, has a hidden flipside, inversely.
Clean up! Clean up!
Naturally, this guy has a flipside, too.
Upside down! Upside down!
And so, the most suspicious of them all currently is... that guy.
Yuma Tsukumo, contrarily!
I completely forgot about that errand Sis asked for!
That boy...
Yuma Tsukumo, a guy famous for such weak Dueling skills.
It's hard to believe he manage to beat Shark, who won the national championships.
There's definitely something underneath all this, conversely.
There's no doubt he got his hands on some questionably good cards.
And if I am to obtain that card for myself...
I gotta give him this and challenge him to a Duel.
Astral?
That's what this guy wants to be called.
This guy... here?
Aren't you guys always calling him a ghost?
"I am not a ghost".
"I am Astral, who came from the Astral World."
Like that.
There he is, arguably.
This guy's been really bossy and annoying since yesterday!
I'm not "This guy". I'm Astral.
Ah--! I got it already...
It's even got a name now..
These symptoms are pretty serious...
Yuma-kun!
Why if it isn't Yuma-kun, conversely!
Tokunosuke...
What are you guys chatting about so inversely happily?
Anything bad about me?
Huh?
Well, I don't mind it either way, on the contrary!
Whether good or bad, I welcome it all contrarily!
This boy is...
I'm pretty sure he's the one from yesterday...
Who are you, anyways?
You haven't heard about me, conversely?
From the outside, he's just a middle school student.
On the inside, he's just a middle school student.
Both my inner and outter! I've achieved... inner-outer harmony!
And they are talking about... Tokunosuke Omoteura.
I'm from your neighboring class.
Okay...
Actually, I was thinking giving this to you, Yuma-kun.
Baby Tragon!
An Exceed Monster, arguably!
Exceed monster!?
This is to thank you for conversely defeating Shark!
I've always suffered contrarily a lot thanks to that guy.
Here's a proof to our friendship..
Proof of our friendship, huh?
Is it really okay for me to take this?
What is that...?
There's something bizarre overflowing from his body...
No need to to be so questionably polite.
Go on and take it, no?
In that case, then don't mind me...
Yuma!
It's your turn to water the flowers today, isn't it?!
If you don't hurry up, you won't make it on time!
H-Hey, but the card!
You can't just accept Tokunosuke's card like that.
But why?
We were in the same class as him in Elementary School, so we know.
That guy's action always has some hidden motives.
Be careful!
Hidden?
What are you guys saying?
He doesn't look like that kind of person.
Tch, some obstacles have contradictorily appeared.
However, I won't just give up contrarily like that.
I will be sure to inversely hand him this card.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Given this example, what do you think the correct answer is?
"Numbers 5:
Read the Flip Side of the Duel, Conversely"
This gigantic structure is split into several areas, that I know.
But what for?
And also, that boy from a while ago..
This is...
Yuma-kun!
The card.
HEY!
Yuma-kun!
You're leaving yourself wide open..
Aren't you guys being a little too distrusting?
Damn it...
He's got total protection, or not...
This way Yuma won't be able to take the card, conversely...
Where's all the the Exceed Monsters? Nothing on the floor here...
That guy is Yuma's classmate, Taichi..
I can use this guy... or not.
Eh--? Really?!
I promise, maybe.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go for sure--!
Awesome!
Super lucky!
Both the idiot and my bait are ready.
Taichi phase, complete success! ...Maybe.
I'm home!
Yuma!
You didn't go out and play Duel Monsters, did you?
Eh, I-I never did anything like that..
Then what is this?
To King of Duels, Yuma-sama...
From Yuma-sama's big fan...
Eh-! You're kidding!
A fan letter?!
Oh no!
Yuma!
Geez, I already told him like that no Duels of any sort allowed...
You knew about this Granny, didn't you?
For Yuma, those Duels are by no means just regular Duels, that's why.
Where'd you go off to anyways?
Oh well.
How about that! Isn't this amazing?
It's a fan letter! A fan letter!
Hm?
"What kind of effect does a fan letter have?"
Aren't you gonna ask something like that?
A fan letter is...
"I'm your fan! I love you so much!"- a letter like that!
Yuma.
You are forbidden from Dueling?
That's none of your business.
Never mind that, the fan letter! Fan letter!
Observation number eight...
Yuma is forbidden from Dueling.
Huh?
This is... the card that Tokunosuke wanted to give me?
The Baby Tragon card!
I wrote this for you with all my feelings...
So please use this card...
Eh-- So it was just a coincidence.
Alright! I got an Exceed Monster!
Second phase, arguably a success!
Afterwards, it'll be the last of the finishing touches, or not.
I'll just paste this here...
This will be Yuma's debatable end...
You'll soon learn the dark side of the world, or will you?
Good~ Morn~ ing~!
Yuma-kun!
I didn't think of you as that type of person,
but I can't believe you're doing this behind our backs.
Behind your back? Am I up to anything?
Are you up to anything?!
Even being shameless has its boundaries!
Everyone's got these anonymous photo on their mobiles!
To summarize, we know what you've been up to!
Destroying the flowerbed.
Causing trouble for our teacher.
Cheating on your tests.
And then, you even ate Taichi's lunch,
and then replaced it with a frog!
When Taichi noticed this, he took the day off from school!
Eh--?! That Taichi was...
Tch! I would never do anything like that!
That's exactly what I said!
There's gotta be a misunderstanding here!
Yuma isn't a shady guy on the inside at all!
You two, although I can understand that you want to support Yuma-kun,
there's some reaaally solid evidence here.
Yuma-kun, from now on we're strangers.
Anyway, everyone, let's go.
Ah--! W-wait a minute!
By associating yourselves with Yuma-kun, nothing good will come from it.
Like I said, it wasn't me!
The plan was a complete contradicting success!
Tch..
There isn't anyone around here to Duel with either.
Why do things end up like this? I don't get it...
I didn't do any of it...
What kind of effect is a "hidden side"?
Hidden side?
It seems like the reason you were despised, was due to that effect.
"Hidden side" means,
What you believe in your heart and what you say are totally different things, that's what it's like.
Totally different things...
Humans have a special trait like this?
Every human has this, no matter who they are.
In that case, Yuma... Why don't you have it?
I do too! My hidden side..
Yuma-kun!
What are you doing at a place like this?
Tokunosuke!
So that's what happened, no...
They totally ignored me. As expected, I'm pretty down...
However Yuma-kun, I believe in you, maybe.
Actually, I saw it. That Duel between Shark and yourself, or not.
Everything became clear from watching the Duel, or not.
Tokunosuke...
Speaking of which...
The card you beat Shark with, what was it again...
Aspiring Emperor - Hope, is that it?
Yes, yes, that's the one, I think.
Aspiring Emperor - Hope, was it?
His bizarre energy is becoming stronger.
What is going on with this...
Cheer up, or not.
Doesn't matter what everyone else says, I'm still on your side, conversely.
Just what in the world is...
Tokunosuke!
You're actually a really awesome guy.
Speaking of which, wanna Duel, or not?
Duel?
At times like this, it's good to have a Duel.
A Duel will surely freshen you up, maybe.
Alright! Then let's Duel!
What an idiot, conversely taking my bait.
With this, Aspiring Emperor Hope will become mine, maybe!
I suggest avoiding Dueling against him.
I have a bad feeling...
Bad feeling?
Don't tell me that you're also doubting Tokunosuke!
Huh?
Tokunosuke was encouraging me this whole time!
This is our friendship!
What are you doing, talking all by yourself?
N-nothing at all...
Anyways.
Let's hurry up and duel!
Let's go!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
D-Gazer, set!
Target, lock on!
AR Vision, link complete.
Duel!!
I'll take the first turn!
My turn!
Draw!
I set one Monster in face-down Defense Position.
Turn end!
So you're hardening your defense, Tokunosuke?
Because you're the one that defeated that Shark, Yuma-kun!
I have to be careful.
Yuma. For this duel, you should also be careful.
How annoying!
You need to shut up!
Again, talking to himself...
Is that some kind of strategy?
Face down defense monster... You won't know its Defense Power if you don't attack.
However, if attacking unwisely, when the Defense Power is higher than the Attack Power of my monster...
At that moment, I'll end up taking damage equal to that amount.
So if that's the case...
My turn !
Draw!!
I'll just summon a monster with higher attack power!
I will...
Summon Gagaga Magician!
Gagaga Magician, attack that face-down defense monster!!
What a light and hasty attack.
Harisenbone, Appear!
Defense point 400!
Alright! Gagaga Magician's victory!
Flip effect!
Flip effect?
When a flip effect monster is set face-down in defense position, the monster's flip effect will activate when flipped faced up.
Flip effect activate!
You take 400 points of damage!
Not bad at all..
However, it's Gagaga that has the higher attack!
Victory is mine!
It's over!
That was a weakling!
I will end my turn!
As expected of Yuma-kun, won't be easily knocked down like that!
But still, hurray!
I was able to hurt Yuma's life points!
Hurray!
Tokunosuke...
So he's using flip effect monsters, is it?
Sorry to bother you.
So Taichi-kun's mother said that he went to school as usual.
Yeah, just what does all of this mean?
Could it be, a hint to everyone's anonymous photographs...?
Huh?
That's it, those photos!
Maybe this can prove Yuma's innocence..
It's my turn!
Draw!!
I set a defense position monster!
Another face-down defending monster...
He's going after another flip effect?
And then, I set two cards face down.
Turn end!
He's able to read Yuma's attacks..
What is he aiming for...
Let's go!
My turn !!
Draw !!
I summon Full Elf!
I'll attack the face down defense position monster with Full Elf!
That face down monster, you can't attack it!
Be quiet!
Even if I take damage or suffer from the flip effect,
If Full Elf defeats his face down monster, Gagaga Magician will be able to attack directly!
Go, Full Elf!
Attack the face down defense position monster!
I knew it would come to this..
Chuubone, appear!
Defense point 300!
Alright! This one is also defeated!
Flip effect!
From my deck, I can special summon 3 Chuubone Juniors in defense position to my opponent's field!
Eh--? They're summoned to my field?
Alright!
I special summoned successfully!
Tokunosuke..
There's really no point summoning monsters to my field...
Huh? Oh no! I got the effect all wrong!
Got it wrong?
Ah--! I tend to do that a lot too!
I understand. I totally understand!
But this is a duel. I won't hold back!
I'll use Gagaga Magician to attack Tokunosuke directly!
Alright, 3600 Life Points vs. 2500!
The tables have turned! I'll use my-
W-wait a minute!
Aren't you gonna do an Exceed Summon?
Exceed Summon?
That idiot, he didn't notice this?
Yuma-kun, you can use my miss to your advantage.
Ha?
Like I said!
The three level 1 Chuubone Juniors that got on your field because of my mistake!
Ah!
I have three of the same level 1 monsters on my field!
I see! I can Exceed Summon, can't I?
What a troublesome guy...
Clearly, he is inviting Yuma to Exceed Summon.
Could it be that card...?!
I overlay my three level 1 monsters, Chuubone Juniors!
Don't complete it!
With these three monsters, I construct the Overlay network!
Exceed Summon !!
Come out, Baby Tragon!
Alright!
The Exceed Summon was a success!
You fell for it, Tsukumo Yuma!
fell for it...?
This is my continuous trap card, Uratra C.
Uratra C?
Uratra C's effect- when Baby Tragon is successfully summoned to the opponent's field,
I can choose one Exceed Monster from my opponent's extra deck,
Special summon it to my side of the field, and equip this card to it.
From my extra deck?
In other words, Aspiring Emperor - Hope now belongs to me!
We'll settle this right now!
The moment you Exceed Summoned Baby Tragon meant your luck coming to an end.
For the sake of Exceed Summoning Baby Tragon,
He special summoned the 3 Chuubone Juniors to Yuma's side of the field.
How can this be?
However, how did Tokunosuke know of my Baby Tragon?
I wrote this for you with all my feelings...
Ah! The sender of that fan letter...
Isn't that Tokunosuke!?
That's not the only thing.
The one who sent those fake photos to everyone's mobiles, just to make you all alone- that was also me.
So it was you!?
Everything has a flipside to it.
Whether it's sending you that fan letter,
Or sending everyone those fake photos.
And of course, this duel included!
Take a look at the note on your back.
The note on my back...?
When did you put this...!
"In this duel, the winner will take from the loser one card of their liking, I have agreed."
The Ante-Rule.
Tokunosuke...!!
If I win, I will be taking your Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
The Numbers..!?
You've been deceiving me since the beginning, haven't you?!
Everything you said about believing in me,
Or being my friend,
Was it all just a lie?!
This world is filled with hidden truths.
Falling for this is your own fault!
Tokunosuke--!
So this is human's hidden dark side..
Is that the bizarre power's true form?
Prepare yourself.
Continuous trap, Uratra C,
Activate !!
I special summon Aspiring Emperor Hope, from Yuma's extra deck!!
And equipping it with this card.
Appear !!
Aspiring Emperor, Hope !!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope, it got stolen away..!
Let's duel! This week's question:
Gogogo Golem's Attack Power is 1800. If it battles with Bugman Y which has 1400 Attack Power, what happens?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Tokunosuke, why must you deceive everyone around you just to win?
Your Numbers cards, all of it will become mine.
Next time, Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal! "The Treacherous Numbers!?"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Gogogo Golem would destroy Bugman Y!
Afterwards, the 400 difference in Attack Power will become damage to your opponent.
Awesome!