Revenge of the peppers!
Enemy carrots!
Grudge of the eggplants!
Desire of the cucumbers!
Whoa there! This guy's got a funny look on his face!
Dont'cha think, Droit?
This is Block D-22.
A disturbance has appeared amidst the Duel Carnival.
Someone making their own special rules.
Take a look at this!
H-Hey!
No, this is...
Tomato juice.
The hell's up with that?!
I can't work up the strength without my Duel Lunch!
Yuma, you shouldn't eat so fast.
But I'm really hungry here!
Gosh...
H-Hey!
Hey, wait up!
Hold on!
My Duel Lunch...
Whatcha lyin' around on the ground like that for?
Here! Eat my cucumber!
It'll make you feel good!
Delicious!
What the heck is this? It's really yummy!
It really is! It's delicious!
Did you grow these yourself?
They taste really good!
I-I did.
Wow man, they taste so good!
I'm Yuma Tsukumo! Thanks!
What's wrong?
What an angelic smile!
Huh?
I-I'm Yasai Housaku!
Out of all vegetables, I like tomatoes the best!
Don't you think it would be great if we turned this city into a tomato paradise?!
T-Tomato paradise?
Yessir'ee! A tomato-based theme park operated entirely by tomatoes!
If I win the Duel Carnival, I will make this city into a tomato paradise!
A-And when I do, will you over there with that smile as bright as a tomato...
W-Will you...?
Huh?
Will you act as my tomato paradise dream girl?!
HUH?!
I'm a tomato dream girl...?
A dream girl...?
Hi! I'm Tomato-chan!
I won't let you.
You won't get away with this!
Yuma!
Housaku, I won't ever forget about the vegetables you gave me.
But the path we choose to walk is far too different!
Yuma, you...
Face me, Housaku!
Fascinating!
I will win this Duel Carnival and create my tomato paradise!
And I'll make Kotori-chan into my dream girl!
You're full of crap! I swear I'm gonna break your ambitions into pieces!
Yuma...
Here I come! I'm bringin' it to ya!!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Duel!!
Hey, Yuma... We're gonna be usin' some original rules for this Duel.
"Number 30: Yuma’s Greatest Ordeal!
Fight to Death: Vegetable Death Match!"
O-Original rules?
This here!
Before you can attack, you have to pick out a vegetable from the vegetables in that basket.
You must eat that vegetable before you can attack!
I dun called it the "Vegetable Death Match"!
Wh-What the heck?! As if I'll accept a bunch of rules you just pulled out of thin air!
You guys're sure in high spirits!
Interesting! As the acting referee of the Duel Carnival, I hereby accept those rules!
Hey! Yasai, ya rascal, I guess you were the one stirring up all that commotion throughout the city.
Goshu!
Don't act on your own!
But it's all fine, Droit!
You're ruining the mood!
This "Death Match" of Yasai's is pretty amusing!
You betcha!
H-Hang the heck on!
That gives Yasai Housaku the complete advantage!
What's the big deal, kid?
You trying to say you don't like Yasai?
You shouldn't be so spiteful.
Th-That's not it!
I'm totally not being spiteful!
Then I take that as an agreement.
I approve Yasai's Death Match.
H-Hey!
Well then, good luck!
Hey, hold on!
Good deal! That gives me the right to go first!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Field Magic, Tomato Paradise!
With this card, I get to Special Summon one "Tomatoken" when I Summon a Plant-Type Monster!
Tomato Paradise?!
He really made it happen!
I Summon Tomatorooper!
Tomatorooper's a Plant-Type.
So I Special Summon a "Tomatoken"!
A tomato Monster!
Just how obsessed with tomatoes can a guy be?!
Then I activate the Continuous Magic, Catapultomato!
I release a Plant-Type Monster to inflict 400 points of damage to you!
Eat this red tomato arrow!
Eatin' a tomato on the edge of death makes for good eatin'!
I dun ended my turn!
Dammit! Tomato this, tomato that! I'll beat your deck to a pulp!
You can do it, Yuma!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Achacha Archer!
Achacha Archer inflicts 500 points of damage to the player when it's Summoned.
Go! Achacha Archer!
Good! Then, use Achacha Archer to attack Tomatorooper!
Yup!
In order to attack...
I have to eat one of the vegetables in this basket in order to attack?
Hurry an' pick one!
I know!
This texture... It's so smooth and long!
It's an... eggplant!
The hell is this?!
That's an eggplant tomato I refurbished from the brink of death!
It's a wonderful tomato you can do almost anything with!
Darn!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Yuma, why didn't you attack?
Are you still feeling your opponent out?
Dueling and vegetables are all about the timing.
You'll come to regret not attacking me!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Tomatomatryoshka!
When this card is Summoned, I can Special Summon another Tomatomatryoshka from my hand or deck!
Tomatomatryoshka is a Plant-Type!
Thus, Tomato Paradise's effect allows me to Special Summon two "Tomatokens"!
F-Five Tomato Monsters?!
This is my tomato paradise!
Then I activate the Continuous Magic, Tomatomatrix!
This card increases the Attack Power of all Plant-Type Monsters on my field by 500 points until the End Phase!
The Tomato Magic will power up this huge tomato family even further!
And I'll draw a random vegetable from my basket as the rules of this Vegetable Death Match state!
Got a pepper!
Delicious!
Yuma, it's coming!
I use Tomatorooper to attack Achacha Archer!
Tomato Striker!!
Then I direct attack with Tomatomatryoshka!
Go! Hit of the Tomatoes!!
How's that?! One more direct attack an' I'll be the winner!
Gosh, get your act together!
Yuma! It's a Trap!
Yup!
I activate the Trap Card, Heartfelt Appeal!
When I take damage during a direct attack, I gain control of the Monster on your field with the highest Defense Power until my next turn.
It looks like Tomatomatryoshka has the highest Defense Power.
Great!
I'll take the Tomatomatryoshka that hasn't attacked yet!
Guess that means I can't attack, eh?
But I still got the effect of the Catapultomato Continuous Magic!
I'll release two "Tomatokens" for 500 points of damage!
Eat this red tomato arrow!
That ends my turn!
I'm covered in tomato juice!
Are you okay, Yuma?
Darnit!
My turn, draw!
I release Tomatomatryoshka to Advance Summon Chacchaka Archer!
Once per turn, Chacchaka Archer can destroy one Magic or Trap Card on the field.
Oh yeah!
I'll use Chacchaka Archer's effect to destroy Catapultomato!
I'll then activate the Magic Card, Unprecedented Wind!
It increases the Attack Power of a Monster on my field by 1000 points!
Nicely done. Yuma, attack!
A-Attack?
I gotta draw a vegetable to attack!
This feels... tough and bulky!
It's gotta be... a cucumber!
Yuma, are cucumbers normally red in color?
Another tomato?!
That's a cucumber tomato I refurbished from the brink of death!
It's really hard! Its crisp texture makes it a topnotch appetizer!
That ain't fair, ya jerk!
How's it unfair? I'm just testing possibilities of tomatoes!
Damn you, always going on and on about tomatoes!
Yuma...?
This... tomato!
Yuma, what's wrong with you?!
If you don't eat it, you'll never get to attack!
No, I can't do it!
What?!
Hey, Yuma... Could it be you...?
That's right! I hate tomatoes!
You hate tomatoes?
They're evil!
Yeah, I don't like tomatoes! No way I can eat 'em!
So that's why you were so desperate to Duel him.
Th-Then, you weren't fighting for me...?
Huh? What the heck you talkin' 'bout?
F-Forget it!
Kotori?!
Next time I'll make you a tomato-flavored Duel Lunch.
A-Anyway, I'll set a card face-down and end my turn.
So you hate tomatoes?
You won't eat my tomatoes?!
S-Say wha?
I won't forgive anyone who dares to talk badly of my vegetables!
First I'll make you repent for your hatred of vegetables!
Then I'll create my tomato paradise!
Shut up! I could care less if you create a tomato paradise!
You bastard! I swear to win this in order to realize my dream!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Tomatomatryoshka!
Then I Special Summon a "Tomatoken"!
What?!
He's got three Level Three Monsters.
I Overlay my two "Tomatokens" and my Tomatomatryoshka!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Appear before us! Bless the Earth! Swallow the sun!
Tomato Monarch: Dread King!
C-Cute!
I use Tomato Paradise's effect to Special Summon a "Tomatoken"!
I then activate Tomato Monarch: Dread King's effect!
Once per turn, I can detach one of its Overlay Units to double its original Attack Power until the Standby Phase of my next turn!
This time it's a tomato goblin?! And its Attack Power's 3200!
This is it! Dread King, attack Chacchaka Archer!
Roasted Tomato Splasher!!
Yuma!
Good deal! It's my vict-
Why do ya still got Life?!
'Coz I activated Summon Transaction!
This card activated if I have a Monster with 1000 or less Attack Power in my hand when a Monster I control is attacked.
The battle damage is reduced by 500 points and I Special Summon a Monster from my hand with 1000 or less Attack Points!
Come out, Gagaga Girl!
In exchange, my opponent's Monster can't be destroyed in battle by the Monster Special Summoned
by Summon Transaction's effect for two turns.
Fine then. You only got 400 Life Points left.
There's no way a guy who hates tomatoes is gonna beat me!
Turn end.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
Yuma, change Gagaga Magician's level.
Right!
I change Gagaga Magician's level from four to three!
Yuma, the rest is up to you.
If you Xyz Summon, our setup for victory will be in place.
But you will have to eat a vegetable in order to allow that to happen.
R-Right, I'll have to eat one of the vegetables in this basket...
This time I'll grab anything other than a tomato!
This... This feeling in my hand...
There's no way it's a tomato!
It's a carrot!
That's a crossbred carrot and tomato I grew called a carrato.
Damn it!
Come on, Yuma! Eat that tomato!
She's right, Yuma! If you keep this up, you'll lose!
Can it!
Say what you want, but there's no way I'm gonna eat a tomato!
And you're fine with losing and allowing Housaku-kun to win and create his tomato paradise?!
If that happens, I'll go to your house and make you eat tomato salad, tomato pizza, and tomato Duel Lunches every single day!
What!?
If you don't want that, you better eat that whole tomato right now!
B-But...
She's right, Yuma!
You have no other choice if you want to beat him!
Now! Eat it!
Yuma!
Shut up! I know! I just have to eat this darn thing, right?!
I'm gonna bring it to me!
Huh? That's really good!
Yuma!
I've never eaten anything so good!
Glad to hear, Yuma! You ate it!
You finally ate it!
Now you can beat him, Yuma! Xyz Summon!
Right!
I Overlay my Level Three Gagaga Girl and Gagaga Magician!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come on out, my new friend!
Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody!
And when Gagaga Girl is used as Xyz Material with another Gagaga Monster,
she can reduce the Attack Power of one of the opponent's Xyz Monsters to zero!
Zero-Zero Call!
My Dread King!
Go, Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody!
Attack Tomato Monarch: Dread King!
Melody Wave!
And now, Dread King won't be destroyed because of Summon Transaction's effect!
But you'll still take the damage!
And now for Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody's Xyz Effect!
Right! Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody can detach one of her Overlay Units
to attack once again if there's an Xyz Monster on the opponent's side of the field!
Housaku, your tomatoes are the best!
Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody, attack Tomato Monarch: Dread King!
I'll activate Brass Fiend Mero Mero Melody's Xyz Effect once again!
Go, Mero Mero Melody!
Melody Wave!!
My tomatoes! I'm shining just like my tomatoes!
Heck yeah!
Hey! You okay, Housaku?
Hey!
Yuma!
Sorry about that. I realized thanks to you.
Tomatoes are really delicious!
I won the Duel, but your strong feelings towards tomatoes were stronger than mine.
Whaccha talkin' about?
I lost the Duel because of your strong desire to like tomatoes!
I got to see a lonely man ascend to the land of tomatoes!
I was deeply moved!
Housaku!
Yuma, my dear tomato friend!
See ya later.
He's a bit of an oddball, but he's a good guy!
You're right.
Observation #16...
"Bring it to 'em" means "loving tomatoes".
Oh yeah! I'm gonna keep this up and win the entire tournament!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
My sister suddenly ordered me to capture some man!
But the guy has created one miracle after another!
Awesome! So only the luckiest people can use that card?
So he really has Number 7!
My Numbers!
If his powers are real, then this Duel...
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"His name is Charlie, the Man with Strongest Luck in History"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!