Still not here? Freaking slow...
Hurry and deliver! Slowpoke!
What are you waiting for so early in the morning?
I already told you!
It's that. That!
That?
He's here, he's here!!
H-hold on...
H-Hold up!!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Don't you have a letter for me?
One for Yuma Tsukumo?!
Yuma Tsukumo?
Lemme see...
Tsukumo, Tsukumo, Tsukumo...
None.
I have no deliveries for a Yuma Tsukumo.
Morning, Class Rep!
You in a good mood?
You're way too energetic this early in the morning!
What's up? Something good happen?
You bet something did!
It's this! This!
It's about to start!
The World Duel Carnival!!
A World-Class Dueling Tournament set here in Heartland!
And the preliminaries kick off tomorrow!
The Grand Prize the Champion receives is a lifetime passport to Heartland
and the fame of being the first
ever Dueling Champion of the tournament.
And the best of it all,
Mr. Heartland will fulfill one wish from the Champion, no matter what it is!
Amazing!!
If I become Champion, I would wish for 100 more wishes!!
I don't think that's allowed...
If I become Champion, then Yuma-kun and I...
Cat.
Are you all gonna participate?
Without a doubt.
Lookie here!
What's that?
A Heart Piece. A key shaped like a heart.
This is the passport for the Duel Carnival.
--I have it!
--Me too!
Everyone has one!
And what about it...?
Y-Yuma? What's wrong?
I... don't have one...
Huh? Don't have what?
Why am I the only one without a Heart Piece?!
Darn it, Darn it, Darn it, Darn it!!
Yuma, you don't want to participate in the Duel Carnival?
It's not like I don't! I can't!!
But why is Yuma the only one who hasn't received one?
Weird...
Did Astral say something?
Just that I think Yuma's an idiot.
Put a sock in it!
They didn't take me as a serious Duelist, right?
Well, did you happen to register?
Wait, what?
I said that you have to register for the Duel Carnival.
There's that?
Of course, just take a look.
All you have to do is click there to register.
I thought... Heart Pieces were sent to all Duelists...
No way they could.
Duelists from around the world are participating.
I see...
So that explains it...
That should've been easy for him to figure out...
Really now, you act just like you Duel.
Yuma!
You should try to register now.
Sure!
Right on it!
Name, Address... OK, good, good...
Alright, all set!
Registrations are now closed.
What?
Thank you for trying to register!
OH NO!!!
Yuma, where are you going?
Where are you running off to?
I'm running for the World Duel Carnival!
You're as clueless as ever.
Oh, aren't you participating in the Duel Carnival?
No, I'm not interested in getting honor on stage.
Shark...
I'm gonna Duel my way.
Gotcha.
Later.
Yuma!
--Shark?
--Yeah.
It's been a while, Ryouga.
No, I believe "Shark" is the appropriate term for you, right?
And you...
What kind of shrewd trick is this?
Just a friendly hello, before the Duel Carnival starts.
I'm not in that tournament.
Well, I'll be.
You still sulking about that?
What was that?
Well, let me tell you something interesting.
Back in that Final, you got yourself disqualified by peeking at my deck in the waiting room.
But you seem a lot different now than you were back then.
After witnessing your precious someone suffer an unfortunate accident...
Ryouga, you will... become Champion...
I'm... I'm all right...
So let's say at that moment,
your opponent set down his deck in a certain way...
...and it turns out, her accident wasn't just some accident.
Y-You...
You did that to set me up?!
Why you!!
No need to be violent.
But isn't it funny?
That incident banned you from the Dueling stage.
And I became the Northern Area Duel Champion.
I'm on a different level than you. You regret that now, do you?
Y-You jerk!!
Then defeat me at the Duel Carnival!
I'll be waiting.
The World Duel Carnival...
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
"Numbers 26: It Begins!
The World Duel Carnival"
As per your wish, Ryouga will participate in the Duel Carnival.
My, my. Nice work on your part.
But why do you care about him so much?
He's an empty shell as a Duelist.
That's all necessary.
It's for when we complete collecting the Numbers.
Makes sense.
It's gonna be fun making that guy go through Hell again.
So, you gotta let me!
That's the whole reason why I came to Heartland!
Regardless of what you said,
there's nothing we can do about it.
Well can you at least try?
Just tell them that if I'm not in the Duel Carnival, I will die.
Yeah. Look, my pulse is...
Ah, no way, no way. I'm dying, I'm dying, dying...
I appreciate your visit today.
H-Hey!!
Give me one! Give me a Heart Piece!!
Damn! Open up! Open this door!!
He turned out to be the troublemaker at the end.
Heartland City population: Increasing 158%.
Increasing 5% more per hour.
They're here, here, here! They're finally here!
All ready for the Duel Carnival.
Any strange happenings?
C-Area looks normal.
Network connectivity fully functional.
All O-Bots operating normally.
So fired up!
I'm so fired up!
We can't have you this excited, Gosh?
Our committee's mission is to look over the Duel Carnival.
We have to remain calm.
Such a killjoy.
But a person with a cold heart like you, Droit, never has fun, right?
What?
Drop the arguing.
Preparations are going nice and smoothly.
Kaito.
I've been waiting.
What business do you have summoning me here?
What do you mean by "summon"?
I want you to look at the magnificent scene before the Carnival begins.
Many Duelists are congregating in Heartland City thanks to the Carnival.
Among those Duelists should be ones with Numbers, right?
It would only be meaningful if you take the Numbers away from the Duelists by winning the Carnival.
So don't let your guard down, because according to my data, there appears to be some tough competition.
Just relax.
Besides, if you can't do it, then I'll collect the Numbers!
Regardless of who they are, they're no match for me.
Just like you, Kaito-sama! How reliable!
Can it, Gosh.
Mr. Heartland-sama.
There's a youth wishing to gain qualification to participate at the main gate.
Eject him.
And to add...
He said he won't leave without a Heart Piece.
He's one unreasonable kid.
Unreasonable?
Please, this is very important to me!!
I wanna Heart Piece! A HEART PIECE!!
It's him.
Hurry and eject him.
--Roger!
--Wait!
Let him participate.
You know him?
No...
But he could be holding a Number as well.
Are you trying to hide something, Kaito?
I remember there being a strange explosion at the Heartland Institution a couple days back.
That was just a machinery malfunction.
As long as I can collect Numbers, you should have nothing to complain about.
I'm not obligated to report everything I do to you.
Understood.
Kaito-sama.
You're not going to report the incidents involving Yuma Tsukumo?
I advise you to keep quiet!
U-Understood!
If I end up facing him again...
Astral...
I will defeat him.
Hold on! Wasn't Yuma Tsukumo your rival?
That's not true.
Yuma Tsukumo...
Yuma Tsukumo?
...is nothing more than an idiot.
I ain't leavin' until I get a Heart Piece!!
Will he really receive a Heart Piece this way?
Dunno.
W-What the...
I-isn't that...
Mr. Heartland!
The real deal!
Old man!
O-Old?
Really, Yuma...!
It's Mr. Heartland-sama to you!
Oh, yeah, yeah. Heartland.
Mister!
Yeah, Mister Heartland!
"SAMA"!
Well, you see, I didn't see the online application for the Duel Carnival.
I didn't see it... because I didn't see it!
So I'm saying that I didn't click on that link to register.
Lying through his teeth...
Why can't he just confess?
I understand.
There's nothing more to be said.
I can feel your desire with my burning heart.
Allow me to make your dreams reality.
I have it...
A Heart Piece!
He brought it to me!!
Kid, that pendant...
Oh, this?
An interesting thing you got there.
It's a memento from my Dad and Mom.
A memento?
I've seen that pendant before...
Now you can fulfill your promise to your Dad.
Your promise to become Duel Champion.
Yep.
Yuma.
You have to win this.
A tournament of this magnitude will most likely have participants with Numbers.
If we can recover those Numbers...
You're right, since your memories would return.
But get this, Astral.
I'm not too obsessed about winning this tournament.
What do you mean by that?
But that contradicts the promise you made to your father.
I've been trying to figure this out.
"What is Dueling to me?"
Ever since you showed up, I've gone from a constant loser to defeating strong opponents.
And it was when I Dueled Shark and Kaito...
...that I felt the agony of defeat for the first time.
But whatever happens, I will never dislike Dueling.
But it's true that Dueling for me has nothing to do with winning and losing.
I can't describe it well...
But to me, I bond when Dueling.
Bond...
Yeah, I wanna bond with everything through Dueling.
I don't mind the results.
I just wanna Duel, regardless of what happens.
Duel regardless...
But if you lose, I'll vanish.
I cannot accept your point of view.
I understand your concern.
I will do anything to save you!
But I understand.
There's something in Dueling that transcends the end result.
That "something" is much more important!
But what about Kaito?
--Kaito?
--Yes.
He's won't side with your Dueling belief.
Kaito...
Yeah, I know that if I lose, I'll have my soul taken away.
But I won't change the way I Duel to beat that guy.
Yuma.
Kotori?
I don't know what I'll do if your soul is taken...
I...
Hey! Don't worry!
No way he'll beat me!
I can win! I can definitely win!!
Right.
You're always stubborn, Yuma.
And Astral is with you, always.
If you decide to take part, then you must win it all!
Got it?
G-Got it!!
Something more important than winning or losing...
Hmm, will this work with this...?
Everyone must be building their decks right now.
--It's finally started
--Yeah!
Man, I can't wait! Now then...
Now what?
FLIPPING!!~~
I'll win with the power of Granny Osaka!
How about it, Nama-kun. If I win, I get some new bunny pants.
What'cha talking about, and who's Nama?
Duelists who have gathered here in Heartland City!
I present to you the rules of the Duel Carnival.
The arena covers all of Heartland City.
The three-day preliminary course starts now.
Participants must accept other's challenges to Duels, no matter what.
They will Duel with a Heart Piece on the line.
The one who loses all their Heart Pieces are automatically ejected.
To qualify for the Final, you must collect six Heart Pieces to complete the puzzle.
Now allow me to declare the slogan for the Duel Carnival.
Use your Duelist's burning soul to make Heartland all the more zealous!!
HEART BURNING!!
Alright, here I go!
I'm winning this one for sure!
I'm off!
Everyone's fired up!
Yeah, I can't contain myself!
Move it, move it, move it!!
My little friend here will decide my first opponent!
Y-you OK?
Hey, you be careful playing Soccer like that here!
It's decided! My first opponent will be you!!
Wha....
Me?!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
My first opponent has been decided!
He's one strong guy with a Soccer Deck!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The World Duel Carnival Kick Off! The Flaming Striker, Kakeru"
I'm gonna Bring it to 'em!
The Monster Popularity Contest's Top Three!!
In third place is...
Baby Tragon!
Don't let his cute looks fool you.
He's one reliable friend!
In second...
The Submersible Aero Shark!
It can wipe the floor with it's effect!
And in first place...
It's Galaxy Eyes Photon Dragon!!
It's Kaito's Ace Monster and is the most popular!
Thanks for voting everyone!