Shuta is able to take pictures of the future using the power of his Number.
According to his photo,
not only I will lose the Duel in that "foreseeable" future, but the airship Kotori rode will fall as well!
Stop joking around!
I'm gonna beat you and rescue Kotori at all costs!
You only have two turns left.
Alright, feel free to come at me!
Towards that future with your inevitable defeat!
Kotori, I will definitely save you!
Let's go! My turn, draw!
Bye-Bye damage!
I Summon Achacha Archer!
When Achacha Archer is Summoned successfully, it can inflict 500 damage to my opponent!
Sweet, I did it!
Didn't I say I already saw through everything?
Not only that I will receive 500 damage here,
but that you will also set the Trap Card Bye-Bye Damage from your hand onto your field!
This picture is the proof!
How's that possible?
Bye-Bye Damage is in Yuma's hand.
When a Monster he controls is attacked, that Monster is not destroyed by battle,
and for the battle damage Yuma received, his opponent will take twice that amount as damage!
Indeed he is planning to set Bye-Bye Damage at this point of time.
Alright, just set it! You don't have a choice anyway.
I set one card and end my turn!
If his pictures really do record the "future", then...
...we have no chance of winning!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Kotori-chan, can you hear me?
Akari-san!
"Number 36: "The Power To Open A Path To The Future!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray"
Are you injured?
N-No...
What's happening inside the blimp?
About that...There is lot of smoke coming out...
the blimp is shaking, and everyone is in a panic!
It's gonna be okay, calm yourself!
I will save you guys for sure!
Hang in there until then, got it?!
Yes!
My turn, draw!
Due to Telephoto Lens' effect,
it will gain 400 ATK for every card in his hand.
Thus Scoop Shooter's ATK is 3000!
If you take an attack like that...
Yeah... I will take 1800 points of big damage...
If Bye-Bye Damage will be successfully activated,
then I can inflict double of that amount, 3600 points, back to that guy!
But he will already know that...
I activate the Magic Card, Night Shoot, from my hand!
What?!
This card can destroy one set Magic or Trap Card on my opponent's field.
Alright, which one should I choose?
I select the card on the right side!
That's Bye-Bye Damage!
And then I Summon Scandal Sniper!
Then, since I have two less cards in my hand,
Scoop Shooter loses 800 ATK.
Even so, it still has enough Attack Power to get the job done!
Alright, go, Scoop Shooter! Attack Achacha Archer!
I am not done yet!
I attack you directly with Scandal Sniper!
Then I activate Scandal Sniper's effect!
When it attacks successfully and inflicts damage to my opponent,
Scandal Sniper gains two levels and switches to Defense position!
After that I activate the Magic Card from my hand, Xyz Flame!
During your next turn, no Monster other than Xyz Monsters can declare an attack!
Now all the preparations are finished!
Now I end my turn!
It's finally the fifth turn after all...
As this photo indicates, you will Summon Hope during the fifth turn,
and lose to me in the sixth turn.
Who are you?
No one can enter here besides the authorized personnel!
It's an emergency!
This is a matter of life and death!
Are you responsible for this blimp?
What's the current situation?
Well... the engine on the left side is on fire due to malfunction...
Plus the pilots are unconscious at the moment...
Is there a remote control?
No, we never had that option installed...
Isn't there any other way to resolve it?
Kotori...
My turn, draw!
That card is Gogogo Giant!
Right now that's the only Monster Card in your hand!
If you Summon Gogogo Giant successfully, you can Special Summon Gogogo Golem from your Graveyard!
Now you have two Level Four Monsters on your field to Summon Hope.
That's the only thing you can possibly do!
Darn it all...
Alright, just Summon Hope! This is your future!
What's wrong, Kotori?
The engine...the other engine too...
Kotori!
Wait for me, Kotori...
In order to save you, I will defeat Shuta Hayami here and now!
Huh? What do you mean defeat Hayami-senpai?
Do you know this guy?
I do...but...
Yuma, why are you Dueling with Hayami-senpai?
He is the one who caused the whole incident!
He was possessed by a Number, and acquired the power to change future at his will!
Then he utilized that power to take scoop photos from those so-called "accidents"!
How... how can that be?
He showed it to me!
Before we were talking, the picture of the falling blimp!
And that actually became reality!
No way... My upperclassman isn't that kind of person!
The pictures he took were always heartwarming. They made people who looked at them feel happiness!
Such despicable behavior just for the sake of scoop photos...
I don't believe this...!
Kotori, he is no longer the Shuta Hayami you once knew!
Once possessed by Numbers, a human's desire will be amplified!
You already knew Kotori is on that blimp.
And you're fine with the blimp falling?
That was merely my imagination,
For me that counts as a tragedy as well.
Upperclassman?!
But my imagination will transfer into pictures without any abridgment,
and it is bound to become reality!
As much as I feel sorry for Mizuki-kun, that image in my mind...
How can I miss it as a professional photographer?
You can't...
Indeed I am different than before.
My soft pictures for the people...
I suddenly realized that scoop photos can bring a bigger impact.
Ever since that day...
That card - that Number...
The moment I acquired it... I completely changed.
I can now shoot scoop photos at will!
In order to bring bigger impact to society, I need more accidental scoops!
A single Number card has such amazing power hidden inside.
If I can collect more...
I will become the number one Professional photographer in the world!
This is why I am participating in the Duel Carnival!
Every single one of them... They're all wrong!
Dueling isn't a tool for revenge! Nor something to fulfill your own greed!
You can shout all you want, but you will not win against me.
Right! You can only walk on the path I have already set for you!
Stop that nonsense!
I should mention that I won't tolerate you surrendering.
You will carry out the Duel with me until the end and lose.
Then I will take your Numbers away.
That is what's been decided.
Shut up!!
I'm the only one who gets to decide my future!!
You decide yourself?
I won't let a guy like you decide me and Kotori's future!
I Summon Gogogo Giant!
Right, that's how it should be!
Then use its Monster Effect from your Graveyard...
I Special Summon Gogogo Golem in Defense Position!
After this effect is used, Gogogo Giant will switch to Defense Position as well!
I guess I really have no other choice but to Summon Hope!
But you won't be able to escape the path he set for you doing that.
Don't panic, Yuma. When in doubt, take a break.
Try to find a way to counter the prediction,
and you may just be able to open a path to a new future.
Though I don't know what kind of path awaits you, if you deny the future he has created for you.
But you're the one who said that you're the only one who gets to create your future.
What's wrong? You won't accept your fate?
Now call out Hope.
Call him!
CALL HIM!
I won't!!
What!?
I won't move as you predicted!
I shall end my turn like this!
E-End your turn?
What's that supposed to mean? Don't get off track!
These pictures are the evidence...
You will summon Gogogo Giant and Gogogo Golem,
then Summon Number 39, Aspiring Emperor - Hope, during your fifth turn.
Finally during the sixth turn, I will destroy Hope.
Then, your Numbers will be mine.
Your future is already arranged accordingly!
Those pictures have nothing to do with it!
I won't ever walk on the path you have set for me!
No matter what kind of future is awaiting me!
I will only walk on my own path! I decide it!
Alright, it's your turn!
You cannot fight destiny! My turn, draw!
I Summon Panic Paparazzi!
Then I activate Panic Paparazzi's effect!
When I release this card, Scoop Shooter gains two levels!
Now I have two Level Six Monsters!
I overlay Scoop Shooter and Scandal Sniper!
With these two Monsters, I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 25!
Fullmetal Photoglide - Focus Force!
So here it comes! Numbers!
Big sis...
It's alright, we will be alright...
Yuma...
Go, Focus Force!
Attack Gogogo Golem!
Lethal Negative: Kill Shot!!
When Gogogo Golem is in Defense Position,
once per turn, it cannot be destroyed by battle!
Idiot! I activate Focus Force's effect!
Once per turn, by detaching one Overlay Unit,
when my opponent's Monster activates its effect, Focus Force can negate that effect!
Do it, Focus Force!
Soul Develop!
How's that? This is Focus Force's power!
But none of this was captured in the photographs he took.
That's true!
Hey! Why'd you go and destroy Gogogo Golem?!
I can't call out Hope with just Gogogo Giant!
As I thought, his Dueling relies entirely on a pre-constructed path.
He simply moves forward without even thinking.
It is true that he can capture the future on the pictures he takes using the power of the Number.
However, that only applies to what he visualizes after he flashes the shutter.
All of the opponents he defeated up until now
who were captured on his photos were told they would not be able to escape what had already been planned out.
It was merely a curse of words that repeated endlessly.
But when you declared the end of your turn, Yuma, you broke through that curse.
You do not have the power to create the future through pictures!
It can't be...! It's a lie! I won't accept it...
A future beyond my imagination!
Those photos have no meaning at all!
The future has already been changed!
He was solely relying on his Number,
thus it is very obvious that he hasn't sharpened his Dueling skills.
Yuma, this man is no match for you!
But... Numbers can only be defeated by Numbers!
If you wish to win, then you have to Summon Hope!
My turn ends now!
Kotori... I am definitely going to save you!
Let's go! My turn, draw!
I Summon Overlay Owl!
I activate Overlay Owl's Monster Effect!
By paying 600 Life Points,
I can send one Overlay Unit from a Xyz Monster my opponent controls to the Graveyard!
I won't let you do that!
When my opponent activates a Monster Effect, by detaching one Overlay Unit, that effect will...
Whatever you do, you will lose your Overlay Unit!
Oh no!!
Sorry for the wait. Allow me to show you Hope you've wanted to see so badly!
I Overlay the Level Four Gogogo Giant and Overlay Owl!
With these two Monsters, I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 39, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
There you are... Hope!
This is it, Hope's ATK is 2500,
But my Focus Force's ATK is 2800.
Next turn...
There is no next turn for you!
Go, Yuma!
I'll bring it to 'em!
Chaos XYZ Change!
Come forth, Chaos Number 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
Hope evolved!?
I activate Hope Ray's Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it gains 500 Attack Points!
Overlay Charge!
Also due to this effect, my opponent's Monster will lose 1000 ATK!
How could that be? My future...
You aren't the only one who can change the future!
I can too! No... anyone can! As long as they muster their courage to bring it to 'em!
The future can be changed!
Go, Hope Ray!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!!
Kotori, sis, it's alright now!
I defeated Shuta and have undone the power of the Number!
Kotori!
Yuma...
Sis...
Though that strange power has disappeared, there still is no change inside the blimp!
The height of the blimp is drastically decreasing! If this goes on...
You can't be serious, Sis!
Three kilometers behind the airship, there is an unidentified object approaching at high speed!
We will now switch to the actual image!
That is...
What's happening, sis?
Yuma, check that out!
Kaito!
Miss...
It's fine, we are going to be fine.
What? The velocity of the blimp's decline has decreased!
The blimp is slowly recovering to the appropriate angle!
Just what is going on here?
Orbital, full power!
Understood!
Thank god, thank goodness!
Mama!
Kotori!
Yuma! Thank you for saving me!
You should thank Kaito for that.
Kaito!
I owe you one!
All Duelists really are friends!
Don't get the wrong idea.
If the blimp had fallen and caused a panic in the city, the Duel Carnival might have been canceled.
Kaito...
That guy...
Hayami-senpai!
Don't tell me you...!
No... I just instinctively clicked the shutter...
Umm... Mizuki-san, I am very sorry for letting you experience that hazard.
I can't believe I actually did that.
Upperclassman...
Forget about it. Everyone is safe now. Isn't that a good?
Yuma-kun...
Sis...
Isn't that a good one? Look!
If you can take such great pictures, you sure don't need Numbers.
U - Umm... Thank you.
But would you mind taking a picture of me?
Imagine my future of me becoming the Duel Champion.
Don't you decide your own future?
That's true, isn't it?
Why are you talking to yourself?
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Tokunosuke was caught by the Tournament Committee members for playing dirty tricks.
If this continues, that guy..
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Disqualified from the W.D.C.!?
Heartland's Assassins Droite and Gauche"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!