It's the World Duel Carnival Tournament Finals!
The time has finally come to decide the best in the world!
Out of the 23 best Duelists who survived the preliminaries!
Here goes! I'm aiming for Duel Champion!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Yuma, the fireworks are starting!
Today's the Duel Carnival Tournament Finals, right?
How long are you gonna keep sleeping?
C'mon, get up alr-
Huh?
He's not here.
Grandma!
Hey, where's Yuma?
Oh, in order to make sure he definitely isn't late,
he slept outside the entrance to Heartland all night.
And he was so pumped up...
He's such a moron!
Yuma is experiencing the importance of this tournament in his own way.
The fireworks have announced the start of the World Duel Carnival-
Cleaning. Idiot's room. Cleaning.
Shark's so cool!
I hear that Kaito fellow's pretty hot too!
There's only 23 remaining among more than 10,000 participants.
This should be an awesome tournament!
Yeah! They're all incredible Duelists!
I wonder who will win the championship?
IV for sure!
That hurts!
Why are you sleeping out here?
Man...
What was that all of a sudden?
What're you guys doing here?
He's still half-alseep.
To summarize, he thinks this is his room.
He's like a wild kitty.
Wake up and open your eyes!
This is Heartland!
Today's the starting day of the World Duel Carnival Tournament Finals!
Duel Carnival...?
That's right!
Yup, yup, yup, yup!
He really is an idiot.
Man, it would've been bad if I overslept!
Then there was no point in sleeping in front of the entrance, was there?
Hey, the opening ceremony is about to begin.
We've got to hurry.
- Oh crap, crap, crap!
- Wait up!
Amazing!
It's huge!
We're gonna Duel here?!
It's awesome!
Does this mean some kind of Field Magic has been casted?
No! This is real!
Either way, this is incredible!
Heart Burning!
I now declare the start of the World Duel Carnival Tournament Finals!
The first stage will be the Park Section!
In other words, we will Duel using this entire Heartland as the stage!
Going by the name Duel Coasters!
Duel Coasters?
To summarize, they Duel using those roller coasters.
But how?
I'm not really sure...
But doesn't it sound interesting?
Right, Yuma?
Yeah, bring on whatever!
It'd be a shame if I can't enjoy this, seeing as how I made it this far!
But Yuma, aren't you going?
Gosh...
You can do it, Yuma!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Now then, the 23 Duelists who won in the preliminaries to get here,
Muster up every bit of your intellect and your strength to fight!
Number 51: "Here we come, Tournament Finals!
Duel Coasters, Go!"
And set that prestigious title of first ever World Duel Champion as your goal!!
Amazing!
So these are the Duel Coasters?!
I'm getting excited!
You'll get hurt badly if you get too worked up.
Duel Coasters are no game.
You're... Droite!
Indeed, what Droite said is true.
This will be a true showdown that puts our lives on the line.
Gauche!
But be sure to enjoy it!
Right!
Of course!
It's IV! IV!
Wow, he's so cool!
Kaito-sama, please, you must take good care of your body.
Orbital, stop time.
I'm about to search for those holding Numbers.
B-But if you do that, you'll end up revealing yourself to Number Holders instead!
0.1 seconds is good enough! Hurry and do it!
U-Understood!
Okay.
Just now...
H-He noticed after all!
You did your job, so get lost!
U-Understood!
Man, some awesome members are gathered here!
This should be a blast!
Among them are Kaito and Shark...
And excluding Tron and his group,
there is bound to be a number of powerful opponents here.
This is so freaking cool!
I'm getting pumped!
So that's our prey, right?
Then we'll start with a small deposit.
The rest comes when you complete your job.
And the target is...?
A boy named Yuma Tsukumo.
They were gathered...
They've been gathered here.
Kaito, you must retrieve those Numbers!
Now! Soon enough, we will fire the signal!
Fellow warriors, prepare for battle!
These Duel Coasters will link to your D-Pads!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
At last, the time has come to bet your lives in these Coasters!
The Heart Pieces you all gathered during the preliminaries
will act as the starting key for the Duel Coaster!
Set your Heart Pieces in the designated location in the cockpit!
So that's a map, huh?
What the? There's M and T marks all over the thing.
"Magic" and "Traps"... I see.
This is well thought out.
They're gone! Gone, gone! My Heart Pieces're gone!
Where'd I leave them?!
Yuma keeps looking down.
What the heck is he doing?
Maybe the mental pressure made him snap?
Why's he fooling around at a time like this?
No... He doesn't seem to be fooling around.
Cleaning done. Cleaning done. Found heart in idiot's room.
A heart?
This. This.
Wait, that's...!
Heart Pieces!
My Heart Pieces're gone! What'll I do?!
Yuma! Akari-san just contacted me.
They found your Heart Pieces in your room!
They're on there way to Heartland.
My sis did?! I owe her one!
Wait!
Stay there, Yuma!
Got it, everyone?!
- Yeah!
The time has now come!
We shall now drop the curtain on this stage of battle that will determine the best in history!
Already?! They didn't make it in time at all!
We start in ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
- Heart Pieces!
- Two!
One!
Fire!
Oh my! Only one, Contestant Yuma Tsukumo's Coaster, didn't start!
Did he encounter some trouble?!
They left! Hurry and get here, Sis!
Akari-san!
I'm counting on you!
Right!
I'll leave it to you!
Okay!
Pass!
Leave it to me!
Whoa!
I'm on my way, Yuma!
Kotori!
Catch!
God, she won't make it in time!
Yuma!
Kotori!
Here's your Heart Pieces! Catch!
Yes, it's moving! Here I go!
Hey, Yuma!
Huh? Why are you in here too, Kotori?
I was running and I ended up in here before I realized it!
Now I can't get off...
Hang on tight, Kotori!
Since it's come to this, the two of us will have to fight together!
You mean three.
I'm here too.
This is an unexpected development!
Contestant Yuma, who had a delayed start, has ridden into view with a girl in tow!
The Coasters were originally made for one.
However, as the founder of this tournament,
I shall personally permit it!
This is feels amazing! Coasters are the best!
Slow down a little!
I can't do that! I've already fallen far behind the others!
But how do we Duel in these things when you can't even find your opponent?
I'm riding on one lane all by myself...
Look, Yuma.
There's two Coasters riding one land.
Move, move, move! I'll send anyone in my way flying like a bullet!
Draw!
I Summon Heroic Challenger - Spartas!
My opponent's got Blood Storm. Interesting!
Then I'll just activate the Magic Card Force from my hand!
This card's effect halves Blood Storm's Attack Power...
...and increases Spartas' Attack Points by the same amount!
Go! Attack him!
Straight Javelin!!
Unbelievable!
Thank goodness...
If we take even one wrong step here, we'll suffer heavy injuries.
Yeah...
You're ten years too early to be riding in front of my lane!
I get it.
If you're on the same lane as someone else, you have to Duel them.
Right.
Plus, you can switch lanes freely if you wish to fight the person you encounter.
Go, Jaws!
Shark Scream!!
I have no shame!
Wow... That's Shark for you!
Goodness... Where's Yuma?
You're putting on quite the show!
You won't get away, IV!
I swear to utterly crush you in this tournament!
Big mouth for such a weakling!
I Summon Gimmick Puppet - Bomb Egg!
Direct Attack! Go!
Yes, bomb!
Be gone, trash!
As always, he's always lusting for blood.
Despite having no idea what kind of prolonged battle awaits us in the near future.
Thus, rather than battling, I should invest all my attention toward protecting and increasing my Life Points.
You are in my way! Move at once!
Send him flying, Vylon Disigma!
Direct Attac-
Wha...What the?
Those who dare to come close to me shall be consumed by Hell's Inferno!
I activate the Trap Card, Sun of the Abyss!
When a Monster holding 2000 or more Attack Points attacks me directly,
this card deals the opposing player 800 points of damage for each card he holds in his hand!
What?!
As I suspected, this is a 'Magic Point'.
Moreover, the set card was the God of Healing, Dian Keto.
The effect of this card increases my Life Points by 1000 points!
Well done, V.
IV and Shark are both fighting relentlessly with all of their might.
As for him...
How is Yuma Tsukumo faring?
Everyone's so strong! Man, I so wanna start Dueling already!
Your wish may soon me granted.
Look up ahead.
Huh?
But... I just passed them by.
Thanks to this guy's late start,
we don’t need to lure him out from the group.
All we gotta do is crush him like we promised!
Then we'll be rolling in dough!
That's right. I will pay you as much money as you want.
Only after you show me just how strong Yuma Tsukumo really is.
Let's go! As we planned before, we'll use Formation One!
Roger!
They're catching up to us!
What's with these guys?
Clearly they've been waiting to ambush you, Yuma!
They're attacking from both sides to prevent you from escaping to the side lanes!
That's dangerous, you know!
Darn! I'm gonna get away from you!
There's a 'T' mark up ahead...
A Trap Card?!
That was Underground Machine Gun.
It deals 200 points of damage for every card you have in your hand and on the field.
How can you say that so calmly?!
So they set Magic and Trap Cards throughout the course?
I can't believe he didn't notice such an obvious trap.
His Dueling skills must not be anything to brag about!
Then let’s finish him off as soon as possible so we can go home and count our cash!
Hey, kid. Duel against us.
What?!
Here goes! Formation Two!
Roger!
They caught up so fast!
I Summon Magnet Eagle Delta from my hand!
I Summon Magnet Saucer!
I Summon Magnet Saucer as well!
They already Summoned Monsters?!
And it's three-on-one!
This has become a three-on-one battle from the get-go!
Is this the Duel Coaster's...?
No, a testament of the World Duel Carnival Final?!
Now then, let's see it, Yuma Tsukumo.
Just how strong are you?
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
A huge battle is underway between the Finalists who made it to the Coasters!
Let's go, Duel Coasters!
But in the beginning, a trio named Fallguys have ambushed me!
And when I was in a desperate situation, she...!
Yuma, they're aiming for you.
What?!
The lane's been blocked!
That's their team play!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
The Duel Coasters Vs the Rampaging Train!
Hey, why the heck are you here?!
Excalibur is a sword wielded by a king long ago.
That's got nothing to do with the Great Me!
I didn't say Great Me, I said King.
(Note: oresama, ousama)
You tryin' ta' praise me?
That's Osaka!
You best be cuttin' it out!