Our hearts are resolved!
The future of everyone is at stake!
We challenge you to a Duel, Dr. Faker!
Very well. I will be your opponent.
Yuma...
Good luck!
Show him your awesome 'Bring it to 'em', Yuma!
What could you guys do to me anyway?
Here I will crush you into pieces!
Stop joking! You will be the one who gets crushed!
I'll make you pay right here!
I'll crush you and your absurd ambitions!
Dr. Faker!
Very well. So you say you're opposing me?
Faker!
Oh?!
Now! I'll take the three of you on at the same time!
Get ready to lose!
Let's go!
Duel Disk, set!
Duel Mode - Photon Change!
D-Gazer - Set!
Duel!
I am begging you... Kaito, Yuma, Shark.
The future is in your hands!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Your shared Life will be 4000.
The three of you will each hold 4000 Life.
I'll have the first draw!
"Number 69: The Three Heroes Unite
One Last Duel For The Future!"
I'll show it to you. The Dueling of my soul.
I send Garbage Ogre from my hand to the Graveyard,
to add one Garbage Lord from my deck to my hand.
Then, by paying 1000 Life, Garbage lord can be special summoned from the hand.
I special summon 3 Garbage Lords!
What?!
Appear! 3 Garbage Lords!
Three monsters at once?!
What are you afraid of?
No... No I am not!
It's coming!
I overlay my 3 LV 5 Garbage Lords!
I use these three Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Take a good look!
From all the Numbers this stands on top of, the strongest of all Numbers.
Equipped with superior armor that will shock the world!
This is...
Did it absorb the power of the other Numbers?
Come forth, No. 53!
Heart-Earth the Counterfeit Deity!
A monster with 100 ATK
This is...
As it happens, my Number is...
...immune to your magic cards, traps and monster effects.
I set 2 cards and end my turn!
Alright! First is me!
Wait, Yuma! There is something strange with the guy's Number.
A 100 ATK monster, that's what it is! I'll just kick it!
So you are my first opponent, Yuma Tsukumo.
Then you will be the first who gets wiped out by me!
I won't let that happen!
Right here with me are Shark and Kaito!
And because of Astral, I gained those friends here!
Astral, I'll save you for sure!
My turn, draw!
I summon Goblinbergh!
When Goblinbergh has been summoned successfully,
I can special summon a LV 4 or lower monster from my hand!
Appear! Gagaga Magician!
Then I will overlay my LV 4 Goblinbergh  and Gagaga Magician!
With these 2 monsters, I build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth! No. 39!
The power of the bond between Astral and me!
Aspiring Emperor Hope!
So Aspiring Emperor Hope appeared.
But at this moment I activate the permanent trap Battle Route!
With this card, while I have a monster on my field,
the opponent's monsters in attack position have to conduct battle.
Huh?!
What does he mean?
Huh? What do you mean 'What does he mean'?
That monster just has 100 ATK.
So... why would he activate a card that forces a battle?
Oh, right!
Does this mean, that he wants us to attack?
Right. So if someone-
Gah, then he's beyond help!
Go, Hope! Attack Heart eartH!
As I thought, you are as reckless as Kazuma.
Hope Sword Slash!
Foolish... I activate the effect of Heart eartH!
When this card is attacked,
I can equip it with a monster card from my graveyard!
I equip Garbage Ogre to Heart eartH.
Then Heart eartH will gain ATK
by the amount of the ATK of the opponent's battling monster!
What?!
So this is, what it means.
Even though the ATK of this Number is low,
every time it gets attacked, it still has the higher ATK than the opponent.
Now Heart eartH 's ATK is 2600.
Take that! Fake Burn!
I won't let you!
I detach one overlay unit to negate the attack!
Well done, Yuma! Go!
Sure! The quick play magic Double Up Chance!
This card: If the attack of a monster was negated,
it can attack once again, with its attack power doubled!
Go, Hope! Attack Heart eartH once again!
Hope Sword Double Slash!
Did you see! This is my Hope!
In front of me, your Hope is nothing but garbage!
It will be ground to dust by me!
Heart eartH's effect activates!
By sending the card equipped to Heart eartH to the graveyard,
it will not be destroyed!
Additionally, when Heart eartH's equip card is sent to the graveyard,
half of the amount of the ATK-change will be inflicted as damage to the opponent!
Yuma!
Then I detach one overlay unit to activate Heart eartH's effect!
The amount of damage Heart eartH inflicted to the opponent
will replenish my life points!
What?
This Number...
It also has an ability to recover life?!
Heart eartH... it can raise it's ATK and evade destruction.
And after being attacked, it replenishes Life Points...
This is just... the strongest of the Numbers.
I set one card and end my turn.
As usual , you're a botcher with dueling.
But it was pretty good.
Leave the rest to me.
Shark.
My turn, draw!
With these fangs of mine, I will tear you into shreds! Faker!
Shark?!
Hey!
I-It's nothing!
This is bad.
This is from before...
What's up? Are you afraid, Ryouga?
Shut up! I summon Hammer Shark!
And in this duel, I can use the power of my partner's cards!
I send all the overlay units of Hope to the graveyard!
My overlay units of my Hope are...!
Stop being fussy!
But I...!
By sending the overlay units to the graveyard,
I can special summon Xyz-Remora!
When this guy is used for an Xyz-summon,
the materials needed for the Xyz-summon are reduced by the number of overlay units sent to the graveyard.
What!?
I overlay my two LV 4 Xyz-Remora and Hammer Shark!
I build the Overlay Network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 32!
Sea Biting Shark Drake!
Yuma, your dueling gave me a hint.
Hu?
Just look!
From my hand I activate the equip magic Shield Fin!
I equip it to Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Yuma, I'll borrow your Hope!
Go, Hope! Attack Heart eartH!
Your attack does not reach this genius of mine!
I activate Heart eartH's effect!
When this card is attacked, I can equip one monster card from the graveyard to this card.
When equipped with a card by this effect,
the ATK of Heart eartH
will be increased by the original ATK of the opponent's monster!
Eat this, Ryouga!
Trash like you has to be melted down!
Fake Burn!
I've been waiting for this moment!
I activate Shield Fin's effect!
With this card, until the end of this turn the original ATK of the equipped monster is changed to Zero,
and it can't be destroyed by battle!
What?!
Clever.
He figured out the weakness of that Heart eartH.
Huh?!
Now the damage we get is only 100!
I see!
Because Hope's original ATK is Zero now, the ATK of Heart eartH didn't increase!
That's right, Yuma.
Thanks to you I could find the thing's weakness.
Here we go! Heart eartH can use its ATK-power up only once per turn!
And if the ATK has not been changed, he can not give effect damage!
Roar, Shark Drake! Attack Heart eartH!
Depth Bite!
So the starving shark detected a faint smell of blood.
But this kind of damage won't affect me!
Heart eartH's effect activates!
By sending the equipping card to the graveyard, this card will not be destroyed.
Oh! What should we do!
He just recovered again!
It’s time to dump your hope too.
I activate Heart eartH's monster effect!
Once per turn I can detach 1 overlay unit,
to inflict the halved amount of damage I received to the opponent!
What? Impossible!
Take this! The judgment of my genius!
Shark!
Damn...
Then that guy's life recovery can be changed into an attack.
I set one card and end my turn!
I'll take over your feelings...
Kaito...
My turn, draw!
Now it's my turn! Dr. Faker!
Kaito, you are so stupid.
I can't believe you'd try to defy me!
I'll send you to hell for this!
Stop annoying me! I will definitly beat you!
Haruto - With these hands, I'll do anything to save you!
Haruto!
I set one card!
Then I summon Photon Crusher!
Come forth! Photon Crusher!
Then I special summon Photon Slayer!
This card cannot be normal summoned.
If there is an Xyz-monster on my side of the field,
I can special summon it from my hand in face-up defense position.
I release Photon Crusher and Photon Slayer!
Darkness within the shining galaxy...
Become the light of hope and live as my servant!
The incarnation of light descends!
Come forth! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Yuma's bonds with them are becoming one.
Hope... Shark Drake... Galaxy-Eyes...
All their ace monsters are lined up.
Now, Kaito!
You idiot son, come at me!
Kaito!
Don't bother!
I am fine...
It... How is this fine?
Seems like your body as a Number Hunter is already at its limits, Kaito.
Stop the joke! This is what has become of Kaito's body for your sake!
You're still are Kaito's dad, aren't you?!
Dr. Faker,
for your lies, me and Galaxy have stained ourselves.
Now is the time to make you pay for that!
Kaito, I wonder if you really can?
True, if I use the effect of Shield Fin, I can inflict damage on him for certain.
But the problem is, how he will use the effect of the overlay units of Heart eartH.
Even the damage he gets, can be bounced back on us.
We don't stand a chance against him...!
But...
Yuma, I'll borrow your monster!
Sure!
I'll attack Heart eartH with Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Useless! When this card is attacked,
I can equip to it one monster from my graveyard!
I will equip it with this card!
Garbage Ogre!
Now the ATK of Heart eartH is 2600!
Take the Fake Burn!
But now, the effect of Shield Fin, which is equipped to Hope, activates!
The ATK of the equipped monster is changed to Zero,
and it can't be destroyed by battle!
Then I attack Heart eartH with Shark Drake!
So it's the same all over again!
Go, Shark Drake!
Depth Bite!
Heart eartH's effect activates!
By sending the equip card to the graveyard, destruction is prevented.
Another effect of Heart eartH activates!
Once per turn, I can detach 1 overlay unit,
to inflict half of the damage I received, in total 1350, as damage to my opponent!
That's it! Kaito!
Bad! Our remaining life is 1200!
If this attack connects...
Now, kneel before me, Kaito!
You're the only one kneeling here!
Quickplay magic, Photon Prevent!
This card: While there is a Photon Monster on my field,
the player will not receive Effect damage!
What is this?!
Alright! And Kaito still has the attack with Galaxy-Eyes!
That guy has 2450 life remaining,
if the 3000 ATK of Galaxy-Eyes comes through...
Dr. Faker, I have followed your orders all the time!
As a Number Hunter, I kept on hunting innocent souls.
I believed in helping Haruto with this.
But... all this was a lie...
You are...!
I absolutely won't forgive you!
For the sake of Haruto and for those many souls,
are you ready for your repentance?!
Go! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
Yes? Did they win?
Yuma and them won, right?
We finally beat Dr. Faker with our own hands!
Serves him right!
Oh... What?!
That's...
Un... unbelievable?!
Why on earth is there a new Number!?
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The Number of Faker is confronting us
By uniting our powers, we thought we had beaten it, but
something unbelievable appeared in front of us!
What's this? Why is there a new Number?
Why? Faker?!
Yuma, there still is hope in you...
With our power and our bonds, we will absolutely defeat this guy!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Most Evil, Horrifying Dragon appears!
False Skeletal God Dragon, Heart-eartH Dragon!"
Who on earth... are you?
Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Shark Drake!
Galaxy-Eyes!
For these three to fight alongside each other is...
Go! Hope-Drake-Eyes!
I can't believe they combined together!
Uh, no they didn't.