And again!
God Rage!
Hey, get a hold of yourself, Kaito! Kaito!
Kaito!!
Faker-sama... Dr. Faker-sama!
Kaito... That Kaito has lost to Tron!
After all that happened, shouldn't we terminate the tournament...
Why should we terminate it now?
Everything goes as planned.
As long as we still have the Sphere Field to go,
the Finals will continue as planned.
As-As you wish.
Kaito... has lost...
Kaito's... Kaito's soul is...
Tron took it away.
The only thing Kaito wanted... was to save Haruto.
He only wanted to protect what's precious to him.
Yuma.
Tron used the power of the crest to take away the souls of Droite, Kaito, and Haruto.
If he is defeated in a Duel...
If that power were to be destroyed, then perhaps...
Sure, I'll do that! I'm gonna kick his butt for sure!
Yuma!
Guys...
Good luck to you, Yuma-kun.
I've got high hopes for you!
Sure, leave it to me!
I'll show you the power of my 'Bring it to 'Em'!
You better get the championship~meow.
Yuma, you're representing us as a Duelist.
Don't you let yourself be defeated by that Tron!
Come on, Yuma, you as well!
Yuma!
Yuma-kun.
Y-Yeah!
Guys, thank you. I'm gonna win the championship for sure.
With everyone's feelings.
Yeah!
Yuma!
Wow, a Duel Lunch!
Thank you, Kotori!
Eat it and be sure to win!
Leave it to me!
You better promise me, okay?
I'm absolutely positive!
Now then, I'm going.
He'd still go even if I stopped him...
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Like there is only one sun in the sky, this shining glory is just as unique!
Anyone who dared to stand in their way was deemed a foe.
Many a battle did they fight, including the survival-death matches,
"Number 65: An All-Out Battle Between Numbers! Yuma vs Tron!
The Surprising Duel in the Ultra Different Dimension!"
during the first part of the World Duel Carnivals.
They defeated enemy after enemy to get here.
Whom will shine the sun on their dash to immense glory?
These two have survived this far!
I give you the Dark Horse of the tournament, the Duelist with the mysterious mask, Tron!
Against the miraculous wonder boy, Yuma Tsukumo!
Yuma, do your best!
The Final of the century!
And the stage now will be changed.
Made by Heartland's top advanced technology:
The Sphere Field!
That Sphere Field is a far cry from any of the fields you've fought on up until now.
It is simulated space from the Parallel Worlds.
Tron, Yuma...
Use all the Numbers you have to your heart's content.
Regardless of the outcome, you both will...
Wha... What is that?!
So this is the Sphere Field.
Just what is this thing?
So that Faker managed to complete it.
Now, Sphere Field, take our two best Duelists...
...to the sky!
What's the deal with that field?
To summarize, that means this special field is built by a mysterious energy from a different dimension.
Good job making it this far!
Tron, you...!
While I was wandering the threshold between the Parallel World in a living Hell...
I gave up on life countless times.
In those moments, I recalled the memory of your father, Kazuma, who gave me constant support.
He used to say this quite often:
"Friends, companions, and a heart that will never give up."
But after being betrayed by Faker, I came to understand.
His talk about friends and comrades...
...all became completely meaningless to me!
But I have to admit that the part about, "a heart that will never give up" is quite important.
It was because I never gave up that I had the hope to get my revenge.
And I was able to be reborn in this form!
That's not right! And I promised III!
He asked me: "Please save my family!"
Tron, this is why I'll fight for III with everything I've got!
And I'll save you!
To save me? From what, exactly?
Isn't that obvious?!
I will drive out the demon of revenge inside you!
For your revenge, you sacrificed III, V, and IV!
But in the end, those kids haven't been very useful.
As punishment, they are now lying side by side as three hollow shells without souls.
Hollow shells?
Right. The crest I gave the three of them
granted them power, but as a price, it was directly linked to their souls.
Numbers require a huge amount of power.
If such a Duel is lost, the soul will be consumed.
The result is quite obvious, isn't it?
You... knew that this would happen...?!
Can a human with such an evil heart truly exist?
And you call yourself their parent!?
They already knew about your emptiness of revenge, but you...
Isn't that the bond between parent and child?
I mean, Faker is the one to blame for all this!
Why won't you get revenge against him?
Dr. Faker did take Kazuma away from you, you know.
My Dad... My dad would never want me to take revenge!
Really?
I wonder if Kazuma really thinks that.
No, couldn't it be that he already started his revenge?
Isn't that right, Astral?
What are you trying to say?
A terrible power is dwelling in the Numbers.
They could destroy this world with their enormous force, couldn't they?
If so, aren't you the messenger lending him power to take revenge on this world?
Kazuma did send Astral to this world, didn't he?
That can't... Astral is the messenger to take revenge on this world?
Aren't you collecting this terrible power as well, Faker!?
- What the?
- Who's that old guy?
- He's kinda scary!
- Is he about to do something?
That's Dr. Faker?
Long time no see, Byron.
Your rejuvenation took me by surprise.
It's all thanks to you.
I'll go pay you a visit in due time.
As soon as I take all of Yuma's Numbers, that is.
Stop joking around here! Dr. Faker! Tron!
I'll take care of you no-good adults once and for all!
Now that sounds interesting. I'm looking forward to it.
I'll show you! We're gonna win this, Astral!
Now, for everyone here,
allow me to explain the Dueling rules of the Sphere Field!
This field has been developed to maximize the power of the Numbers.
Each player can overlay two Monsters of the same level in his hand,
then, ignoring the Summoning conditions, a random Numbers Monster will be Special Summoned from the Extra Deck!
But a Number that has been Summoned in that way
will be destroyed once its Overlay Units are used up!
Now, use this as best as you can.
The Duelists chosen by the Numbers!
Heart Burning!
Right, let's go!
Duel!!
I will start! My turn! Draw!
I'll use the effect of the field right from the start!
I will take 2 Level Four Monsters from my hand.
I Overlay Heraldic Beasts Aberconway and Yale!
There's a Number coming already?!
Of course, it's a Number I can't choose myself.
I Special Summon Number 56,
Goldrat in Defense Position!
With this, I end my turn.
600 Defense Points? A Number this weak...
Yuma.
Huh?
Do you think the Numbers really have the power to destroy the world?
Astral.
Don't tell me you're still thinking about what Tron said.
I don't have any memories.
Have I really been sent to this world for revenge?
Astral...
I don't have a clue why you've been sent to this world.
But I've come to know more than anyone that you're not a bad guy.
But if the Numbers really have that crazy sort of power,
these guys should never get a hold of them!
Astral, I'll hand them to you because I know you'll do the right thing with them.
I believe in you.
Yuma, I understand.
Let's do our best to defeat this Tron.
Sure!
How about we surprise him with some secret strategy you've been saving up 'til now?
I don't have one.
Oh? Wait!
You shouldn't rely on me anymore today!
By the way, about strategy and your Dueling style...
We're back to our usual way now!
That's what I'm talking about!
Let's go! My turn! Draw!
Yes, it's there! I'll bring it to 'em!
From my hand, I Overlay the Level Four Gagaga Magician and Gogogo Golem!
This is the Number I Summon!
Come forth, Number 12!
Armor Ninja Crimson Shadow!
That's a good draw!
To summarize, with his Attack Power, he can defeat Goldrat!
Force yourself through!
Go, Yuma!
Crimson Shadow, attack Goldrat!
Crimson Slash of Moon Shadow!
Good!
I set one card and end my turn.
My turn! Draw!
Nice work, Yuma, Astral... That's the way!
Bring forth more of your power.
The more power you bring forth,
...the tighter you grasp your own necks!
I'll take two Level Four Monsters from my hand!
I Overlay Heraldic Beasts Twin Head Eagle and Aberconway!
Come forth, Number 10!
Shining White Knight Illuminator!
Tha... That's... Kaito's Number.
Oh? So Kaito used this, did he?
I guess he's useful for something after all!
Tron... You bastard!
Don't be swayed by his words!
I detach one Overlay Unit from Illuminator,
to send one card from my hand to the Graveyard.
And I draw one card from the deck.
And then I...
...activate the effect of Aberconway, who was sent to the Graveyard as an Overlay Unit.
By Banishing Aberconway from my Graveyard,
I can add the other Aberconway in my Graveyard back into my hand.
He's going for it again?!
I Overlay the Level Four Heraldic Beasts Aberconway and Leo!
Come forth, Number 30!
Acid Golem of Destruction!
He's got... two Numbers now?
And there's still another one.
Yuma-kun, this is my special service to you!
I Overlay two Heraldic Beast Unicorns!
Come forth, Number 8!
Heraldic King Genome Heriter!
So you showed yourself, Genome Heriter...
He's got three Numbers now?!
You're aware, aren't you, Yuma?
Genome Heriter has many Monster Effects.
Now, let's go! I'll activate Genome Heriter's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, for this turn,
the Attack Power of one battling Monster the opponent controls will become zero!
Now Crimson Shadow's Attack Power changes to zero!
Then Genome Heriter's Attack Power becomes the original Attack Power of my opponent's Monster it battles!
Though, the Attack Power didn't change at all.
Oh crap!
It's coming!
Genome Heriter, give the death blow to Crimson Shadow!
I'll just use Crimson Shadow's effect!
Wait, Yuma!
Use the Trap.
If you just answer the attack with a Monster Effect, we'll still receive damage.
If we take consecutive attacks like this, we will...
Understood.
Trap, activate! Half Guard!
Half Guard negates destruction during this battle,
and after the battle, Crimson Shadow will change into Defense Position.
Darn... he took a lot Life from me!
Tch... So it's in Defense Mode now, is it?
Well, never mind that. Go, Acid Golem!
Acid Splash!!
Crimson Shadow's effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, Crimson Shadow will not be destroyed by this battle!
I'm not finished yet! Go, Illuminator!
Attack Crimson Shadow!
Crimson Shadow's effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, he won't be destroyed by this battle!
Somehow I managed to block it.
Really now? Your Monster just lost all its Overlay Units.
Now Sphere Field's effect activates, and all Monsters Special Summoned by its effect will be destroyed!
Yuma!
That was dangerous...
To summarize, without the Trap, Yuma-kun would have lost!
I'll end my turn with this.
Tron...
Don't quail, Yuma.
Show your 'Bring it to 'Em' to him!
Sure! Let's go!
My turn! Draw!
Summon a Number!
Sure! From my hand, I Overlay Tasukerton and Flelf!
Come forth, Number 34!
Computer Beast Terrabyte!
Now! Activate the Magic!
Then I activate Xyz Treasure!
With Xyz-Treasure, for every Xyz Monster on the field, I can...
...draw one card!
There are four Numbers on the field!
This means...
... I can draw four cards!
Yes! It's there!
From my hand, I Overlay Needle Swordsman and Amarylease!
Come forth, Number 17!
Leviath Dragon!
Then I will Overlay Rai Rider and Zubaba Knight!
It's here, here, here, here!
Come forth, Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
We're counting on you, Hope!
Now both of them have three Numbers!
Yuma, good luck.
So, both sides have Summoned three strong Numbers!
Whom will the Goddess of Victory smile upon?
Heart Burning!
Yuma, the true fight is just starting.
Right, I know!
I'll show you why you should fear me!
Quite thoroughly!
Yeah, I couldn't ask for more! Let's do this!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
With our respective Numbers, Tron and I clash hard!
During this showdown, Tron's trump has finally showed up!
And at least, that guy's mask...
Does that Number have any weakness at all?!
Everyone believes you will return to normal one day!
Yuma, use the ZeXaL Weapon!
I won't ever give up!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Terrifying Duel! Arise, Hero of Bond ZEXAL!"
That's your true face?!
Finally the fight of Numbers has started!
Lots of fantastic Numbers will appear! It's so exciting!
More importantly, Yuma...
Is it true that tonight's dinner is a Number?!
Uh, I think you mean nanban zuke.
TL: Nanban zuke = vegetables pickled in Chayenne-Pepper