Now then, the 14 remaining Duelists who survived the Park Section
have broken through and are
headed to the location of the next battle!
The light from the blue sky
overhead the stadium is enveloping them.
They go from the light to the
pitch darkness of the Underground Section!
14 of the Coasters survived.
And Yuma's among them, cat!
Go! Bring it to 'em, Yuma!!
But Yuma's in 14th place.
He's last place!
That doesn't meowter!
This isn't a race, you know.
That's right. The winner will be
determined through a Duel in the end.
But they can't see anything in such a dark pit.
They have no idea when a a flip side will reveal itself.
No matter what traps await you, cat it to 'em, Yuma!
Well then, allow me to introduce to you the highlights of the Underground Section!
Their aim is to decidedly defeat their opponents to determine the strongest.
And the battlefields are...
Magma.
Space.
Jungle.
Canyon.
Each of the four fields hold special characteristics.
Now, lure your opponents into the field that gives you the advantage during your Duels!
Get fired up! Heart Burning!!
This will be true Hell, unlike before.
Who will survive...?
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Did you hear what Mr. Heartland said, Yuma?
Yeah. Our aim in the Underground Section.
"Number 53: The Fated Rail:
Try Your Luck on a Trap Card?!"
We've got to decide which opponent we take down.
Who are you planning to fight against, Yuma?
Anyone's fine.
I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
But there's only four fields.
That means only eight people can Duel there.
Huh? Can't two groups clash at the same time?
If there's four fields, that means...
Two groups of four will start off, making eight people in total.
Right! Eight people. It's eight. Huh?
Eh?! Only eight people?!
Wait... You just realized that?
W-Well...
That aside, how are we supposed to search for our opponents when it's this dark?
C'mon. There's a map on the monitor.
Ah, so you use this to figure out where the others are.
I've taken the lead in first place.
Tron is in second place.
That means Kaito will be third place if this pattern continues.
Tron is...
I won't let you get away!
This looks interesting!
I wonder what's waiting up ahead in this darkness!
My heart's throbbing with excitement!
Tron, I'm the one who's going to fight you.
I'm coming for you.
I'll raise my Life to the utmost maximum, and then I'll...
IV! I'll catch up with you in no time at all!
I swear to defeat you in this section.
That's it.
That's good. Follow me, Ryouga.
At this rate, I'll lure you right into the Magma Field.
Ryouga... Your deck uses the Water Attribute.
You have no chance of winning in the scorching hot Magma Field.
He's the one who kidnapped Haruto before.
He was looking at the guy during
the evening festival like he knew him well.
His appearance matches the
description Yuma gave me back then.
According to Droite,
the one manipulating those people who kidnapped Haruto from the background is that guy called Tron.
V... Tron... Those two are connected somehow.
I don't know why they kidnapped Haruto...
...but I'll make you pay for dishonoring my name!
You're in my way!
Huh? What the?
Don't you dare ride in front of me!
The battles have begun at last!
Number 13, Burning Toramaru,
has challenged Number 12, Gauche, to battle!
I'll kick the crap out of you!
Go, Wall Creator!
Shut up! I'm not in the mood
to play around with some small fry like you!
I activate the Magic Card, Heroic Call!
This card lets me Special Summon
a Heroic Challenger from my hand!
Come forth, Warhammer!
You're the one who's gonna be kicked about!
Go, Warhammer!
And it ended just like that in an instant kill!
I expected no less from the former W.D.C. Operation Committee Member, Gauche!
Not only does he have the looks going for him, he's got exceptional skills!
Gosh, show Yuma already!
They started a battle over there!
Shit! I gotta hurry and get a battle started!
Whoa, hit the breaks! There's a Trap Point up ahead!
Huh?
Look!
You're kidding...
Gosh, pay attention properly.
There you are! We got a nice mood going here!
V, I challenge you!
And it's Gauche yet again!
This time he's challenging V to a fight!
Show us a fiery battle this time!
Heart Burning!
Hmph. You plan to fight me?
Warhammer! Attack him directly!
I activate the Magic Card, Radiance of Hell, from my hand.
This card negates a Monster's attack
and sends it back to the hand.
Tch, what a mood killer.
We can't use our full power when you play such cheap little tricks!
I don't need to use my full power against you.
I activate the Magic Card, Flames of Retribution!
If inflicts 600 points of damage.
Whoa there! Now Gauche is Burning!
Th-This may be a bit too much for all you good kids at home.
Oh!
Another battle has started in a separate location!
It's the Asian Champion, IV!
Let's get this started now!
Killer Knight, Direct Attack!
On this side, Number 5, Ryouga, will begin his assault!
Sick them, Big Jaws!
Big Chew!!
He got me!
That's it, Ryouga. Keep following me.
I'll guide you straight into Hell.
IV's so strong! He's so cool!
Shark's the stronger one!
What gives? IV's the one who's been stronger and cooler all this time!
Shut up! Yuma's obviously the strongest and the coolest!
- As if.
Cat?
Don't! If you go that way, another-
Oof...
Y-You're not looking at all, are you?
Observation #19...
Yuma is truly an idiot... after all.
There's a Magic Point up ahead.
If my intuition is correct, it's likely...
I knew it!
The God of Healing, Dian Keto.
Its effect increases my Life.
7000, huh? It's still not enough.
I need more Life in order to fight him...
What?
Tron stopped again... This movement...
Orbital!
Yes, Kaito-sama.
Number two's Coaster, Tron's, is moving suspiciously.
Look into it immediately.
Understood!
Tron...
Another Trap Card.
The Trap Card, Poison of the Butterfly.
This is a Trap that will inflict 1000 points of damage unto me.
There's Traps laid about all over the place.
I wonder where they're trying to lead me.
Things are getting more interesting.
It's still not enough... More... I need more Life!
I can't believe you only have 200 points left.
You're in trouble if they decrease any further!
I-It's not like there's anything I can do about it.
Losing points during a Duel is one thing,
but losing them because you fell into a Trap yourself...
But it couldn't be helped!
Yuma, in front of you!
Eh?!
A-A Trap Point!
Hit the breaks!
Oh crap!
Again?
The Trap Card, The Paths of Destiny.
You conduct a coin toss
and if it's heads, your Life Points increase by 2000 points.
If it's tails, you take 2000 points of damage.
2000 points?!
Let's do it!
I'm definitely gonna get heads and increase my points by 2000!
Wait! If you get tails, your Life will be reduced to zero!
I'll recover the Life Points I lost myself!
I figured Yuma would say that.
Here goes! I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
It's futile, no matter what you do.
Shut up!
Stop wasting time babbling!
My spirit hasn't fallen yet!
Foolish.
But I've been waiting for this moment.
For the moment my Life fell down to 500!
I Summon Heroic Challenger - Double Lance from my hand!
This one Monster can be treated as two Xyz Materials!
I Overlay my Level Four Double Lance treated as two Xyz Materials!
I use this Monster twice to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Heroic Challenger - Excalibur!
Excalibur can't attack unless my Life Points are 500 or lower!
And that time is now!
I detach all its Overlay Units in order to double its Attack Power!
Go, Excalibur! Attack V directly!
Single Sword Strike: Sure-Kill Divine Sword!
How laughable.
I activate the Trap Card, Those Crawling Into Hell.
This card negates the attack of a Monster with 2000 or more Attack Points.
And the opposing player takes damage equal to half the Attack Power of that Monster.
Wh-What!?
To be cut down by the sword of his own comrade...
I truly pity the fool.
Hold it!
Yuma!?
Use Achachacha Sword Fighter, Yuma!
Right! I Summon Achachacha Sword Fighter from my hand!
Achachacha Sword Fighter springs into action during Effect Damage and negates it,
inflicting 400 points of damage to the opposing player in the process!
A-Absurd!
My Life...
Hey, V, are you about to Summon a Monster?
Tron!
We still need to let him go for now.
I understand.
Hey, Yuma! Why didn't you chase after him?
You should also hold a grudge against V!
More importantly than that for now, you need to focus on recovering your Life first!
Y-You...
C'mon and follow me!
Hey! Where are you going?
Yuma Tsukumo... Is his aim victory or friendship?
He resembles Kazama quite a bit.
Kazama Tsukumo...
He valued friendship greatly.
Perhaps that is what called forth his misfortune.
Here it is!
This is... a Trap Point?
You recovered Life Points with this?
Yup! If you get heads in a coin toss, you get your hands on 2000 Life Points.
You're one surprising guy.
You just gotta believe in your luck!
But if you fail, your Life Points will be cut down by 2000 instead.
You...
Put all your fighting spirit into that coin toss.
Later!
That bastard...
Oh crap! I fell behind again.
Yuma, a Trap Point!
Yuma!
2950 Attack Points...
2700...
4200!
Impressive.
Little old me up against three top-class Monsters.
This could be trouble.
Three people with one strike...?
Just how strong is Tron?
Kaito...
I can't let Kaito fight with Tron...
And so they press on!
Out of the 23 Finalists, only 14 survived the Park Section.
And so far in the Underground Section, six have dropped out.
That leaves us with eight!
Cat, Yuma!
Yuma finally came out.
I was worried he'd be knocked out, but to summarize, he did it!
But the remaining group is incredibly strong!
Yuma will be just fine!
Cat it to 'em with all you've got!
Now, starting now are the one-on-one Duels!
They are aiming for four of these Duel Fields!
Go into battle, my warriors!
Heart Burning!
Now follow after me, Ryouta!
Since it's come to this, I'll go do
another coin toss and increase my Life!
Don't! If you don't get heads next time, you'll only limit yourself!
It's about fighting spirit! Bring it to 'em!
What? A Trap Card?
That is correct, Kaito-sama.
Tron's strange movements
were due to him stopping a series of Trap Cards in his way.
All the set cards had "Butterfly" in their names.
Butterfly cards...?
Droite...
Tron is my prey! I won't let anyone else touch him!
Why are you after Tron?!
I've sworn my allegiance to Mr. Heartland.
No matter who it is, I will utterly crush anyone getting in his way!
Here it is! This time it's Droite!
She is a former W.D.C. Operation Committee Member. Her Dueling skills are topnotch!
Advance onward with the revived Gauche!
Droite has indeed sworn her allegiance to me.
But why would she get in Kaito's way...?
You're in my way!
I won't let you go! I'm the one who's going to fight against Tron!
Then I will show you no mercy!
And I'll return those words to you!
I pay 1000 of my Life Points to activate the Continuous Magic Card, Dance of the Butterfly!
It inflicts 300 points of damage to my opponent for each card with "Butterfly" in its name in my hand!
I reflexively changed my course...
Live... Kaito!
The Jungle Field is up ahead.
If I lure him out into the dense tropical forest, my deck will have the advantage,
and my chances of winning will increase!
So she's the one who's been trying to lure me into a trap, huh?
Fine. I'll take the bait.
If you want to fight me that badly...
Wow... It's like it's a real jungle.
So this is the area you wanted?
That's right. The Jungle Field...
The two of us alone will fight here.
Sounds like fun.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
It's the Duel Carnival Tournament Finals!
Droite and the mysterious masked boy
duke it out in the Jungle Field!
You're amazing, Droite!
This is a perfect Magic Combo she utilized along with her Field Magic!
The power of love... It's kind lovely.
That Number is...
Memories? What the heck's that Tron guy up to?
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Tron vs Droite - Allure of the Death Butterfly!
The Life-Threatening Jungle Field!"
Stop it!!
The Duel Coasters are so much fun!
We don't have the luxury to enjoy the Duel Coasters right now.
But I bet they wouldn't hold a candle to Big Sis Akari's motorcycle!
Motorcycle?!
Yuma, don't you think it's too much
for Akari to just take off like that?!
So now you're interested in the motorcycle?!