Haruto!
Haruto...
Where's Haruto?!
Where on earth did he go?!
Gauche-sama and Droite-sama are currently tracing Haruto's whereabouts...
Have you found Haruto? Gauche?! Droite?!
Tch, which of those guys opened there mouth?
Who told Kaito?
Why won't you answer?!
Answer me! Gauche! Droite!
Obviously because you're so damn annoying!
Relax. We have confirmed Haruto's safety.
Droite!
But he is not under our protection yet.
And Kaito, we will require your strength.
Right now Haruto is located at
the top of Windmill Tower in 5th Area…
...along with Yuma Tsukumo.
What're you talking about?
You trying to call that guy here?
The heck are you feeling?
Have you forgotten Haruto's power?
As he is now, we can't approach him.
Kaito is the only one Haruto accepts from the bottom of his heart.
He's the only person Haruto will listen to.
Windmill Tower...
Here.
It's called caramel.
It's got a magical power that makes you feel better.
Delicious...! It's really delicious!
Haruto... I'll stay with you forever.
Haruto!
Haruto!!
That place...
And he's with Yuma Tsukumo?
H-Hey, Haruto!
You...
It seems Haruto-sama wanted to see me again.
My mission is to destroy the Astral World.
Haruto!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Well, it's a good thing, isn't it?
That guy before seemed to know Haruto.
"Number 41: Haruto's Gone!
A New Enemy, Tron"
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sure he was sent by Kaito to pick him up.
Kaito...
Brother is... always tired because of me.
So...
This time, I wanted to give my brother caramel.
I wanted him to eat the caramel.
So he.... Kaito was really gathering Numbers for Haruto's sake.
Just what the heck is going on?
His reason for collecting the Numbers is...
My mission is to destroy the Astral World.
Just what was that...?
Wh-What the heck?!
It's the helicopter that took Haruto-kun!
Y-You're...!
You damn brat!
Where's Haruto?!
What the heck?!
Didn't Haruto go back home?!
Say what now?!
Someone came to pick him up!
You didn't hear about it?!
He was one of your people, wasn't he?
That helicopter before had the same mark as yours!
Did you hear anything about that, Droite?
Yuma...
No, we should be the only team out searching for Haruto.
Lying right to me face, huh? You're in a bold mood today, kid! Huh?!
Ow-ow, ow, ow, ow!
Stop it!
Hurry up and tell me where Haruto is! Otherwise...
I... ain't... lyin'!
I returned Haruto already!
I don't got the time to fool around with you!
You little bastard! The mood just got even better!
You!
Let go! Let go of me!
Listen well.
We are members of the Duel Carnival Operation Committee.
If you continue to act like that, we have the right to disqualify you.
Darn...
If you don't want that to happen, answer honestly!
Where is Haruto?
Ah! That's...!
Landing!
Where is he?
Where is Haruto?!
Droite!
Hey, Kaito! These guys think I'm the one who's hiding Haruto!
You were hiding Haruto?
No! I turned Haruto over to someone from Heartland who came to pick him up!
Someone came to pick him up from Heartland?
Huh? So then that means...
Then what the heck is going on here?!
Who... Who took Haruto?!
Don't play dumb, Foolma!
You were the one who kidnapped Haruto-sama, weren't you?!
Get lost.
U-Understood!
You said someone from Heartland picked him up. What did they look like?
Huh?
I mean their characteristics! Were they male or female?!
It was a man!
That's all?!
He was a very young man!
He was in his early 20's, very skinny, and...
His height was 185 cm (about 6’1).
His weight was about 70 Kg (about 155-160 lbs).
Right! His height was 185 cm!
His weight was 70 kg!
He had long hair, and his eyes were blue.
He had long hair! And his eyes were... huh?
What color were they again?
Why you little...! You messing with us?!
Stop it, Gauche!
Shut up! I don't take orders from you!
Gauche!
Droite! Are you saying you believe his stupid words?!
I'm not saying I believe him per say, but he doesn't seem to be lying either...
Let's go, Gauche!
It must be someone else who took Haruto.
Tch. If you insist.
Yuma!
Sorry, I gave Haruto away without checking with him first...
Haruto... He's sick.
Sick?
Wait a minute, Kaito!
It's my responsibility to let Haruto go!
I'm going to look for Haruto too!
It's none of your business.
Kaito, I promised Haruto.
I swore to let him see you!
Orbital.
Understood! If you happen to find him, please contact us, Foolma.
Kaito...
I can't believe we actually gave Haruto to a stranger when he's sick.
Kaito, why are you collecting Numbers?
Why are you acting like the underling of a devil?
To save my brother, I sold my soul to the devil.
So Kaito collecting Numbers...
...has something to do with Haruto's sickness?
and what did he mean by selling his soul to the devil?
Darn! What did he mean by "devil"?
For now we know that Droite and Gauche are trying to find Haruto as well.
Droite and Gauche were either ordered to find Haruto,
or they encountered some trouble, and let Haruto slip away.
They looked panicked, like they were desperately trying to cover their mistakes.
So that means...
Not only are those two part of the Duel Carnival operation committee,
but they are also subordinates of Mr. Heartland, the main founder of this tournament.
They're from Heartland?
I'm afraid the reason they were searching Haruto must have something to do with Mr. Heartland.
It's likely that Haruto escaped from the Heartland's security.
He escaped?
Then Kaito... is working under Heartland for Haruto...
collecting the Numbers?
In other words, the devil is...
...Mr. Heartland.
But... if the one who took Haruto is neither Droite or Gauche...
Exactly. The problem is someone else has an eye on Haruto besides them.
Who in the world are those people?
Alright, let's start the ritual!
Where...
Where are you, Haruto?
Answer me!
Haruto!
Found you!
Brother!
You really are awesome, Brother!
You always find me, no matter where I go!
That's right!
I will definitely find you this time!
So scream all you want!
Call me!
Now... it's finally here.
The time has finally come for me to make Haruto's power mine!
My revenge hereby starts from this moment!
Just wait, Dr. Faker!
Ooh... that is...
That's Astral World!
How beautiful!
I can feel it... I can feel... Haruto's power!
This...this is the power I am looking for!
Amazing...
So wonderful!
Brother!
The voice just now...Haruto!
What happened, Astral?
Haruto...
Haruto is...
What's wrong with Haruto?
Did something happen to Haruto-kun?
Save me!
Save me, brother!
Brother!
There's no mistaking it. It's Haruto!
Haruto is suffering!
Fantastic!
This power is magnificent!
Haruto, give me all of your power!
Brother...
Brother!
Haruto?
Where are you? Tell me!
Haruto, answer me!
Brother...
The moon reflected in the water outside the white castle!
The moon reflected in the water...
A white castle?
Did Haruto really say that?
Ah. That's what he said.
The moon reflected in the water outside the white castle.
The moon reflected in the water outside the white castle?
They indicate...
The moon reflected in the water...
If I recall, there's an old museum no one uses around here.
That's what he meant by white castle, don't you think?
I see!
Also, the moon reflected in the water must suggest the moonlight reflected off the lake!
Alright!
That's it!
Now that we know the address, let's roll!
Kaito! Kaito!
Kaito?
So Haruto is here.
Haruto-kun.
Kaito... Haruto's in there. There's no mistake!
How do you know that?
I know... because...!
What do know?! You aren't even his brother!
What do you know about Haruto?!
Brother!
Yuma, Haruto is in pain!
Hey Kaito, this isn't the time to be arguing.
They're here. They came a lot quicker than I thought.
Were you followed, V?
Impossible.
Well, we were going to defeat them sooner or later anyhow.
Not like it matters if it's a bit earlier.
Then let's get going!
Don't push yourself!
Huh? Are you saying I can't beat them?
Kaito is a formidable adversary. Don't fixate on defeating him so much.
It's fine as long as we buy some time for Tron's ritual.
Hmph! I don't know what'll would happen once the fight starts.
I can't guarantee their lives!
III.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, Brother V.
Looks like they are inviting us.
Interesting! In that case, let's rush right in!
You go back!
Kaito!?
I can't go back!
I'm the one who gave Haruto to someone else other than you.
So unless I return Haruto to you safely,
I ain't going back!
I finally get to meet you, Kaito! I've been waiting.
You're IV!
You know them?
Yes...
Are you here to avenge your friends?
Fine, I welcome the challenge anytime.
Don't let your anger make you lose focus!
If you are influenced by anger, your Dueling will suffer!
I know, I won't use Dueling to get my revenge!
Did you kidnap Haruto?
Where is Haruto?!
He;s still alive, so relax.
For the moment, that is...
What did you say?!
But I can't give him to you yet.
He's quite "occupied" at the moment, you see.
If you wish to save your little brother...
...do it after you defeat us.
It's... a Tag Duel!
Let's go! I'll bring it to 'em!
I won't forgive anyone who tried to hurt Haruto!
D-Gazer, set!
I'll hunt...
... your souls!
AR Vision. Link established.
Duel!!
Brother!!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
In order to recover Haruto, Kaito and I start a Tag Duel with IV and III.
Stop it, Kaito!
Why'd you do that to Yuma!?
Without cooperation from him, we can't win this Duel!
It's okay if you treat me as an enemy...
...but I already promised Haruto!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Yuma and Kaito: A Spirited Tag Duel"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Heartland City's symbol is Mr. Heartland,
so "Heartland's Mr. Heartland" is pretty tedious!
There are many repetitive matters in this world.
Like soup pot, salsa sauce, etc.
Hope King Hope!
(Literal for "Aspiring Emperor - Hope)
Don't say it like that.