It's the World Duel Carnival Preliminary Round!
Using Heartland City as the battlefield, the strongest Duelists from all around the world
compete against each other, betting their Heart Pieces.
You qualify for the Finals when you collect five Heart Pieces!
I don't care who it is, just bring it on!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Well... Guess I really made you worry.
Me and the Class Rep are doing okay now.
Well, if you call "okay" couping himself up in his house.
Good! Glad to hear!
Yuma's the only one who won in our group.
The tournament is filling up.
You can be sure that the remaining participants are quite the competition.
Don't let your guard down.
Right, I keep telling you to leave it to me!
Hey, I sort of feel like we're forgetting about someone.
Huh?
Me too.
I'm still remaining.
Cat-chan!
I've collected three.
Cat-chan, that's awesome!
I collected four!
And you barely made it through any of those matches.
D-Don't make it sound that way!
I just had a bit of a close call, is all!
Really? "Just a bit," huh?
You really think so?
Listen, you!
You saw my bravery, didn't you?!
H-Hey!
My Heart Piece!
Give 'em back!
Why's that dog taking your Heart Pieces?
What're you gonna do? You're going to be disqualified at this rate!
I-I don't know what to do~!
I-It's a buncha cats this time?
My kitties, go search for Yuma's Heart Pieces!
Kotori, aren't you going to ask some birds to search?
(Note: "Tori" = "Bird")
I... can't do anything like that.
Oh, is that so?
You can't, huh?
Clean. Clean.
Really?
You know where the dogs are?
Wh-What're those guys doing?
That's...!
Yuma's Heart Pieces!
Yuma, let me take care of this.
You've got nowhere left to run! Return Yuma's Heart Pieces!
Stop it at once, ya'll!
What's all the ruckus about?
A-A dog!
It spoke!
This here's some Heart Pieces! Don't tell me ya'll been stealin'!
Ya damn fools!
Th-The heck is going on here?
Why'd the dogs take the Heart Pieces?
These here Heart Pieces belong to ya'll?
I hope ya'll forgive my followers.
Well...
You thieving dogs!
Huh?!
You can apologize to the police all you want!
Say what?! I thought I heard you call us thieving dogs...
But isn't it true?! Dogs are always up to no good!
Like that little act, for starters!
They always turn and stare up at you with that fake expression!
You fall in love with that pug and want to call him "Hito-chan"!
You feel sorry for it and you lose all your sense!
Why are you making that weird face, anyway?!
Say what now?!
Then how about ya'll, then?
And you peaceful looking cats are always scheming something!
Pipe down!
Since it's come to this, let's settle it with a Duel!
With a Duel?!
That's just what I wanted!
Eh?!
And if I end up winning, you dogs will leave this city immediately!
I'll return those words right back to you, cats!
I-Is she really gonna Duel a dog?
My Heart Pieces...
I can feel it. This is a fated showdown between dogs and cats stretching over millions of years.
And why are you so carefree about this?!
Those're my Heart Pieces!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
AR Vision - Link established.
"Number 39: Fated Showdown!
Cat-chan VS Dog-chan"
Cat-chan, please don't forget about my Heart Pieces!
Cats always dash forward!
My turn, draw!
I Summon Stray Cat!
It's got 100 Attack Points?!
What a weak Monster!
No, she's most likely...
I need to find something fast that'll trick the dog into sinking its teeth in.
I'll place a Monster for it to attack as a decoy and I'll counter it.
I then set two cards face-down, ending my turn!
It's my turn! Draw!
The dog drew...
...a card?!
I Summon Triple-Dog!
And when Triple-Dog is on the field, I can Special another Triple-Dog from my hand.
Then I activate the Magic Card, Double Dog!
When I have two Triple-Dogs on my field, I can Special Summon another Triple-Dog from my deck!
He's got three Level Four Monsters?!
I don't believe it!
I Overlay my three Level Four Triple-Dogs!
I build the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, legendary dog from the older days!
Smoking Dog!
How can a dog Xyz Summon?!
Damn! How is it everyone has such good tactics to Xyz Summon so well?!
Perhaps its Dueling tactics are better than yours, Yuma.
Shut it!
That's it! Go ahead and bite onto it, and become my prey!
I activate the Magic Card, Wanderbull!
This card Special Summons two Wanderbull Tokens onto my field.
And then, I activate the Equipment Magic, Dog-cking!
Dog-cking raises the Attack Power of the equipped Monster by 500 points for each Dog Monster on the field.
I've got three Dog Monsters on my field, so that's 1500 points!
It's got 4100 Attack Points!
At this rate, Cat-chan... My Heart Pieces will...!
That's right! It's a WOOF-Turn Kill elimination!
Go, Smoking Dog!
Attack Stray Cat!
Trap Card, open! Cat's Deception!
When the opposing Monster tries to attack my Stray Cat,
the attack is negated and that Monster is sent back to your hand!
I anticipated your cat-like shallow thinking.
Huh?
I activate Smoking Dog's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can negate a Trap Card's activation and destroy it!
Smoking Dog had such an effect?
It really is a One Turn Kill!
Cat-chan!
I win, ya'll.
Are you sure about that?
Hmm?
I aligned myself just right to absorb Smoking Dog's attack.
I activated the Quick-Play Magic, Cat Food!
This card released Stray Cat and Special Summoned Stray Catgirl!
And when Stray Catgirl is in Attack Mode, she can't be destroyed in battle!
Quite a crafty way to do so.
But you only got 500 of your Life remaining. You're about as good as dog food!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
And at the end of the turn, the Dog Tokens are destroyed by their own effect.
Now you've done it! You saw through a human's trap, even though you're just a mangy dog!
Silence, ya stupid cat girl!
My turn! Draw!
Behold, you foolish dogs who can only obey humans!
The noble spirit and the power of freedom cats possess!
I Summon Cat Girl!
I Overlay my Level Four Stray Catgirl and Cat Girl!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come on out, Cat Girl Magician!
Then I activate the Equipment Magic, Catnip Turbine!
This card increases the Attack Power of one of my Cat Monsters by 1200 points!
Good going, Cat-chan! Now it's got more Attack Power and the opposing Monster!
But I can't attack with the Monster I powered up with this effect!
So you're really just a foolish cat in the end.
Don't be so sure.
I activate the effect of Cat Girl Magician!
By detaching one Overlay Unit and halving her Attack Power during this turn,
I am able to attack you directly!
What'd ya say?!
Go, Cat Girl Magician!
Cat's Eye Magic!!
All right!
I set two cards face-down and end my turn!
Now Cat Girl Magician's Attack Power will return to normal!
Well?! Did you learn how foolish dogs are yet?!
How dare you...! How dare a lowly cat rebel against us dogs?!
I ain't ever gonna forgive ya!
A little girl?!
Huh?!
Eh... Uh, huh? Um...
Wh-What the heck is going on?
A little girl just came out of that barrel!
Is that little girl actually the one Dueling?
So it wasn't really the dog?
In that case, it would mean a little girl's Dueling tactics are better than yours, Yuma.
Shut up!
What's your name?
Dog.
Eh?
What?
I told you, it's Dog! I'm called Dog-chan!
Dog-chan...? Why are you Dueling while riding on top of a dog?
I-I'm... I...
I'm too scared to talk with other people.
So I've always been alone.
Chukichi is my only friend, but I liked to Duel.... I loved Dueling...
I used to Duel against Chukichi all the time.
Chukichi tried desperately to remember how to Duel.
He finally was able to draw a card.
And he Dueled against me day after day.
But I really wanted to Duel against other people!
That's why I disguised myself as Chukichi and entered this tournament.
But I was too scared to talk to people I didn't know, after all.
So then what do you want to do?
Eh?
Do you want to continue the Duel?
Or do you want to surrender as you are now?
Hmph. I guess this is all you dog lovers can do.
H-Hey...
Be quiet!
Are you fine always hiding behind a dog's shadow?
You'll be a loser dog the rest of your life!
Hmph! You're wrong!
But I'm not wrong, am I? You're too scared to Duel on your own!
Duel Disk, set!
I challenge you!
That's just what I want!
What a thing to happen!
I can't believe it went from Dog VS Cat Girl to Dog Girl VS Cat Girl!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Wan Chance!
If I control no Level Three or lower Monsters on my field, I can Special Summon four Wanchance Tokens onto the field.
As my dog friends increase, the effect of the Equipment Magic, Dog-cking,
raises the Attack Power of my Smoking Dog 2000 points!
Battle! I use Smoking Dog to attack Cat Girl Magician!
Trap Card, open!
Gold Coins for Cats!
When my cats are attacked, I can add half the Attack Power of the opponent
to the Attack Power of my Monster!
She's got 5750 Attack Points! She's stronger than Smoking Dog!
Not yet. She's still got the effect of Smoking Dog.
I activate Smoking Dog's effect!
I detach one Overlay Unit to negate your Trap effect!
Oh crap! The cat's Attack Power returned to normal!
I've been waiting for that.
Even if Smoking Dog makes Trap effects invalid, it can't make Magic effects invalid!
The card I set on my field was the Quick-Play Magic, Counter Nyaunter!
When one of my Trap Cards is destroyed, I can destroy one of my opponent's Magic or Trap Cards.
Then, I can double the Attack Power of one of my Cat Monsters until the end of the turn!
No way!
The card I destroy is the Equipment Magic, Dog-cking!
If I destroy that card, Smoking Dog's Attack Power will return to 2600!
And the Attack Power of my Cat Girl Magician will rise up to 6400!
You have nothing left to... protect!
I've turned this match around!
It's no use. I can't win...
I guess I just can't do anything on my own.
Just give up! You're just a loser dog!
Bring it to 'er!
Don't you ever give up! Bring it to 'er, Dog-chan!
That's right, Dog-chan! Bring it to 'er!
Never give up and always challenge yourself!
Don't give up, Dog-chan!
Never, ever give up!
Mm, that's right! I can't let myself give up!
I am not a loser dog!
I'm gonna dog it to 'em!
Trap Card, open! Defiant Howl!
This card destroys one of my own Equipment Magics,
and returns the Attack Power of all Monsters on the field to their original value!
You destroyed your own Equipment Magic. Good of you to come to that realization.
Go, Smoking Dog!
I won...?
I won!
I won! I really won!
You did it, Dog-chan! That's the way!
My Heart Pieces!
I'm sorry. I'll give these back to you.
Th-Those are my...!
My Heart Pieces!
And these are my Heart Pieces.
Take them.
Eh...? But...
You won, didn't you?
Yeah...
You brought the dog pretty well out there.
I used to always only have cats as my friends.
Eh?
But once I worked up the courage to cat it to 'em...
I started Dueling.
And I made some friends.
I made friends with everyone through Dueling.
You became friends with everyone through Dueling?
Did you lose on purpose?
Take a look.
Observation #18...
"Cat it to 'em, Dog it to 'em...
There are many ways to bring it to 'em waiting in this world.
I wonder if there's a way to connect people around the world this way."
Yes! I'm gonna bring it to 'em with all I got tomorrow!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Kaito's little brother Haruto suddenly appeared in the city!
Just where are you going?
That kid's in danger!
Are you able to see me?!
Are you looking for your older brother?
If this continues, everything will be swallowed up!
I understand, Haruto. I promise to take you to Kaito's home!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Visitor from Heartland, Haruto"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!