Haruto's been kidnapped!
While we were searching for Haruto,
III and IV appeared before us!
Kaito, let's beat these guys down in a Tag Duel!
I will definitely bring Haruto back!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
It's beautiful...!
So this is Astral World!
The time has finally come, Kaito...
Duel!!
Now, let's get my fanservice started!
Don't even joke with me...
And don't think you'll get out of this in one piece after laying your hands on Haruto.
You sure are confident.
I'll give you the same loss I handed that one's friends!
I'm the one who's gonna beat you, IV!
Yuma, don't get worked up.
It's part of his strategy.
I know that. I won't Duel for revenge!
Kaito-sama...
Hey! Sucky Foolma over there! You better not get in Kaito-sama's way!
What's your problem?!
I said he sucks because he sucks!
Come again?!
Eeee...! Um...
I won't let you make fun of Yuma, you deadbeat!
D...deadbeat?
Hmph!
This girl might be even scarier than Kaito-sama...
Here goes! My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gimmick Puppet - Bomb Egg!
Bomb Egg's effect activates!
This Monster lets me send a card from hand once per turn to inflict 800 points of damage to my opponent.
Right off the bat?!
You aren't able to attack on the first turn of a Tag Duel, but Effect Damage is something else entirely.
I send Gimmick Puppet - Necro Doll to the Graveyard!
Consider this my greeting. Accept it, Kaito!
Kaito!
You stay out of this!
Why should I? I'm worried about you, you know!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Now it's your turn.
If you dillydally, there's no telling what will happen to Haruto.
You monster...
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Field Magic, Photon Pressure World!
What the heck? Now we're in space?
That means...
I can't breath!
Calm down, Yuma.
Then I Summon Photon Crusher!
And with the Field Magic, every player not controlling a Photon Monster
will take damage equal to the Photon Monster's level times 100.
What?!
H-Hold on a minute!
I don't have Photon Monsters!
That means I'll take damage, doesn't it?!
I don't need your strength.
Huh?
I will get Haruto back with my own hands.
Take 400 points of damage!
You're supposed to be on Yuma's side, you know!
So you don't care about your comrades, huh?
Heh, I like that.
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
Kaito, why you...!
I understand. If that's how you're gonna be, then I'll do the same!
Wait, Yuma! We need to cooperate with Kaito if we want to win this Duel!
It's not my fault!
It's his fault, isn't it?!
Did you forget?
It's not just us riding on this Duel. Haruto's life is also in danger.
Haruto...
Looks like you don't know a thing.
Huh?
Kaito, you're a pitiful soldier working for Haruto's sake.
You're collecting Numbers for Dr. Faker and Mr. Heartland so they'll cure Haruto's sickness, right?
I knew it...!
You're gathering Numbers to cure Haruto's sickness!
To save my brother, I sold my soul to the devil.
That's right! He struggled to gather Numbers for Haruto's sake!
All without giving a damn about the souls of strangers!
What a touching story!
I can feel the tears coming.
Be quiet.
Why, Kaito...? Why didn't you tell me that?
I don't need your pity!
Anyone holding a Number will be hunted by me one of these days.
You and every one of them will...
Kaito... You...
I like, I like! Chase 'em all down, Kaito!
Healing Haruto... But that means that if we collect the Numbers, Haruto will...
Yuma, just concentrate on the fight right now.
If we don't win this Duel right now, we won't be able to get Haruto back.
Astral...
I understand.
My turn. Draw!
Brother, I'm going with the usual combo.
I Summon OOPArts Golden Shuttle!
And then I activate the Magic Card, OOPArts Resonance!
This card lets me Special Summon an OOPArts Monster other than an
an OOPArts Monster on my field from my hand with a level one higher.
I call forth the OOPArts Monster, Moai!
Then I activate Golden Shuttle's effect.
I can increase the level of this card once per turn.
Now he's got two Level Five Monsters.
I Overlay the Level Five Golden Shuttle and Moai
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 33!
OOPArts Super Weapon - Machu Mach!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
I set 2 cards and end my turn!
L-Look at the size of that thing!
"Number 42: Yuma and Kaito:
A Spirited Tag Duel"
Looks like they have more than more Number.
Don't let your guard down, Yuma!
I know!
My turn, draw!
I summon Ganbara Knight!
Next! When I normal summon a LV 4 monster to my field,
I can special summon this!
Come, Kagetokage!
I'll gonna bring it to 'em!
I overlay my LV4 Ganbara Knight and Kagetokage!
I build the overlay network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz summon!
Oh? You were able to Xyz Summon, were you?
Come forth, Number 39: Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
What?!
A Number?!
That boy...
Impossible?! That brat... has a Number?
So he is a Numbers user.
Brother, maybe we were too negligent during the previous duels.
He already has observed our duel once.
Do we need to change the strategy?
Brother!
Now that's interesting!
It would be worthless to defeat someone without Numbers!
Yuma, set the card!
Both of them are Numbers users, and they are exceptionally strong!
This duel... we don't have luxury to hold back and not play the right card!
Right. I set 2 cards, and end my turn!
My turn, draw!
Now the show shall finally get started!
I activate the Magic card Level Cross!
With this card, I can send one card from my hand to the graveyard
to double the level of one LV4 or lower monster!
I send Gimmick Puppet Necro Doll to the graveyard, and double Bomb Egg's level!
Plus, since there are 2 Necro Dolls in my graveyard,
I can banish one of them, and special summon the other one!
There are 2 LV8 monsters!
So here it comes, that Numbers...
I overlay my LV8 Gimmick Puppet Bomb Egg and Necro Doll!
I build the overlay network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, Number 15: Gimmick Puppet - Giant Killer!
That thing!
A Rank 8 Number!
I can't believe it would appear so quickly!
That monster...
...did something so brutal to Tetsuo-kun and the class president.
I activate the Permanent Trap Numbers Wall!
As long as card exists,
The Numbers on my field cannot be destroyed by the effects of Magic, traps or monsters!
An exclusive trap for Numbers!
Cannot be destroyed by card effects means...
Yuma, that's bad!
Let me tell you now.
I activate Giant Killer's effect!
By detaching one overlay unit, it will destroy all Xyz monsters except this card!
That way... his Number also won't be destroyed?
You fool!
Since my Number is protected by Numbers Wall, it will not be destroyed.
I am afraid that trap just now is a combo after foreseeing Giant Killer's effect!
That is...
We just fell into the trap set by those 2!
I can't use Hope's effect?!
It's no use.
Moon barrier can only be activated in response to attacks.
HOPE!
And Giant Killer will inflict damage equal to the ATK of the destroyed monsters,
to the player who controlled the respective monster!
Yuma!
That's bad! Giant Killer's ATK is 1500,
and it hasn't attacked yet!
If we take that hit...
Darn!
Yuma, special summon Damage Mage!
I... I know!
I special summon Damage Mage in defense position!
This card can be special summoned when I take effect damage.
Then I recover life points equal to the amount of effect damage I took!
So you recovered your Life Points? How boring...
In that case, I activate the Magic card Attack Gimmick!
Due to this effect, until the end phase, Giant Killer gains 500 ATK.
Plus, when the targeted monster destroys a monster by battle,
it inflicts damage equal to the destroyed monster's ATK to my opponent!
Get ready, Kaito, you're first!
Giant Killer, attack Kaito's Photon Crusher!
Why? The same attack should cause both of them to die!
Giant Killer is a Number.
It cannot be destroyed by this battle.
Final Dance!
Alright, take that 2000 damage, Kaito!
Kaito!
Kaito-sama!
Can you still hunt my soul with the way you are right now, Kaito?
I just activated the Trap card Unrivaled Attack!
What did you say?
Unrivaled Attack: In battle with its effect it can prevent destruction!
As long as Photon Crusher is not destroyed, Kaito won't be damaged!
So your set card was to protect Kaito?
I end my turn!
Do you... really plan to protect me?
That's not what I meant!
What's that person's problem?! Yuma just helped him!
I am sorry, that's the kind of person Kaito-sama is.
I already said it once. I don't need your strength.
Anyone who possesses Numbers is my enemy!
That's right. Is that Astral's order?
No, that was up to my own discretion!
If you treat me as your enemy, then I will be your enemy!
But I already promised Haruto.
He really desires to meet you!
Therefore, I will definitely take you to where Haruto is!
How annoying, you bastard!
Rejecting my service left and right...
Why can't you allow me to duel happily?
I really want to see your painful expressions!
Wha... what's wrong with that person?
Oh wait, I got a good idea.
If you don't like the previous services, then allow me to introduce other "services" to you!
You will definitely like this!
This is...
Haruto...
Haruto!
That's the 'life' of your cute brother.
What are you guys doing to Haruto?!
Oh... I have no idea...
But I do know my big brother's character is even more shameless than mine.
But judging from his condition, if you can't stop it quick enough, it's gonna be bad...
Brother...
You bastard!
Your expression is really nice, Kaito!
See, you can do it if you try.
Seeing your prideful expression became twisted is such an irresistible joy!
Unforgivable!
Just summon it, summon your ace!
That moment will be your last, Kaito!
My turn, draw!
Hey, Kaito, calm yourself!
I summon Photon Slasher!
Then at this moment, Photon Pressure World's effect activates!
When a photon monster was summoned,
players who do not control a photon monster will receive damage equal to the level of the summoned monster x 100!
I will annihilate anyone who dares to stop me!
Kaito...
Now there are 2 monsters with 2000 or more ATK on Kaito's field.
I release Photon Crusher with 2000 ATK and Photon Slasher with 2100 ATK,
The galaxy that shines within the darkness now become the light of hope, and serve under my command!
The embodiment of light , descend now!
Come forth! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
So it finally appears...
So that's the legendary Galaxy-Eyes!
But everything is going according to our calculations.
Time to assault.
I got it, brother.
This is bad... Photon Pressure World's effect will activate once again!
Go, Galaxy-Eyes, attack Giant Killer!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
You fell for it, Kaito!
Permanent Trap activate! Stonehenge Shield!
This card negates the attack from a monster with 3000 or more original attack,
its ATK will become zero, and its effect will also be negated!
What did you say?
Now Galaxy Eyes's ATK become zero.
And its monster effect will also be negated.
A trap that foresees Galaxy Eyes's ability!
So all this was a trap?
OOPArts monster Masshu Maccu's effect activates!
With Masshu Maccu, when a monster on the field changes its ATK,
by detaching 1 overlay unit, it can inflict damage to my opponent equal to the changed amount!
Go, Masshu Maccu!
Infinity Cannon!
Your Galaxy Eyes changes its ATK from 3000 to 0,
It's over, Kaito.
Take 3000 damage!
Kaito!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
After seeing Haruto's painful expressions, Kaito's dueling finally start to crumble.
Thus we were pushed to the corner by IV and III's strategy,
Calm down, Kaito!
What's that light?
Now a new power will be entrusted to his deck!
Don't give up, Kaito!
If you don't protect Haruto, then who will?
Next time in Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal:
The Miraculous Overlay, Neo Galaxy Eyes Photon Dragon!
I'll gonna bring it to 'em!