Tron has sworn revenge on all his opponents.
Then, there is the dad of Kaito and Haruto, Dr. Faker.
His goal is to ally himself with the Varian World, to become the ruler of this world!
I won't forgive him for forcing Kaito to collect Numbers for that reason!
To teach these egoistical adults a lesson, I will definitely win this!
I will become Duel Champion!
I'll bring it to 'em!
The Semi-Finals of the World Duel Carnival!
The battlefield for our passionate Duelists...is here!
Show yourself, Duel Tower!
On these sky piercing Duel Fields,
our warriors will clash and fight to their hearts' content!
Ao Yuma's opponent is Shark.
This could be a slight advantage for Yuma,
because he has been fighting Shark several times already.
To summarize, he should know his abilities.
But the same goes for his opponent.
Besides, Yuma does tend to forget the skills of his opponents.
Meowhat? Whose side are you on, Tokunosuke?!
Sure, Yuma has fought against him many times...
But that Monster Shark received during his fight against IV...
In order to complete my revenge, I am willing to accept everything!
Come, Shark Drake!
Accept my wish, and evolve!
Show yourself, Chaos Number 32!
Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake Vice!
Yuma...
Be careful...
Now, finally, the first round of the Semi-Finals will start!
Practically unknown until this competition, in this tournament he has won many hard fights!
The wonder of the tournament finals! The miracle-boy who managed to pull through!
Yuma Tsukumo!
Thanks, thanks- oops!
On the other side, out of the depths of exile from the Dueling stage because of a scandal,
he has reemerged again as a hero:
The revenger!
Today we will settle this!
Somehow Shark is very odd...
Hey, Shark! Shark!
What's wrong with the guy?
Now, my two heroes, up to the stage for the final battle!
Only one will earn the invitation to move on past this field of the Semi-Finals!
Now, who will survive to the finals?
Will it be Yuma?! Or Ryoga?!
Let yourself be emblazoned by this fiery battle!
Heart Burning!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
"Number 62: The Vanishing Bond!
Yuma VS Shark: The Fated Duel!!"
Really... What's up with Shark?
I can't believe this... The darkness of the Number...
Huh?
During his fight against IV, Shark suddenly received that Chaos Number...
This could only happen because the dark powers of the Number took absolute control of him.
Shark...
What kind of fight will you show me?
I'm really looking forward to this, you know.
Though it's already obvious who the winner will be.
Snap out of it, Shark! Hey!
Shark!
Yuma.
If he really is possessed by the Number,
Then his battle instincts should be sharpened as well.
Don't let your guard down.
Sure.
Then, I'll have to get through to him with the Duel!
Let's go!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Duel Target: Lock-on!
AR Vision: Link established.
Duel!!
I will go first!
My turn, draw!
I set a Monster in Dace-Down Defense Mode!
Then I set a card and end my turn!
Right. Set in Dace-Down Defense Mode is Dododo Bot with 1900 Defense Points.
The other set card is the Trap Card, Attack Invulnerability.
With this, there is a high possibility that we'll survive the first attack.
Come on, Shark!
My turn. Draw.
I Summon Spear Shark!
1600 Attack Points! If that's all...
Stay wary! Shark's Dueling isn't that simple.
Spear Shark attacks the Face-Down Defense Monster.
What?!
Without any precautions...  he is attacking Dododo Bot?
Shark?!
I can't believe this...
He is attacking without any precautions...
What's up with Ryoga Kamishiro?!
Because of this careless attack, he will receive the damage!
I've never seen Shark act like that.
The guy's Dueling as bad as Yuma used to.
No... This may be part of his strategy.
To summarize, maybe Shark wants to show Yuma-kun up with this,
as their Dueling patterns are completely reversed.
Then you're saying he took the damage on purpose?
To do such a thing...
I set one card face-down and end my turn.
Shark...You've always had such harsh fighting spirit, but now this?
Just what is going on in his head?
Stay cautious anyway, and pay attention to that set card.
Ha, you betcha!
Let's go! My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gogogo Golem!
Then I change Dododo Bot to Attack Position!
Yuma!
Go, Gogogo Golem! Attack Spear Shark!
Shark!
Still not back to your senses?
Then with a Direct Attack.
Go, Dododo Bot!
Thunder Blade!!
This is intense!
He received 1800 damage with one blow!
Hurry and get up, Ryoga!
Get up, Shark!
Come at me like you always did!
Shark! Shark! Shark! Shark!
That Shark... This is really disappointing.
What are you waiting for, Shark?! Stand up already!
Haven't you always bitten back no matter how strong your opponent was?!
That's the Shark I know!
A shark that won't fight back is no shark!
But we aren't finished yet.
I set one card and end my turn!
Go on and take your turn!
Shark, get up! Will you get up, Shark?!
Right... I'm here to Duel.
But... Why am I fighting?
What am I fighting for?
I can't remember... Why... Just why?
Did you forget?
Tron...
Thank God you didn't forget me.
It seems like something of your self still remains.
But it's all right.
If you listen to what I will tell you, you will Duel without hesitation.
Well? Then, why are you fighting?
You see... It's for me.
For you?
Yes.
You will fight in my place, as my marionette.
So, the opponent you have to defeat is...
My... opponent I have to defeat... is...
Shark!
What's up, Shark!?
Oh my, what is happening here?
Suddenly Ryoga seems to be suffering from heavy pain!
Now, we can't have this...
You still can't remember the opponent you have to defeat?
Even though I explained it that nicely yesterday...
All right. Then I will explain it once again.
The one you have to defeat is...
Rio...
IV...
Tron?!
The one I have to defeat is Tron?!
Who is that guy?
This is Dr. Faker.
Faker? Faker...
That name... I do remember, I seemed to have heard it somewhere...
Rio!
Dr. Faker.
Of course you heard that name before.
I mean, you've been hunting the guy down all this time.
After Dr. Faker made your sister suffer so terribly,
you swore in your heart to take revenge.
Right... That's right...
Rio had to suffer because of Dr. Faker!
My true enemy is...
Right.
Dr. Faker... And wasn't there someone else?
That annoying guy, who always gets in your way?
Someone else...
Yuma Tsukumo!
Right! Didn't you always think of him as an eyesore?
He always was bothering and in your way, with everything you did.
And he now stands right before you.
He teamed up with Dr. Faker.
From those who made your sister suffer that terribly, one half is over there.
Shark!
I'll never forgive you, Yuma!
You... Because of you...!
Yuma.
This is...?!
It's the same crest as Tron's.
So Shark's not only being controlled by the Number, but by Tron as well?!
Well, you could say that.
To be precise, my faithful servant, the Number, has united with him.
Ryoga has now become my absolutely faithful, darling puppet.
Now tear Yuma Tsukumo apart!
Let's go! My turn! Draw!
I Summon Two-Head Shark!
Then, from my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Aqua Jet!
Until the end of the turn, the Attack Power of Two-Head Shark will be increased by 1000!
Attack Gogogo Golem!
Defend! Yuma!
Trap, activate! Attack Invulnerability!
With its effect, Gogogo Golem won't be destroyed!
Naive! I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Shark Spark, from my hand!
When this card is sent to the Graveyard,
it negates an opponent's Trap!
What?!
Resume the attack, Two-Head Shark!
Yuma!
That's not all!
Two-Head Shark can attack twice per turn!
Attack Dododo Bot!
Shark! You're so cool!
Shark! You're hot!
Until a moment ago, it looked like Ryoga had surrendered,
but now he managed a furious counterattack reverse!
Now everyone's got their Heart... Burning!
What a sudden change of personality!
What just happened up there?
Treacherous like a cat!
Does this guy want to be put down...? Meouw!
Wh... why?
I'm not finished yet!
Then I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Dead Sweep, from my hand!
When an opponent's Monster was destroyed by battle,
the Attack Power of one Water-Attribute Monster in my Graveyard is decreased by 1000 points and it is Special Summoned!
I bring back Spear Shark!
Sick him, Spear Shark!
This is the payback for my little sister!
Huh?
Direct attack Yuma!
Yuma!
Shark's incredible when he finally gets serious.
No... This is much more than serious.
Now Shark is being controlled by Tron.
I am positive that this is where his current strength is coming from.
Under Tron's control...? And now, he is...?!
I will never forgive you, Yuma!
This is the payback for my little sister!
Im- impossible! It can't be that Tron manipulated his memories?
That's right, like he did during your Duel with III,
this likely happened to Shark as well...
I set one card and end my turn!
The Attack Power of Two-Head Shark is decreased by 1000.
Awesome! So awesome!
He instantly defeated the two Monsters of the opponent, and on top of that made a direct attack!
I expected no less from the man I set my eyes on!
Now he is flawlessly Dr. Faker's assassin!
I have to save Shark from Tron somehow,
but what should I do?
It's not only Tron.
There is still the Number inside Shark's heart.
Additionally, it has already evolved into a Chaos Number, Shark Drake Vice!
If Shark manages to Summon the Number before we break the curse of Tron...
I know! I just have to win this Duel, right?
I'll win and wake Shark up!
Yuma! Yuma! Yuma! Yuma!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gogogo Ghost!
Go, Gogogo Ghost! Attack Spear Shark!
Trap, activate! Zeus' Breath!
This card can negate my opponent's Monster's attack,
and when there is a Water-Attribute Monster on my field,
it can inflict 800 damage to my opponent!
He had a Trap like that?!
Shark really is flawless!
Now Yuma-kun only has 1800 of his Life left!
But Shark only has 1700 left...
The real match has only get started!
I set one card.
Turn end!
It's over, Yuma!
You have nothing left to defeat me.
I'm going to pay you back for my sister's suffering and get my revenge!
It wasn't me! Open your eyes, Shark!
The one who hurt your sister is Tron!
You're trying to make up excuses now, pleading for your life?
Unforgivable! For this, I will send you right to Hell!
With my own hands and my Number!
Your Number?!
That's bad! There are already 2 Level Four Monsters on Shark's field.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Sharktopus!
I Overlay the three Level Four Monsters: Spear Shark, Twin-head Shark, and Sharktopus!
I use these three Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 32!
Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake!
He's finally...
Nice. Very nice, Ryouga.
Go on and bury that annoying Yuma Tsukumo alive!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Shark was restrained by Tron's curse. Just what should I do to bring him back to his senses?
I can no longer endure the agony of losing friends!
It's coming! The Chaos Number!
I will save you using whatever method possible!
This is bad! At this rate, Yuma will...
Shark or Astral... I can only choose one of them?
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Shark's Back!
The Bonds Bounded By Bringin' it to 'Em!"
I'm going to bring your real heart back!
Yuma, you're still playing with Shark?
Shark and me are now 1:1, so I'm at 50%! I won't lose this!
Even I'm not sure who will win this.
After all, this is a battle between a horse and a shark.
"Yuma VS Shark"
"Uma (Horse) VS Shark"
That's your problem?!