Haruto, I'm heading out.
The Finals are finally here.
Afterward, just the two of us will...
Kaito-sama! Kaito-sama! Kaito-sama!
I won't let it get in my way until I finish hunting all the Numbers!
In the first round of the Semi-Finals, the unexpected Dark Horse, Yuma Tsukumo, reigned victorious!
Yuma!
Cat!
Now, who will be the one to fight against that very same Yuma Tsukumo in the Final?
The second Semi-Final match shall decide which of these two will!
The Cinderella Boy without any history suddenly busted into the scene!
But his strength is the genuine article!
His name is Tron!
Fighting against him will be this young lad!
The Lone Hero yet to lose against anyone!
He is a true born genius!
His name is Kaito Tenjo!
Kaito, I'm counting on you.
You had better...
...defeat Tron, that man.
Kaito!
Kaito! You better not lose!
I want to fight you!
We still haven't settled our score yet, after all.
Me too.
Astral.
Astral?!
Kaito...
Wait for me in the Final, you two.
Huh? "Two"?
"You two"?!
And the actors have gathered!
These two warriors have been invited to the Sky Field!
Wait just a minute!
Yuma, where are you going?
I ain't gonna watch this in some stadium!
Upsie-daisy!
Whoa!
Yikes! You fool! You're crazy!
Heh, come watch if you really want to.
My overwhelmingly powerful Dueling, that is.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Now, who do you think will win?
Will it be Kaito or Tron?
The gong announcing the greatest battle of the century will now...
...ring throughout the entire stadium!
Heart Burning!
Kaito, you can do it!
"Number 63: A Horrifying Dark Strategy!
Tron's True Colors Revealed!?"
I really hope Kaito-sama doesn't -over strain his body.
Huh?
Oops!
What's so funny?
It isn't what's funny.
I'm simply trembling, overcome with shivers of excitement!
I can sense the gaze of that traitor.
Watch closely the greatest moment, Faker!
Tron... Rather, Byron.
I never would have imagined that you would live on, completely changed in that form.
Interesting. Anyone who dares to get in the way of my ambitions,
regardless of who they are, will be utterly destroyed!
Tron, I won't ever forget how you treated Haruto!
I will destroy you for Haruto!
Now, now, let's not get so angry.
I've got something waiting later down the line that's sure to surprise you, after all!
Enough with the nonsense.
Here goes! Duel Mode! Photon Change!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
I'm taking the first turn!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Photon Crusher!
I then equip the Equip Magic, Photon Spear, with Photon Crusher!
Photon Spear can only be equipped with Photon Monsters,
and the equipped Monster is treated as two releases.
He's got two Monsters with 2000 Attack Points!
Here it comes!
I release my Photon Crusher, counted as two releases!
Darkness within the shining galaxy...
Become the light of hope and live as my servant!
The Embodiment of Light will now descend!
Appear before us! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Kaito...?
Kaito-sama!
Hmm?
I... set one card face-down and end my turn!
So you've stolen that many
Numbers and the souls of people that it hurts?
You can hardly stand anymore, can you?
You're wounded all over, aren't you?
You bastard...
Even so, you aren't permitted to go to the nurse's office, now.
What's going on, here?!
Is Kaito gonna be okay?
Eh... Well... You see...
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Heraldic Beast Basilisk!
Then I use the Equip Magic from my hand, Blast Medallion,
and equip it with Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
What?!
He's using an Equip Magic on the opponent's Monster?!
Then Heraldic Beast Basilisk attacks Galaxy-Eyes!
No way! Basilisk's Attack Power is 1000.
It doesn't stand a chance against the 3000 Attack Power Galaxy-Eyes!
When Basilisk battles,
it holds an effect that will destroy
itself along with the opposing Monster.
And when the Monster equipped with Blast Medallion is destroyed,
its controller takes damage equal to half the Attack Power of the destroyed Monster.
Eh?!
Go, Baskilisk! Attack Galaxy-Eyes!
I activate Galaxy-Eyes' effect!
During a battle, Galaxy-Eyes can Banish itself along with the opposing Monster!
Using Galaxy-Eyes' effect,
both Monsters have been Banished, and Blast Medallion's effect was avoided.
I knew you could do it, Kaito!
Return to the field! Galaxy-Eyes!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Not to bad, considering what a horrible mess your body's in.
Everything's for your adorable little brother, right?
Well, I think it's a good thing. Having a goal and all.
I have one too, you know.
And you see...
It happens to be getting revenge against your father.
Holding a grudge against Dr. Faker,
due to me wandering the
threshold in between the Parallel Worlds...
...my body turned into the form you see before you.
Yes, I lost everything.
I've become completely empty!
And that's about the only thing important to me.
My hatred toward... your father.
Revenge alone is everything to me.
Revenge? For that reason, V...
No...
You were willing to sacrifice your son?!
Wow! You're actually criticizing me?
That's a bit odd!
You hunted souls for your brother's sake, didn't you?
Naturally, you started doing it for your brother.
But didn't you start getting a thrill out of hunting souls one day?
Kaito...
Me and you are alike.
We are willing to sacrifice everything for our goals.
Shut up!
If it means saving Haruto, I could care less what you say about me!
But...
I will hunt your rotten soul!
I'll crush you with my own two hands!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Photon Satellite!
When this card is Summoned, it gains a level equal to a Photon Monster’s level on the field!
That means the level of Photon Satellite becomes nine!
And when Photon Satellite is used as Xyz Material,
It can be treated as two!
I Overlay with my now two Level Two Monsters!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
This ironic fate will become the foundation!
Turn V's... No, Chris' feelings into an iron hammer!
Swing it down on his foolish father!
Come out! Number 9!
Wh-What the?
Whoa!
That Monster is...
Sky Canopy Star - Dyson Sphere!
Kaito... You...
V's feelings...
Dyson Sphere...
Here I come, Tron! I equip Galaxy-Eyes with the Equip Magic, Photon Wing!
I activate the effect of the equipped Photon Wing!
Once per turn, I select one Xyz Monster on the field!
I select Dyson Sphere!
By absorbing all of Dyson Sphere's Overlay Units into Galaxy-Eyes,
I can increase its Attack Power by 200 points times the rank of the selected Monster!
Th-Then...!
Dyson Sphere's rank is nine!
That means it gains 1800 points!
Then, because I used Photon Wing's effect,
I can attack you directly with Galaxy-Eyes!
A Direct Attack with 4800 Attack Points?!
That's amazing! He'll end it with one strike!
Now that it's been settled, Kaito-sama can get some rest!
Galaxy-Eyes, attack Tron directly!
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
A-Amazing...
Now it's...
What...? Why is your Life...?
Wh-Why?! He just took a Direct Attack worth 4800 damage!
That card...
It's the Trap Card, Change Medallion!
During an attack from the opposing Monster,
I can Special Summon a Level Four or lower Heraldic Beast Monster from my hand,
then negate Battle Damage equal to its level times 1000!
Meaning you can negate damage up to 4000 points!
Grr...! That is not fair!
How about it? Are you happy now?
Oh yeah... It's time to surprise you even more.
I have a little present here for you.
It hurts...
And it's all your fault, Brother!
And you even promised that you'd heal me.
Despite saying that, you're putting me through this suffering.
Haruto's face is...
Impossible!
What are you trying to do, Byron!?
Up until now, I listened to your boring nonsense quietly.
I intended to take you on fairly, but...
I will not tolerate this mockery!
Are you angry?
You bastard!
But you know, I really am Haruto!
Don't you dare deceive me using Haruto!
I'm not deceiving you.
I really am Haruto.
And Haruto is really me.
Remember? It happened back when I kidnapped Haruto.
That day, I absorbed all of Haruto's power and memories into my body,
What did you say?!
And then, you see, we joined together.
Both our hollow hearts joined as one.
Haruto!
Both Haruto's will and my own life force are connected.
So if I were to do something like this...
Haruto!
Someone go to Haruto's room!
Protect Haruto!
Hey, hurry!
It's no use! The system's been shut down!
The door won't open!
What did you say?! Is this his doing?!
It hurts! It hurts, Brother!
Have you... Have you really become connected with Haruto?!
Indeed I have. I am Haruto.
Haruto!
You can't!
I won't let you go to see Haruto!
Kaito!
I'm going to see Haruto!
I'll protect Haruto, so focus on the Duel for now!
Yuma...
Orbital 7!
Understood!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
What an energetic kid.
Now then, let us continue the Duel.
My turn! Draw!
I Overlay the Level Four Abercornway and Basilisk!
I build the Overlay Network using these two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 8!
Heraldic King Genome Heriter!
So that's Tron's Number...!
I activate Heraldic King Genome Heriter's effect!
I detach one Overlay Unit,
and I can activate one out of three effects!
The one I choose states that until the end of the turn,
the Attack Power of the Monsters battling this Monster will be zero,
and their original Attack Power becomes Heriter's Attack Power!
It steals its Attack Power?!
I, you see, will choose to attack Dyson Sphere!
Thus, Dyson Sphere's Attack Power becomes zero,
and the Attack Power of my Genome Heriter becomes 2800!
But it won't work against Dyson Sphere!
When Dyson Sphere is attacked while it has no Overlay Units,
it can revive the Overlay Units and negate all attacks against it!
How naive! I use all of its Overlay Units,
and I activate another of its effects!
Until the end of the turn, the effects of my opponent's Monsters are negated,
and those effects become Genome Heriter's effects!
What did you say?!
This time it's taking Dyson Sphere's effect?!
Now Dyson Sphere can be attacked.
Go, Genome Heriter!
Flash Impact!
I set one card and end my turn.
Now then, the real fun doesn't start for a little bit.
Our Duel, you see...
...will make the shocks from our
attacks into reality and assault our body.
So, all of the shocks I receive from these attacks...
You wouldn't...?!
Yup. It means you'll be fighting against me, Brother.
I have to... fight against Haruto?! Don't be absurd!
It's your turn next, Brother.
Let's have fun together, just the two of us!
Haruto, wait for me! I swear I'm gonna save you!
Tron...!
It's perfect. Now Faker, you will...
...lose two sons before your very eyes...
...and they'll be crushed.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
If Kaito attacks Tron, Haruto will end up taking the damage as a result.
Realizing this, Kaito has been pushed into a corner psychologically.
If this keeps up, Kaito and Haruto will be taken down by Tron!
Yuma! We have to sever that evil heart!
Hang on, Kaito!
I'm definitely gonna save Haruto!
It can't be...! A new Number?!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Roar, Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
The Brothers' Bond That Smashes The Darkness"
Everything is for the sake of summoning this guy!
This time we will be introducing the Chaos Number used by Shark, Shark Drake Vice.
It's a Monster that thoroughly devours its enemies.
What're you staring at?
You look like you would make a good meal.
You plan to eat me?!