A fierce battle broke out between Kaito and Tron in the second match of the Semi-Finals.
But during his attacks against Tron,
the damage was inflicted on Haruto, and Kaito was backed into a corner psychologically.
and Tron finally started his counterattack!
Go, Genome Heriter!
Flash Impact!
I-I don't believe it! Dyson Sphere was...
...destroyed by Genome Heriter!
And the tables have turned to Tron's favor!
Kaito was cornered in an instant!
Tron, you've really done it now.
Dyson Sphere was...
And Kaito's expression looks really odd compared to before!
Something must have happened...
You understand, don't you?
My pain is Tron's pain.
And that means Tron's pain is my pain as well...
Brother.
What?!
What is...?!
Haruto!
It's a special screening especially for you, Brother.
Haruto! Stop it, you bastard!
Tron!
What are you trying to do to Haruto?!
Haruto! Haruto!!
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
C'mon. It's your turn, Brother.
It's okay. Go on and attack me!
With your Galaxy-Eyes!
"Number 64: Roar, Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
The Brothers' Bond That Smashes The Darkness"
If you don't mind what happens to your beloved Haruto, that is.
If I attack him, Haruto will...
But if I lose...
My turn! Draw!
I just have to win!
Winning is the only way!
I'll defeat this guy and save Haruto!
But will Haruto be able to endure so much pain?!
I use Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon
and attack Heraldic King Genome Heriter!
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
That's cruel... You're cruel, Brother...
Genome Heriter may not be destroyed in a battle with a non-Number,
but I'm still damaged.
As I thought, you'll...
...use any method necessary to achieve your goal.
You're a horrible human being!
I'll end my turn with that!
Hey! Can't you fly any faster?
At this rate, Haruto will...!
Foolma! I know that already without you telling me!
I'm diving in!
Huh?
Hang on tight!
As I expected, we activated the flawless security system!
My turn. Draw!
Brother...
I bet you're disappointed that it's my turn and you can't attack, right?
But it's alright. I won't let you be disappointed.
What?!
I equip the Equip Magic, Cursed Medallion, to Genome Heriter!
Once per turn, both players receive...
... 300 points of damage for each Monster on the field!
There are two Monsters on the field,
so both of us brothers receive 600 points of damage!
Let's do it together, Brother.
Brother... Broth...
How can this be?!
Haruto...
Haruto!!
I can't stand this! I just can't stand it!
Let's go!
Hey, Haruto! Get a hold of yourself!
Haruto! Haruto!
Haruto...
Kaito! He's okay! Haruto's still alive!
Can you hear me?
Is that so? Haruto...
Got you! You fell for it!
Surprised, are we? I bet you thought he was done for, didn't you?
You bastard...
Don't be like that. It was nothing more than a small joke.
But the real drama starts now!
Right, "Father"?
Enough of this! Haruto's done nothing to you!
Haruto just wanted to be together with Kaito!
Same with Kaito.
He just wanted to save you, and he's only thinking about you.
And despite that, why does Haruto...?
What's happening?
This is...
That's right.
Just like that time...
Yuma. I always believed that you guys would come here eventually.
I cannot get out of here.
Please, save my brother.
That's right. This is inside Haruto's consciousness.
The place where Haruto summoned you before.
Haruto...
What the...?!
That's...
How...? How did you...?
So he really has been hiding inside Haruto!
You're always getting in my way! You're such an annoying kid!
Yuma!!
Yuma.
I know!
Come forth, Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Nice work!
What?!
Stop joking!
How can I allow someone like you to do what you want inside Haruto's heart?!
Go, Hope!
Slash the evil power rooting inside Haruto's heart!
Hope Sword Slash!
Did we finish him off?
Yuma... Yuma!
Foolma!
Darn!
Damn you, Yuma!
How far do you plan to get in the way?!
Yuma!
What's going on here?
Hmph! I took care of Tron's consciousness inside Haruto's heart!
There's no connection between Haruto and Tron anymore!
You can relax for now, Kaito.
And kick that guy's butt!
You...
You are absolutely unforgivable...
Tron!
I hope you're ready for your repentance!
Kaito-sama, do your best!
Kaito!
Yuma, Kaito...
You guys never allow things to go my way, do you...?
Stop spouting bullshit! I'd never allow you to!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Galaxy Expedition!
When there is a Galaxy-Eyes on my field,
I can Special Summon one Galaxy Knight from my deck!
Then, when I control a Galaxy Knight on my field,
I can Special Summon another Galaxy-Knight from my hand!
Go, Kaito!
I overlay the Level Eight Galaxy-Eyes and two Galaxy Knights!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Great Galaxy of Reversal!
Become the rolling waves of light and show your mighty form!
Descend, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
So this is the evolved version of Galaxy-Eyes!
When I summon Neo Galaxy-Eyes successfully using Galaxy-Eyes as the Overlay Unit,
all other Monster Effects are negated!
Photon Howling!
Genome Heriter's effect is...?
Now your Monster is nothing more than a marionette!
Meaning his Number can now be destroyed!
And if this attack connects, Kaito will win!
Tron! My anger cannot be silenced, even if you beg for forgiveness a million times!
I don't care if it's Hell or the Parallel Worlds!
Just get away from Haruto and me!
Attack Genome Heriter!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
He did it!
You did it, Kaito-sama!
Good job. I expect no less from...
What?
Huh?!
He can't be...!
You thought you defeated me, right?
I targeted Neo Galaxy-Eyes
and activated the Permanent Trap, Protection Medallion!
What did you say?
That's right. Due to Protection Medallion,
Neo Galaxy-Eyes lost 800 Attack Points.
N-No way...!
Is that why Tron's Life wasn't totally wiped out?
Alright, Kaito, what are you going to do?
I...end my turn.
Thank you, Kaito.
What?
This is all thanks to you.
Because of your rage, the Medallion God...
...has awakened!
What's that?!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Heraldic Beast Berner's Falcon!
Then I activate the Magic Card, Reborn Medallion!
This card can Special Summon one Level Four or lower Heraldic Monster from my Graveyard!
I Special Summon Heraldic Beast Basilisk!
Then, when I control two or more Heraldic Beasts on my field,
I can Special Summon Heraldic Beast Yale from my hand!
I Overlay the Level Four Berner's Falcon, Basilisk, and Yale!
I build the Overlay Network using these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Rage, release yourself!
Come forth, Number 69!
God Medallion - Coat of Arms!
What's with this Number?
To control this guy, enormous energy is required.
And that energy is...
...rage.
Rage?
That's right. I have no emotions,
so I can't produce pure rage.
That's why I attempted to make everyone angry.
Droite and Shark... I was even willing to utilize my sons...
...in order to create rage.
Say what?!
You did pretty well too!
You get angrier and angrier when it comes to Haruto!
It's all thanks to you! Have a look!
I finally managed to call forth the Coat of Arms!
Don't tell me all of this was so you could summon that Number!
So if I were to do something like this...
Haruto!
Descend, my very soul!
Tron!
Plus, Coat of Arms can...
...activate effects without using Overlay Units.
It negates  the effects of all other Monsters on the field,
and it gains all of those effects!
What?!
Go, Coat of Arms!
Snatch Neo Galaxy-Eyes' effects away!
God Medallion Hand!
That way, your Monster will lose all of its effects.
And they will become mine.
Neo Galaxy-Eyes...
Kaito!
Kaito-sama!
Here I come, Kaito!
I activate the Monster Effect stolen from Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
I send all Overlay Units but the ones attached to Coat of Arms to the Graveyard.
And now the Attack Power of Coat of Arms...
...goes up 500 points for every Overlay Unit sent away.
Thus, it gains 1500 Attack Points!
Then, Coat of Arms can...
...attack Monsters up to the same number of Overlay Units sent!
Which means three consecutive attacks!
Neo Galaxy Eyes' effects were...!
Also, due to Permanent Trap, Protection Medallion's, effect,
Neo Galaxy-Eyes cannot be destroyed!
Let me taste you to my heart's content!
And have a good look for yourself, Faker!
The painful struggles of your son!
Impossible!
I attack Neo Galaxy-Eyes with Coat of Arms!
God Rage!
And again!
Kaito!
Haruto...
Not yet! You're not allowed to fall just yet!
This wasn't the extent of your rage, now was it?!
God Rage!
Kaito!
No!
What the?
Im... Impossible! You're...
Haruto.
Brother, thank you.
Haruto...
So he used his remaining power for the sake of his brother, huh?
That's terrible. Your revenge tastes awful.
Kaito... Kaito!
Hey, get a hold of yourself, Kaito! Kaito!
Kaito!!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
With the feelings that everyone has entrusted me,
my battle with Tron has finally started!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The All-Out Battle of Numbers! Yuma vs Tron!
The Shocking Duel Within Ultra Different Dimension!"
I will fight you with all I've got!