The battle between Tron and I in the Sphere Field is getting intense.
Not even the power Astral and I formed, ZEXAL, could bring him down.
But I can't afford to lose this Duel!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Yuma...
I have to admit I'm impressed,
though this is as far as you'll go!
I never thought you'd get past that unscathed...
But, that was your ultimate move, wasn't?
With your special move out of the picture now, that means...
...you no longer have any chance of winning!
I will never give up!
Not before I deliver the feelings that everyone entrusted me with!
And to make things clear, I will not give up!!
I don't need such things!
It's my turn! Draw!!
It's the end of the road for you two!
Coat of Arm's effect activates!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
I can use the effect taken from Hope Ray!
For this turn, Coat of Arm's Attack Power is raised 500 points,
while Hope Ray's Attack Power drops by 1000 points.
I'll bury you alive with Hope Ray's effect!
Coat of Arms attacks Hope Ray!!
God Rage!!
Trap, activate! Half Unbreak!
The Monster targeted in battle won't be destroyed during this turn,
and the damage during this battle is halved!
Yuma!
Now he only has 50 Life left!
Persistent pest.
I'm not done. I still have Life left!
When I watch that unyielding will of yours, I'm reminded of Kazuma.
Just like Kazuma, irritating!
I won't allow you to insult my father!
Calm down, Yuma.
Thanks to the previous attack, I figured out a winning formula.
Really?
Astral!
Don't tell me you realized that Coat of Arms was running out of Overlay Units,
and that you would win with that?
I activate Heraldic Beast - Twinhead Eagle’s effect from my Graveyard!
By Banishing this card from my Graveyard,
Coat of Arms restores two Overlay Units.
His Overlay Units...
It's about time you give it up.
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
3800 versus 50...
The match is basically over now.
To summarize, Yuma-kun might have met his match.
Yuma...
Yuma.
This is bad, very bad.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
What's wrong, Yuma?
Are you alright?
Yuma!
My tummy...
Man, I'm starvin'.
Why are you saying this now?
"Number 67: Believe in Victory!
The Final Shining Draw!"
I really am hungry!
Oh right!
Isn't that...
Eat it and be sure to win!
Here it is!
It's the Duel Lunch Kotori gave me!
NOM!
Wh-What's he doing?!
Does this mean Yuma-kun gave up the Duel?
No way.
You're wrong.
Yuma ain't done yet!
That's right!
Go, Yuma!!
Now this is something.
Eating while Dueling.
NOM!
What's this feeling?
Oh yeah! This is your first time eating it.
So this is "eating"?
Yep. You can't fight on an empty stomach.
Unbelievable! I can feel my fighting spirit burning inside me.
Haha, ain't that right?
So this is how it is to feel alive.
Even if it goes away, this sensation is unbelievable!
It's interesting!
It has become very interesting staying with you, Yuma!
Let's win this, Astral!
Yeah, but I want some more Duel Lunches!
I want two bowls, no, three!
I want to feel alive again!!
Now we're talkin', Astral!
Our winning formula is set, Yuma.
Just believe in me!
Yeah!
It's my turn!
Light and strength, gather on me!
Illuminate the path towards hope once again!
Final Shining Draw!!
I have been waiting for this!
I equip this card to Hope Ray!
Come forth, ZEXAL Weapon!
Tornado Bringer!
What? A twin-sword ZEXAL weapon?
Due to equiping Tornado Bringer, Hope Ray's Attack Power...
...is raised by 1300 points!
5000 Attack Points?
To add, the Monster equipped with Tornado Bringer, now an Equip Card, cannot be destroyed!
Plus, when Lightning Blade is used as an equip card,
Magic and Trap cards on my field cannot be destroyed when targeted!
In other words, you can't destroy either of them!
What was that?
You're saying that your equip combo with the ZEXAL Weapons...
...prevents Coat of Arms' card-destroying effect from activating?
That's right.
Hope Ray's twin-sword combo is invincible!
Go, Hope Ray!
Attack Coat of Arms!!
Hope King Double Chaos Slash!!
It's finished!
You sure?
Trap, activate! Blast Medallion!
This card returns your ZEXAL Weapons to your hand during a Battle.
This also ends the Battle Phase.
N-no way!
My ZEXAL Weapons...
And to add, Blast Medallion's effect, for every card sent back to your hand,
inflicts 500 points of damage at the end of the turn!
What was that?
Your Battle Phase is over.
All that's left is ending your turn.
Which means you lose, Yuma and Astral!!
Even so, we won't give up!
I'm not giving up!!
Nice one, Yuma.
But how are you gonna get out of this?
About that...
Same as always, huh?
But you got the "not giving up" part down.
It's getting ugly, Astral.
Your Battle Phase is over.
Like I said,
our winning formula is set!
What?
Let's go, Yuma!
Got it, Astral!
I activate the Magic Card, ZEXAL Catapult!
This card Special Summons a ZEXAL Weapon from my hand!
Come forth, Lightning Blade!
It's no use.
You forgot this! Coat of Arms' effect activates!
It negates and absorbs all Monster effects on the field!
And now I activate Amarelease's effect from the Graveyard!
The Graveyard?
By removing Amarelease from the Graveyard,
I can decrease the number of Monsters needed to Advance Summon by one!
Come forth, Tornado Bringer!
Didn't I tell you it's useless?
Coat of Arms' effect activates!
Absorb Tornado Bringer's effect!
Now both your ZEXAL Weapon's effect have been absorbed!
No way. He's out of options.
Now it's all over...
Yuma...
What a useless struggle, Yuma and Astral.
Really now?
Tornado Bringer and Lightning Blade's Levels are five!
Everything is set!
Don't tell me those ZEXAL Weapons...
It's exactly what you're thinking, Tron!
I Overlay my Level five Lighting Blade and Tornado Bringer!
I build the Overlay Network with my two ZEXAL Weapons.
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, ZEXAL Weapon!
Lion Arms!!
A ZEXAL Weapon that's an Xyz Monster?
This card can be used as an Equip card with Hope Ray, and with it equipped...
raises its Attack points by 300!
And this effect cannot be negated!
The raging impact from the warrior's golden armor will shake the ground!
Blitz of Lightning!
Grant the warrior the strength of a God slayer!
The Beast-Armor fusion! Lion King Hope Ray!!
And with 5500 Attack points...
Have you forgotten?
Your Battle Phase turn is over!
No! Lion Arms' effect activates!
Lion Arms can attack again when the Battle Phase is over!
No way! Two Battle Phases in one turn?!
This is the ultimate ZEXAL Weapon!!
But your ZEXAL Weapon's effects are now mine, so your invincibility is gone!
Coat of Arm's effect activates!
Bare witness to Coat of Arms' true form!!
It destroys one card on my opponent's field!
Smash Hope Ray to pieces!!
God Shatter!!
Lion Arm's effect activates!!
Once per turn, this card negates a Monster's effect...
and halves its Attack points!
No way...
Now go, Lion King Hope Ray!!
Hope Sword - Triple Chaos Slash!!
He won!! Yuma won!!
He won!!
He did it!!
He won!! ZEXALornot won!!
He got him, yeah ZEXALornot!!
Yuma Tsukumo...
He won...
I give to you the first ever World Duel Carnival winner, Yuma Tsukumo!
So Byron lost...
But none of that matters in the end.
I'll just recover the Numbers here and now.
W-what the...
Is this...
What's going on here?
What the...
The Numbers are...!
I won't let you, Faker!!
Tron!
Yuma! Yuma!!
Yuma!
It's no use, Byron!
Your power is useless without the Numbers.
Disappear, Byron!!
Tron!
Yuma...
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Kazuma...
Shit, what the hell is going on?!
Yuma, Astral.
The Sphere Field is a field meant to recover all the Numbers.
What?
What do you mean?
The Duel Carnival brought all the Numbers together.
No way would Dr. Faker waste this opportunity.
So from the start, this field was a trap?
Correct. He let us battle here so we would expand the Number's power.
Shit...
Let go!
We're foreign objects in this field.
At this rate, you two will also...
No way...!
I... I won't give up!!
But why?
Why are you trying to save me?
It's obvious, isn't it?! Everyone I Duel are my friends!
Yuma...
I don't understand all this complicated stuff.
But we create bonds with friends through Dueling!
And since you Dueled me, you are my friend!
I finally understand.
Now I see why you don't give up.
Your Dueling goes beyond my desire for revenge.
Yuma, I can't live the same way as you and Kazuma.
Tron!
But I can't allow Faker to do what he wants.
I'll release all the souls I've captured!
Farewell, Yuma, Astral.
Tron!!
Father!
Dad!
Forgive me, everyone.
This time, I will never forget those times...
Tron!!
We've...
Brother!
Astral!
Yuma!
Yuma...
I've been longing for this moment! Yuma Tsukumo! Astral!
Dr. Faker.
Now then, it's time for the finishing touches.
The finishing touches for the destruction of the Astral World!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Due to Faker's power, we're stuck in the Sphere Field.
Meanwhile, Shark and Kaito have arrived at the collapsing stadium.
The Duelists guided by the light of destiny will now gather here!
This is the place from before!
He's going to destroy the Astral World?
We have to protect the future!
You guys are our only remaining hope.
Next time, on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Overture Towards Destruction!
The Threat of Sphere Field Cannon!"
Lend me your power!!
The ZEXAL Weapon today sure was awesome!
But now that we've got a ZEXAL Weapon,
I wonder if a ZEXAL Bell Clapper will ever show up?
I sure hope a ZEXAL Side Clapper appears.
You can do something like that? I'm excited!
You're hopeless...