Shoot, shoot, shoot!
If I don't earn some Life before I reach the field...!
Geez, will you please stay calm!
That's right!
I don't see any Magic or Trap Cards here that can recover your Life.
Then all I can do is fight against someone!
Hey! Is anyone there?!
Like I said, just stay calm!
Even if you tell me that...!
Tron, ever since I saw you for the first time at the evening festival,
I haven't been able to shake off the fear that's been eating away at me.
I'm positive this man can step on those things precious to us and crush them without hesitation.
But I'll stop him.
Tron, I won't let you reach Kaito.
Wow, you must really think highly of Kaito...
I do.
I love him.
That's quite beautiful.
Oh my… The ones who chose Jungle Field were…
...the former Operation Committee member Droite and the mysterious boy Tron!
A Field Magic has been implanted in all four fields of the Finals,
which have given them distinctive characteristics!
So, what will this Jungle Field offer-
Wh-What happened here?!
- What the heck happened?!
- In the middle of such an important moment, too!
I can't see anything!
What an unthinkable mistake!
I am most sorry!
Please fix this as soon as possible, staff!
There's no way I can allow
our guests to see this match, after all...
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Duel!!
8000 Life Points!
"Number 54: Tron vs Droite - Allure of the Death Butterfly!
The Life-Threatening Jungle Field!"
You're a crafty one!
No matter what trick you use, I will defeat you.
Here in this Jungle Field.
If a player does not Summon, Special Summon, or set from their hand while
this Field Magic is activated, they take 1000 points of damage.
I see. You came here knowing that.
So you're the one who set Traps on my Coaster route in order to lure me into this jungle!
You really went to some great lengths.
The first turn belongs to me! My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card,
Phantasmal Dance of the Confusing Butterflies!
When I play this card when there is a Field Magic in play,
I can Special Summon the Level 4 or lower Phantom Butterfly Assassins, Morpho and Swallowtail!
Show yourselves, Phantom Butterfly Assassins Morpho, Swallowtail!
I Overlay the Level Four Morpho and Swallowtail!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Photon Butterfly Assassin!
An Xyz right off the bat?!
Furthermore, I'll entertain you further with these three Continuous Magic Cards!
Up first is Butterfly Charm.
Due to the Field Spell, this Jungle Field will deal great damage to the player who has not Summoned or set a Monster.
Right, I was listening before.
However, with Butterfly Charm,
if you Summon a Monster in Attack Mode that does not declare attack, it will be forcefully destroyed.
Then all I have to do is attack!
I won't let you do that.
The second, Assassin Gate.
When a Monster whose name does not contain “Assassin” attacks, it will be forcefully destroyed by this card.
Then my Monsters will...
Right. The only fate awaiting your Monsters is destruction, regardless of what you try to do.
N-No way!
I'm not done!
Huh?
The third, Death Butterfly's Invitation.
In order to maintain this card once activated, I need to pay 2000 of my Life.
But, when a Monster on the field is destroyed, it will inflict 1500 damage to the controlling player!
In other words, I will receive damage if I don’t Summon a Monster,
and even if I manage to Summon one, it will be destroyed, and I will receive critical damage in the process.
You use up 2000 of your Life in exchange for 1500 damage...
I see! So that's why you raised your Life all the way up to 8000!
With this combo’s operation, you will be engulfed by this jungle within three turns!
Kaito...
Ever since that day, I have always...
My fellow young Duelists,
It's painful... unbearable, isn't it?
But thanks to that pain, the next generation of elite Duelists shall be born!
Trap, activate!
Draw!
Th-That's...?!
Alright, the Ghost Lord is on a rampage!
If you wish to be rescued, you will need to win the Duel!
Droite!
No!
Kaito...
Draw!
I Summon Daybreaker!
Go! Direct Attack!
Don’t rely on others!
The moment you begin relying on others is the moment you lose sight of yourself.
That's... Kaito...
If I recall... that's Kaito's little brother...
Haruto, take a look. It's a butterfly.
That might of yours that refuses to rely on anyone...
It exists solely to protect your little brother.
When I see your smile, I can't help but think that.
But even that smile... looks kind of sad.
I've made up my mind.
Just as Kaito protects Haruto, I will protect Kaito.
I won't rely on anyone else. I will fight on my own.
All so I can see Kaito's smile.
Then that means I must be a sacrifice for your love.
Ah man! It seems I'll be playing the buffoon!
Where are we?
The jungle...
That's...!
That's...
Droite!
Tron!
Droite...
Yuma! Hey, look over here!
I got caught by a terrifying trap.
Trap?
The three Magic Cards on Droite's field?
Those are...
I see now.
It's a combo using those three Continuous Magic Cards and the Field Magic.
A strong one that forces the opponent to Summon a Monster, destroy it, then inflict damage to the player.
It's that powerful?
But there is a way to get around it.
That's right.
But I will triumph over love!
My turn! Draw!
Due to the Jungle Field, I have to Summon a Monster.
If I Summon it in Attack Position, your combo will activate.
Thus, the correct response is…
The correct response is to set a Monster in face-down Defense Position!
Then I set one card and end my turn!
So what now? Your combo won't activate if I set a Monster in Defense Mode, right?
It's useless to struggle.
You cannot escape me in this jungle.
My turn! Draw!
At this moment, in order to keep Death Butterfly's Invitation, I will pay 2000 of my Life!
I activate Photon Assassin Butterfly's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it can switch one Monster on the field from Defense Position to Attack Position!
And that Monster's Attack Power will drop 600 points!
Heraldry Beast Aberconway was changed to Attack Position!
Photon Assassin Butterfly, attack Aberconway!
Butterfly Death Dance!
And because of the Continuous Magic, Death Butterfly's Invitation,
the destroyed Monster's controller...
...takes 1500 points of damage!
That's awesome, Droite!
I set a Monster in face-down Defense Mode.
Turn end.
A flawless, perfect combo, is it?
I won't let you meet Kaito.
Huh?
You're cutting away your own Life...
...no, cutting away your actual life in order to protect Kaito?
Are you thinking of Kaito to that extent?
All of your actions are what
we refer to as the "power of love", right?
Huh? Love? Droite's doing this for Kaito?
Gosh, you're so thickheaded.
But the power of love, huh? It's kind of lovely...
Do you get it now? Even if you play a Monster in Defense Mode,
you will be unable to escape from this combo.
My turn. Draw.
I Summon Heraldry Beast Bernard's Falcon.
So you finally prepared yourself.
This moment you Summoned a Monster in Attack Mode,
the effect of the Continuous Magic, Butterfly Charm, will activate!
All the Monsters on my opponent's field in Attack Mode must attack!
In addition, I activate the effect of the Continuous Magic, Assassin's Gate!
When Monsters attack that don't have "Assassin" in their name, they are forcefully destroyed!
And because of the effect of Death Butterfly's Invitation...
...you take 1500 damage.
Awesome!
That Tron dude may really not be able to beat Droite!
I did it! Now my victory is assure-
Nice. Very nice.
The "power of love" humans share.
I want to experience it as well.
I mean your painful emotions overflowing with memories of Kaito!
I want to sink my teeth into those memories.
Now, here I come!
I activate the Magic Card High Medallion Arts!
This card allows me to conduct an Xyz Summon using two Heraldry Beasts with the same level from my Graveyard!
He's going to Xyz Summon with Monsters from the Graveyard!?
I Overlay the Level Four Aberconway and Bernard’s Falcon from my Graveyard!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 8!
Heraldry King Genome Heriter!
That's...
Tron's Number!
I'll end my turn with this.
It makes no difference whether you played a Number! The next turn will determine the outcome!
My turn! Draw!
I won't let you lay even one finger on Kaito!
I activate the effect of Photon Butterfly Assassin!
I detach one Overlay Unit!
It switches a Defense Monster into Attack Mode and reduces its Attack Power by 600 points!
Excite Scales!
Photon Butterfly Assassin attacks Heraldry King Genome Heriter!
This ends it!
Butterfly Death Dance!!
Yes! If this gets through...!
I activate Genome Heriter's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can choose one of 3 effects!
I will steal your Monster’s name!
What's going on?
I stole its name. Watch carefully.
My Genome Heriter’s name changes to Photon Butterfly Assassin.
On the contrary, your Monster's lost its name.
I wonder what will happen if it's no longer an "Assassin".
Th-This can't be...!
Now, I'll activate the effect of the Continuous Magic, Assassin Gate!
When a Monster whose name does not contain "Assassin" attacks,
the attack is negated and it's destroyed!
Smash to pieces, Miss Nobody!
My combo's been broken...!
In addition, as per the effect of the Continuous Magic, Death Butterfly Invitation,
you'll take 1500 points of damage!
Does this mean I can't defeat that man?
Oh yeah, I just thought of something good.
I'll steal your memories from you.
No!!
It can't be... Droite's memories have...
Hey, Droite!
What's wrong?! Droite!
Don't let Tron's powers beat you!
Weren't you fighting for Kaito's sake?!
You gotta win... and go see Kaito!
I... Kaito...
Kaito!
Kaito...
Don't rely on others!
That's right... I won't rely on anyone else!
I Summon Moonlit Papillion!
Then I Flip Summon the Phantom Butterfly Assassin Ulysses I had set in reverse!
I Overlay the Level Four Phantom Butterfly Assassin Ulysses and Moonlit Papillion!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself! Photon Alexandra Queen!
Droite... hasn't given up yet!
I activate the effect of Photon Alexandra Queen!
I detach all of her Overlay Units to send every Monster on the field to our hands,
inflicting 500 points of damage to each player for each!
- A draw?!
Butterfly Effect!
I don't need my Life... nor my real one at that!
Together with the memories I hold of Kaito, I will...!
Well said for an insect!
Your feelings, your memories...
...will become a delicious meal for me!
Trap, activate! Medallion Record!
It negates an effect that uses Overlay Units!
N-No way...!
Your turn?
Turn... end.
Droite! Stay with us!!
No! I don't want to forget... you.
They're flowing into me.
Your consciousness... Your memories... Your love!
My turn! Draw!
Sleep inside me, Droite.
I attack Photon Alexandra Queen with Photon Butterfly Assassin!
Stop it!!
Butterfly Death Dance!
Because of the effect of Death Butterfly's Invitation...
Droite, you will journey to the land of amnesia.
Kaito...
Kai...
What gives?
Memories of love aren't tasty at all.
Tron!!
Next time I'll eat your heart, Yuma.
Droite!
Tell that person...
Please... remember me...
Kaito...
No way...
So that's... Tron's power!
I won't ever... forgive you!
Tron!!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
The next battle takes place in the Space Field! The showdown between that Kaito and V will start!
Plus, we learn the shocking truth from V.
His attacks won't get through?!
Yuma...! Over there!
Kaito, V, and my dad?!
Did all the mysteries start here?
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Galaxy Eyes Sealed?! The Cosmic Class Number Appears!"
Is that...really a Monster?!
This time we're gonna introduce Number 8, Heraldry King Genome Heriter!
It's a terrifying Monster with the ability to absorb the name of the opposing Monster.
Let's see...
Whoa, did you forget my name?
Wait, who are you again?