Pardon me?
What do you think yer doin', you?
So... You're gonna keep following me around?
It's not that I don't want to leave. I just don't know how.
I might learn how to leave once I regain all of my memories.
And just how are your memories gonna return?
By gathering all of the Numbers.
Numbers?!
You're not about to tell me that I'm the
one who's gotta do it, are you?!
Yuma's over there talking to himself again...
I wonder if this "Duelist Spirit" of his really exists...
That's a definite, definite "no", pal!
So quit following me!
Yuma... You're becoming really weird lately...
Observation number two...
"You are weird."
I'll be sure to remember that.
I am not weird!
Wh-What the?!
What's wrong, Sis?!
It's gone...
The manuscript's gone...!
The system's been infected by a virus...
And there's only one hour until the deadline...
C-Calm down, Sis...
I won't make the delivery...!
At times like this, my sister gets...!
We better get outta here...
Right...!
Yuma!
You better find an explanation for this pronto!
It's impossible to deal with my sister when she gets like that...
That aside, this delay is way too much.
Yeah.
The traffic lights are all corrupted.
And the monorail's stuck in its tracks.
Wh-What's this?!
Whoa!
How lucky!
It's raining juice!
H-Hey, Yuma!
You can't just take those!
I'll give 'em bac-
Cleaning! Cleaning!
Hey, you! Lem'me go!
Lay off!
Today, the city suffered a massive system downage.
The cause-
The manuscript's gone...
Time to dig in!
I missed the delivery!
Earlier today, I got grabbed by one of those O-Bots!
My, my, as did I!
Huh? What's with that?
It was just on the news!
It's a big crisis!
The public vending machine broke down.
Wow, the monorail's moving again.
Looks like things are finally working again.
So basically, I wasn't the only one who lost all their data?
Sis?
Something smells fishy.
- Huh?
NO!
I meant this incident smells!
I can't waste any time!
Gotta replenish my energy!
That's mine!
Gotta hurry and eat!
God!
So this is the method humans use to replenish their energy?
So...
That energy...
...is then released after said replenishment...
...I think?
There's lots of reasons for this!
I am confused as to why I can't join you inside there.
Idiot!
That's obvious, ain't it?!
It's a trade secret method we use to release our energy!
If someone happened to see us while doing it, we'd die!
My word!
To think you would go to such lengths for nourishment...
Observation number three...
"Humans must eat and release in an endless combination.
However, they will die the moment anyone sees them doing this."
Can it!!
But it is peculiar.
If humans really operate in such a perfect combination...
...why is your Dueling so incompetent?
And what the heck is that supposed to mean?
Put bluntly, you are unskilled when it comes to Dueling.
Shut up!
There's no such thing as a "perfect human"!
It's more fun when you fail!
If you fail, you will lose something of great value.
Humph!
I can't bring it to 'em if I'm scared of failing!
A spirit like you will never get it!
I'm sure that I have a very important mission to fulfill.
I'm certain that I have been trapped with Yuma in order to see that said mission is completed.
Despite that, my memories have been trapped within 99 different cards...
And then scatterd bearing the name "Numbers".
My memories won't return unless I gather these Numbers...
Numbers seem to have the power to control humans...
Right... This young boy was able to use the Numbers to its fullest while I couldn't...
Why...?
Is it because he secretly harbors something within...?
What is this place?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
OW!
"Numbers 3:
A Sudden Incident During the Aftermath!!"
Su-weet! The guy's not here anymore!
O-Oh, snap!
I'M LATE!!
Made it on time~
Okay! Listen up, everyone!
Due to yesterday's communication error, the entire school's broadcasting computers are currently down as a result.
So we can't access the textbooks.
The cause of the error was-
Me! Please let me answer this!
Oh? Committee Chairman, you know something about this?
I do! I simply used my programming skills to mentally place myself in a similar setting.
To summarize, the malfunctioning issue was caused by someone infiltrating the city's host computer.
So if I were to create-
Sensei!
How 'bout we make today into a Duel tournament!
Hmm... Perhaps.
Why not?
Booyah!
I'm gonna bring it to every last one of you today!
- All right!
- That's Ukyo-sensei for you!
Just when I was finally on stage...
In that case, Yuma-kun!
To summarize, you Duel with me!
Sure! It'd be my pleasure!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Duel Target: Lock-On!!
Link established between A and B.
Duel!!
You can do it, Yuma!
Yuma-kun, is there any merit to the
rumors that you defeated Shark?
You bet! It's true!
I just can't believe that.
That you did, despite having never defeated me in your entire life.
It's the truth, Committee Chairman.
We're the witnesses!
So I see. Meaning that if I were to win this Duel...
To summarize, it would mean that I am
stronger than Shark, correct?
You keep saying "to summarize"...
It'd be really bad if your throat was
sum-mothered by that sea lion-sized sentence!
"If my throat was smothered"?!
Okay, let's get it on!
I got me a Numbers card!
Huh?
Gone! The Numbers' gone!
Here I come!
My turn! Draw!
H-HOLD ON A MINUTE!!
Go, Bugman X!
Direct Attack!
You gotta be kidding!
4,000 to zero...
Y-Yuma...
He totally wiped the floor with you!
As expected, someone like Yuma-kun who never studies could never beat me!
To summarize, a fool can't hope to win a Duel.
What?!
Don't be like that, now.
Life and Dueling are one and the same.
It never goes just as you plan.
One should learn through messing up.
Bugman, for example, lives off of failure.
Bugman...
An electrical fairy that lives off of the other bugs.
It becomes extremely powerful because it lives off its bug friends.
It's said that those who witness its full moon like appearance may forever live in happiness.
Sensei, to summarize, there's no such thing as stuff like that in real life!
There is. I'm sure of it.
Yuma, it's fine that you lost just now.
You just have to learn from it.
Isn't that the challenge spirit you like to call "bringing it to 'em"?
Ukyo-sensei!
You're right!
I'll always keep bringin' it to 'em!
Ukyo-sensei sure is a nice guy!
He's really smart when it comes to teaching math and he's really nice on top of it!
I'm definitely gonna become like that man!
Hi, Yuma!
Sis!
Why don't the two of you come for a little drive?
It's a certainly a good thing that the computer virus incident that spread yesterday only lasted for a while.
But what if things had lasted much longer?
There's a very good chance the entire city would be thrown into a huge panic.
A-A huge panic?
Beyond traffic lights or vending machines.
Suppose the banks' data was erased and rewritten.
Or say the hospital lost all its data.
It'd be a terrible thing, wouldn't it?
Y-You serious?
Who would try to do such a thing?
Well, the computer virus was transferred from the jurisdiction within your school.
I want the two of you to stake out the jurisdiction.
There's a good chance the culprit will appear again.
This seems pretty interesting, don't you think?!
Hold it. Why do we have to do this?
I don't wanna hear any complaints!
It's my article that was ruined by this!
Once we find the culprit, I'll karate chop the guy 'till he's blue in the face!
Listen up, Yuma.
Your sister said the culprit is sure to appear in the library so he can access its personal computer.
What a drag...
Gosh! Shape up and get on look-out already!
It's almost closing time.
Maybe he's just not coming today?
Yuma, look! Isn't that...
Committee Chairman!
He looks pretty suspicious...
Yuma!
That's a flash drive!
Don't tell me this is...!
Caught you!
Wha-
So you were the culprit behind that incident!
I am not!
I am not the culprit!
I was being used!
You're a liar!
We just saw you input the virus!
What're you doing?
I'm intervening the culprit!
If I search for any locations that
accessed this machine from the outside,
the culprit has to be there!
Damn it!
I came here to retrieve the data files so I could reveal the culprit's whereabouts!
Without knowing it, I activated the installation files that launched the virus bomb!
I accidentally released the virus bomb into the city!
Found him!
He triggered the virus bomb?
Yeah! I'm looking for the culprit!
So you have to do something about the bomb, Sis!
Hold on, Yuma!
It's over there!
The culprit is inside the nodule within the top of the tower!
You sure the culprit's really hiding out in here?
I am. He is here, without a doubt.
Surprise, surprise.
Despite the various options, you made it here so quickly.
Ukyo-sensei!
Why are you here, Sensei?
So, to summarize, Ukyo-sensei is the culprit?!
I suppose you could say that.
You gotta be pulling my leg, Sensei!
The very fact that our Committee Chairman was able to make it here was all within my expectations.
To summarize, this was a trap!
The virus bomb you uploaded will go off in a mere 30 minutes.
Because I truly wanted you to witness firsthand my virus bomb being set off.
So that makes me your accomplice?!
Numbers!
Observation number four...
"This is not something of this world."
It may be hiding some kind of message within it.
Like a puzzle of some sort.
What the?
Could that be a Numbers?!
Sensei...
That's the mark of the Numbers...
You didn't get sent away?!
Of course not.
But you weren't here all this time!
Y-Yuma-kun...?
Why is he talking to himself?!
Maybe that Dueling Spirit appeared!
Talking with this guy's a waste of time!
Sensei, why are you doing something so stupid?!
Consider this a challenge issued down from me!
It is no different from you "bringing it to 'em"!
No it's not!!
Causing trouble for others isn't what we call "bringing it to 'em"!
Yuma, let's Duel him.
His heart is being engulfed by the Numbers.
Trying to persuade him is pointless unless we remove him from the Numbers.
Let's Duel, Sensei!
If you lose to me, you'll agree to stop that virus bomb!
Duel?!
So be it!
If you win, I'll stop the virus bomb!
But I do wonder if you can oppose me?
I'll show you my strength when I bring it to you!
It's a match!
D-Gazer, set!
Target: Lock-On!
Link established between A and B.
Duel!!
You can do it, Yuma!
You better win!
If you don't, I'll be framed as a criminal!
I'll be going first!
My turn! Draw!
I set a Monster in Face-Down Defense Position!
Face-Down Defense Position?!
What kind of Monster did he set?!
I will leave it at that and end my turn.
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
I have no idea what the Defense Power of the Monster he set is!
Fine! No use over thinking it!
Gagaga Magician!
Attack the thing!
Naive.
Come out, Bugman X!
It's got 2000 Defense Points!
Yuma's Monster stayed in one piece, but his Life fell!
When you attack a Monster with higher Defense Power, the attacking Monster isn't destroyed,
but its Attack Power is subtracted from the other's Defense Power.
To summarize, that's 2000 - 1500!
As a result, he takes 500 points of damage!
Then it's my turn again!
Draw!
I Summon Bugman Y!
I continue with a Magic Card from my hand.
Bug Load activates!
This card lets both players select one Level Four or lower Monster on their field.
We can then Special Summon a Monster from our hands holding the same level as the chosen Monster.
I Special Summon Bugman Z!
Okay! I got a Monster in my hand
with the same level as Gagaga Magician!
I have the Level Four Gogogo Golem!
I'm gonna take Gogogo Golem and-
Yuma, Summon it in Defense Position.
Gogogo Golem has an effect that will allow for it to not be destroyed in battle once per turn.
I don't mind Dueling, but I never asked
for you to tell me how to Duel!
I Summon Gogogo Golem in Attack Mode!
How 'bout it?! You won't break 1800 Attack Points so easily!
You've just provided me with the chance
I needed for my perfect victory!
I Overlay the Level Three Bugman X, Y and Z!
I construct the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
He played it, as expected.
An Exceeds Monster using three overlays?!
Oh, yes!
Exceeds Summon!
Show yourself!
Numbers 34!
Computer Beast Terabyte!
N-Numbers?!
Please tell me what the Monster is!
A Numbers?
Got it!
Wow, I got Revise Dragon in here now, too.
Huh? Did this guy take it or something?
Allow me to proceed!
I activate Terabyte's effect!
I can use one of the Overlay Units on this card once per turn
and gain control over one of the opponent's Level Four or lower Monsters for the turn!
This is the perfection that makes up my Dueling!
Ah! My Gogogo Golem is...!
Go, Gogogo Golem!
Gagaga!
I managed to access the program hosting the virus bomb...
But where is the activation switch?
So I have to search for it in this dungeon, huh?
Under a time limit to boot...
What do you think of my perfect Dueling?
"Perfect, perfect"...!
Is perfection that important?!
It is. Perfection is everything.
I infected this city's program in order to seek the perfection I seek!
A dunce like you can't hope to win!
This is the same Sensei I praised so much?
It hurts.
Where does it hurt?
My heart!
Observation number five...
"Humans feel pain in their hearts."
I'll be sure to remember that.
In summary, I understand this pain I'm feeling now all too well.
Yuma-kun...
Yuma-kun!
I hate to bring it up at a time like this, but...
"To summarize" is meant to be the finalizing part of the sentence to give closure to the subject at hand.
So in the end, it gives off a meaning of "absolute finalization" of sorts...
Whac'cha talking about?!
I can use it however I want!
To summarize, it means an idiot like yourself can't possibly hope to defeat me!
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's question!
Monster Cards have these star markings on them, you see?
And what exactly do these stars mean?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
You can't beat him in this Duel.
I don't wanna hear that from you!
Hurry! We're almost out of time!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Countdown to Reversal! The Ace-In-The-Hole's Astral!?"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
And the answer is...
It's the Monster's level!
If it's got four stars, it means it's a "Level Four"!
You can bet a higher level Monster's gonna have a ton of 'em!