I overlay 3 LV 2 Giant Virus,
and construct overlay network with these 3 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Here it comes! Numbers!
Come forth, No.96!
Black Mist!
A...ATK 100?
Don't tell me...it's very weak?
Let me crush this Numbers!
Wait, Yuma! It's most important now, to observe your opponent!
Don't attack recklessly!
I attack Black Mist with Hope!
Yuma!
Go, Hope!
HOPE SWORD SLASH!!
I did it, a big win!!!
That was awesome, Yuma!
A piece of cake, I call it perfect victory!
Did you see that?
Hmph, as long as I'm around, the Numbers stand no chance!
It's just a single win you know.
But that attack from Hope was kind of reckless.
It's alright, that kind of Numbers ain't worth it...
That's NOT what I meant! You're completely clueless about what that monster is!
But I won anyway! I have my own ways to do things.
Hmpf... What's up with your attitude?
You are so darn annoying!
STOOOOOOOOOOP IT!
Alright, time to duel, who should I...
Looks like it's kinda serious this time.
The devastation of world...
... is that part of my memory as well?
It's already been 3 days.
This is the first time I haven't dueled with Tetsuo for this long.
My name is Tsukumo Yuma, my dream is to become Duel Champion!
Hey you...are you really that good at dueling?
Although I haven't won a duel even once...
Are you stupid?
Ever since then, he's been challenging me.
How dare you laugh at me!
Save your regrets after you beat me! DUEL!
In the end I was crushed
Even so Tetsuo was willing to duel with me again and again.
Although that guy kept losing all the time, he was still willing to challenge me every day.
I am definitely NOT going to give up!
After witnessing that guy's duel, I...
Apology!?
But if neither side is willing to apologize...
Hmpf! After all, it's his fault!
Yuma, do you really think it's OK if things continue like this?
As friends, isn't it necessary to communicate and share your thoughts?
Friends? Tetsuo is not my friend anymore!
Aww n- no...
Geez...
Tetsuo!
Y- You were the one coming at me!
And grabbed me all of sudden...
What is.. this?
Astral!
What on earth is that?
You are No. 96!
What are you saying there?
I've been waiting for this moment for a long time.
The moment I possess your body and become complete!
Destroy! Destroy everything!
What is this?
Yuma!
Re- release me!
It's useless, you can't run anywhere!
Yuma, give Hope to Tetsuo!
Hope?
Hurry!
Tetsuo!
Ehh...Hope?
Astral...
Now I've become the strongest of Numbers...
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
Ich hab mich damit belogen, das alleine sein leichter sei.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
You... you bastard, how dare you do that to Astral!
Numbers 20:
The Pitch-black Numbers! Dark Yuma vs Tetsuo!
Now you brat over there, give that Numbers to me!
Wha...
Tetsuo-kun...what was that just now?
I'm not sure, but I think it's due to the power of this key.
You bastard...
If so...as long as I beat him, and return Emperor's Key to Yuma,
maybe Yuma can be released!
If you want this Numbers that badly, then get it by defeating me in a duel!
Duel you say?
No, Tetsuo! This guy is very dangerous, hurry up and run!
How can I leave you like this?
But...
Would you run if you were in my situation? Would you abandon me and run away?
Tetsuo...
Interesting, I will be your opponent.
DUEL DISK SET!
D-GAZER SET!
AR-VISION, LINK ESTABLISHED.
DUEL!
You have no freedom, my servant.
Even though Astral is my opponent, I do know every single card Yuma has in his deck!
I will go first!
My turn, draw!
I summon Aiaian!
Then I activate equip magic Spring Punch, and equip it to Aiaian!
Then I activate the monster effect of Aiaian!
Once per turn, its ATK increases by 400!
At this moment I activate the effect of Spring Punch!
If the ATK of equipped monster increases,
the opponent will receive damage equal to half of its ATK, in other words 1000 damage!
Yuma!
I...I'm alright.
Now! Come at me!
I activate Continuous Magic Clockwork Catapult! I end my turn.
Wait Yuma. I will save you as soon as possible.
My turn, draw!
I special summon Fallen Cone!
This card can be special summoned, if I send one card from my hand to the graveyard!
Next, as it was sent to the graveyard from my hand, Growing Pinecone can be special summoned as well!
Be reborn, Growing Pinecone!
Then I normal summon Darklon!
When Darklon is successfully summoned,
all monsters on my field become DARK-attribute, and have their Level increase by one!
I overlay level 2 Fallen Pinecone, Growing Pinecone and Darklon!
I construct the overlay network with these 3 monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, my true form!
No. 96!
The messenger from the Pitch-Black Darkness! Black Mist!
That's Black Mist?
It's completely different from before!
This is the real form of Black Mist.
I attack Aiaian with Black Mist!
Attack? With only 100 attack points...
I activate the effect of Black Mist!
By detaching one overlay unit, the ATK of one of my opponent's monsters is halved.
And that halved amount is added to my own attack points!
SHADOW GAIN!
That means it's always more powerful than the opponent's monster?
That's right! Go, Black Mist!
BLACK MIRAGE WHIP!
I set two cards, and end my turn.
So this is the power of Black Mist...
My turn, draw!
I activate the effect of Continuous Magic Clockwork Catapult!
When my turn comes, it gains one Clockwork counter!
Counter?
Counters are units you can use to activate certain effects!
So you want to strengthen the effect of that Magic card by saving counters?
I summon Tin Goldfish!
Next from my hand I activate Iron Call!
The effect of this card is that when there is a machine-type monster on my side of the field,
I can special summon one LV4 or lower Machine-type monster from my graveyard!
Resurrect yourself, Aiaian!
Then I activate the magic card from my hand, Iron Draw!
When there are 2 Machine-type monsters on my field, I can draw 2 cards from my deck!
Yuma, I'll definitely save you!
I overlay LV4 Tin Goldfish and Aiaian!!
I construct the overlay network with these 2 monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, No. 39, Aspiring Emperor Hope!!
Hope...
So you're finally here...No.39.
What is this feeling?
So this is the power of the Numbers.
Yuma!
I activate the effect of Clockwork Catapult!
By removing one clockwork counter, this turn, Hope's attack increases by 500!
An attack power of 3000!
Alright, go, Hope!
It seems you still don't understand the terror of Black Mist!
I activate the effect of Black Mist! Shadow Gain!
What?!
I thought Shadow Gain's effect can only be activated when it declares an attack!
Hope's attack points were absorbed!
Go! Black Mist!
Tetsuo!
Black MIRAGE WHIP!
I activate the monster effect of Hope!
It can negate one monster's ATK!
MOON BARRIER!
Alright, it's a success!
Hmph! As expected.
I activate trap! Resilience!
If the battle was negated,
this card inflicts damage to my opponent equal to the difference of those monsters' attack points!
Tetsuo-kun will receive 1100 damage?!
Tetsuo!
Do you understand now?
How can you ever beat me?
Tetsuo...
No matter whether it's attacking or being attacked, its attack power will increase,
What kind of monster is that?
Sorry, Tetsuo!
Yuma...
Astral, is that you?
Yuma, listen to me carefully.
I activate the Continuous Magic card from my hand, Automated Clockwork Machine!
When activated, I can place 2 clockwork counters onto this card!
When my turn comes, it will get one more!
And when I send this card to the graveyard,
this card's clockwork counters can be transferred to another card!
So you're trying to save up even more clock counters?
I set one card, and end my turn!
Clockwork Catapult's effect will expire now.
Hope's attack will decrease by 500!
What?!
Yuma!
Finally, has he gotten possessed by me as well?
My turn, draw!
I attack Aspiring Emperor Hope with Black Mist!
And I activate the monster effect! Shadow Gain!
I activate Hope's monster effect! Moon Barrier!
Trying to defend with that again?
I activate a trap! Overlay Banish!
It negates an effect from my opponent's monster that uses Xyz material!
Go, BLACK MIRAGE WHIP!
Tetsuo-kun!
And now, I will destroy Clockwork Catapult...
What?!
I've already see through it, you save all those clockwork counters...
... in order to strengthen your next summoned monster!
You're wrong.
His aim was to find a way to defeat you with only one blow.
With only one blow you say?
That guy's set card is Clockwork Explosive...
Don't tell him, Yuma!
It's useless! He can no longer hear your voice.
The effect of clockwork explosive is...
when his turn comes and the counters increase,
it inflicts 800 points of damage for each counter on the field.
800 points?
Next turn, the counters of Clockwork Catapult and Automated Clockwork Machine will both increase by one.
There will be total of 4 counters, in other words 3200 damage.
If that card is activated, we will lose.
So that's how it is.
No... Yuma!
In that case I shall destroy that set card!
I activate a Quick-Play Magic card from my hand, Xyz Cyclone!
When a Xyz monster is destroyed,
it can destroy one trap card!
Clockwork Explosive was...
Now I end my turn.
Good job Yuma, now I can win this duel.
Yuma...
I am definitely NOT going to give up!
Darn it!
That's right, even Yuma would never give up!
Wait... Clockwork Catapult?
Yuma...
My turn, draw!
It's here!
Due to their card effects, the counters of Clockwork Catapult and Automated Clockwork Machine will all increase by one!
Hmph! Useless struggle!
Then by removing 3 counters from Automated Clockwork Machine,
I special summon Clockwork Shikigami from my hand!
The effect of Clockwork Shikigami is, once per turn, until the end phase,
The attack power of one monster my opponent controls becomes zero!
What?!
Then I activate a magic card from my hand, Monster Reborn!
Come, Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Hope is resurrected!
What on...earth?
You did it! Tetsuo!
What the...? What's going on here?
Yuma pretended that he was possessed by you.
Back then, if you would have destroyed Clockwork Catapult,
then I would have no chance of winning.
That's why Yuma pretended he was being manipulated,
to defend Clockwork Catapult at all costs!
Damn you all!
Our friendship will never lose to the likes of you!
I activate the effect of Clockwork Catapult!
By removing one Clockwork counter, Hope's attack increases by 500!
An attack of 3000?
Plus Black Mist's effect can no longer be used!
You lose! No.96!
Go, Tetsuo!
This is how I Bring it to 'em!
No way!
HOPE Sword SLASH!
Impossible! I was...
Yuma, catch!
We did it, Tetsuo!
Yuma!
But I can't believe you actually had that combo for a comeback up your sleeve.
Eh...I guess.
That means...it was Astral's plan?
No, no! Although I did take some advice from him.
I thought so. You wouldn't think that far ahead.
In the end, I did that because you couldn't finish off that guy fast enough!
What did you say? I am the one who saved you! How can you say that?
Yuma, Tetsuo. I was saved.
No.96...
This Numbers is...
The First Monster Popularity Voting!
Part two!
Decide who is number one among these 13 monsters!
Go to the show's home page and vote!
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Our new friend!
Her name is Obomi!!
But a guy is planning to use Obomi as Jewelry Bandit.
Next,Yu-Gi-Oh ZeXal, Yuma vs Trashbot Obomi!!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Needle Swordsman
Big Jaws
Baby Tragon
Black Ray Lancer
Submersible Aero-Shark
Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon