Here, your favorite hot chocolate.
Where are we?
Can't you remember? We've been living inside this house since we were little.
I see. I can't remember a thing.
You used to laugh a lot back then.
You were quite talkative and you loved to joke.
Haruto...
The one who made you this way...
Did I bother you guys?
Alright, Haruto, time to get to work.
Mr. Heartland. Haruto collapsed due to exhaustion from overusing his ability.
If we continue to use Haruto's power like that...
Kaito, this is an order from Dr. Faker-sama.
But...
I don't like it...
I don't like you when you're not considerate of others.
Haruto...
I am fine with it. If my power can contribute something to this world, then there's no need to worry about me.
Fantastic, Haruto!
Dr. Faker-sama must be proud as well.
Kaito, if you really wish to cure Haruto, then you should hurry up and collect all the Numbers.
That hurt...!
Did you say there's a spaceship inside Emperor's Key?
Yes.
Inside such small key...?
It seems this key is not something that belongs to this world.
There are many hidden secrets inside your father's key.
Then can that spaceship fly?
There is a huge puzzle inside the spaceship's construction.
We need the Numbers in order to solve this puzzle.
I'm afraid when all the Numbers are collected, that spaceship will...
Numbers...
Orbital, we will resume the Numbers Hunt.
Explain the current circumstances to me.
Orbital!
Orbital Seven!
Un....Understood!!
K-Kaito-sama!
You little...
How's the data analysis for the Duelists holding Numbers going?
Eh... That? Well...
I hate incompetence the most... Are you incompetent?
Un...Understood!!
Please don't beat me into scraps, that's my only request!!
Search for the Original Numbers.
Original?
Yes. Dr Faker said that the Numbers carried along with them a messenger to this world
That person, the Original, must have attached himself to someone's body.
Original...?
Then Kaito-sama, I may have found something that will interest you.
This is that strange pendant, from the Numbers Duelist Yuma Tsukumo, whom we battled a few days ago.
What is this?
It's not something that belongs to this world.
What? The Duelist from before?
Alright, hurry and gather more data about this guy!
Un...Understood!
Yuma Tsukumo, huh...?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Shoot!
I forgot we have swimming for PE today!
"Numbers 22: The Stolen Emperor's Key!
Showdown - Kaito VS Shark!"
God, he's always so hotheaded...
I'm quite relieved.
I'm glad you finally came to school.
Did Yuma bring your heart back?
He has a unexplainable power like the sun.
People who have contact with Yuma have their hearts illuminated without noticing.
Don't you think so?
Maybe.
Hey, is Yuma-kun gonna bring it today?!
Who knows.
I'm looking forward to it.
I...guess...
Hold on!
What's your problem?!
You are not allowed to enter the pool while wearing a pendant!
Why?
That's because, to summarize, it's dangerous!
It's not dangerous at all!
Cat thinks so as well.
Say, Yuma, didn't you dive into the pool a few days ago...
...and injure your head as a result? Right...?
Head injury? Who hit theirs?
God...
My head!!
Man... Damn that Class Prez... He's such a pain.
Speaking of which, Astral... is he really inside this small thing?
Well... just make yourself comfortable.
A power comparable to the sun, huh?
I don't wanna be turned into scrap.
There must be some secrets about that pendant!
The pieces of my memories, the Numbers cards...
I managed to recover 10 of them.
What's that in my memory?
No... I can't remember it! I have to collect more Numbers!
So it' s here, let me find it.
Target confirmed!
Then I will receive it.
Mission complete!
What on Earth are you doing?
I... P-Please return that pendant to me!
Otherwise I will become scrap!
I don't get a damn thing you're saying!
Nice one...
In that case, I will definitely make you return that pendant!
Let's see who will become scrap in the end!
What the hell is this thing?!
I will exterminate you!
Stop running away!
What? The key just stopped running!
The settled Numbers were deactivated as well! Was the Lord's key actually turned off?
Gimme that pendant!
That's enough, Orbital!
Just butting in like that...
Kaito-sama...
Would you mind handing me the pendant you're holding?
I refuse! This doesn't belong to you!
I'm aware. It belongs to Yuma Tsukumo.
Shark: You know Yuma?
Yeah. Since he has Numbers.
Numbers... I see...
You're the Numbers Hunter?!
Oh? You know who I am?
Then you must have Numbers.
And if I did?
Then it's just perfect for me!
I will get both a Numbers and the pendant! Let's Duel!
Yuma...it's time for me to return the favor to you.
Interesting!
I accept your challenge!
Duel Mode! Photon Change!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Now...! Offer me your soul!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Cruel...
Cat thinks it's too much!
Who did this...?
To summarize, no human could have done it.
It's gone...! Gone... gone! Gone!
The Lord's Key's gone!
The first turn is mine!
My turn! Draw!
If he's the Numbers Hunter, he must have a ton of Numbers at his disposal.
But I have a strategy meant to defeat the Numbers.
I send Big Jaws from my hand to the Graveyard!
I activate the Continuous Magic, Shark Rare, from my hand!
As long as this card's effect remains active,
you can't attack any of my Monsters with Attack Power less than the Monster's I just sent to the Graveyard!
Big Jaws's Attack Power is 1800!
Now you can't attack with any of your Monsters having 1800 or more Attack Power!
I then Summon Shacktopus!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Now call out your Numbers!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Fusion Magic Card from my hand!
Fusion?!
I fuse the two Photon Lizards in my hand!
By sending these small materials to the Graveyard,
I can Special Summon the Fusion Monster from my Extra Deck!
Fusion Summon!
Show yourself, Twin Photon Lizard!
It's true that Fusion Summoning allows you to play a powerful Monster in your first turn.
But for him to use fusion instead of an Xyz Summon...
Can this guy use any strategy to his will?
Your Magic Card blocks off attacks from a Monster with 1800 or higher Attack Power.
Such basic tricks won't work against me!
Go, Twin Photon Lizard!
Subliminal Breath!!
But I'll use the moment to activate Shacktopus's effect!
When Shacktopus is destroyed in battle, it becomes an Equipment Card attached to the opponent's Monster
and you can't change the captured Monster's Battle Position!
In other words, you're stuck with a zero Attack Power Monster on your field!
That changes the situation!
I'll deal you massive damage next turn!
I-Is this guy really good or something?!
I have to wonder if things will go that smoothly for you.
What?
I activate Twin Photon Lizard's effect!
If the material Monsters used for the Fusion Summon are in my Graveyard, I can cancel the fusion!
Two Level Three Monsters...!
Is he going for it?
I Overlay the two Level Three Lizards!
I use the two Monsters to construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear, No. 30!
Let your cursed power flow out of you!
Acid Golem of Destruction!
3000 Attack Points!
So this is his Numbers...!
But he fell for the trick I planned!
Trap, activate!
Splash Capture!
When my opponent Xyz Summons,
this card Banishes two Fish-Type Monster in my Graveyard
to grant me control over my opponent's Xyz!
I Banish the Big Jaws and Shacktopus in my Graveyard!
You fell for it, Numbers Hunter!
I was aiming to take control of your powerful Monster!
Now I've taken control of Acid Golem!
I've stolen your ultra powerful 3000 Attack Power Numbers!
This Duel is mine!
Kaito-sama, this is getting bad!
You stand back.
Understood.
I activate the Magic Card, Compulsory Removal!
This card sends the Overlay Units attached to an Xyz Monster on the field to the Graveyard!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
So you destroyed its Overlay Units, did you?
But as long as it's got its 3000 Attack Points...
My turn! Draw!
This very moment, you'll take Acid Golem's curse!
Curse?!
Acid Golem is a self-destructing Numbers, you see.
Acting as compensation for being a mere Rank Three, yet wielding 3000 Attack Power...
its body is engulfed with a set of deadly curses.
Wh-What did you say?
One of those being, if you don't detach one Overlay Unit from the start of your turn,
you suffer 2000 points of damage.
But Acid Golem still has its Attack Power!
Go, Acid Golem!
Direct Attack him!
It's useless.
What?!
If Acid Golem has no Overlay Units attached to it, it can't attack.
Wha-What did you say?
I knew you planned to use a Magic Card when I Summoned my powerful Numbers.
So I... was the one to fall into a trap?
If this keeps up, Acid Golem's effect will destroy me!
Numbers Hunter... He's unbelievably strong!
Am I going to lose like this?
That's right, huh?
Yuma...
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
The card I just set is Kick Back Life.
During a turn I would take Effect Damage, that damage is negated.
I still have a chance to win!
I won't ever give up!
I activate the Magic Card, Photon Sublimation!
By Banishing two Photon Monsters in my Graveyard,
I can draw two cards!
I Banish my two Photon Lizards!
I draw two cards!
I Special Summon Photon Slasher!
If I control no other Monsters, Photon Slasher can be Special Summoned.
I then Normal Summon Photon Crusher!
Here I come!
I release these two Monsters for a Special Summon!
Just what are you-
This card cannot be Normal Summoned.
But by releasing two Monsters with 2000 or more Attack Power, it can be Special Summoned!
Descend, Avatar of Light!
Wh-What the?
Show yourself, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Astral!
Wh-What the?!
Wh-What's going on?
Yuma!
What's up with those clouds?!
Could it be...?
Yuma!
Is there something happening in the outside world?
What?!
He immersed in the guidance time...
Obtain the power of "Rare".
The power that will turn all darkness into light...
ZeXal.
What is that Monster?!
This is over.
Photon Stream of Destruction!!
What?!
You're attacking a Numbers?!
Impossible!
Galaxy Eyes isn't a Numbers!
Why can it destroy a Numbers?!
Without Overlay Units attached to it,
Acid Golem will still be destroyed when it takes an attack.
But that attack just now was a bad play on your part!
You just set me free from the curse of Acid Golem!
I made a mistake, you say?
You're quite the romantic!
What?!
The curse has not ended.
When it is destroyed, its controller takes 2000 points of damage.
Wh-What did you say?!
Forgive me, Yuma...!
Offer it up...
Your soul.
There isn't a Numbers inside this soul...!
Sh-Shark!
Yuma Tsukumo.
You...! Kaito!
Shark!
Just what the hell did you do to him?!
Kaito-sama, you've used up about 85% of your Photon Mode!
You can't afford to Duel now...!
I know that.
Th-That's the Lord's Key!
Astral!!
Let's do this again!
It's the second popularity contest!
Here's a bunch of Numbers from Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
Which Numbers do you guys like?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
The time for me to fight you has finally come, Kaito!
Astral's fighting...!
I can tell!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Fated Duel! Astral VS Kaito"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
It's the second Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal popularity contest!
Let's Summon some new ones!
No. 39: Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
No. 17: Leviath Dragon.
No. 34: Computer Beast Terabyte!
"No. 83: Galaxy Queen"
No. 61: Volcasaurus!
No. 19: Freezadon.
No, 56: Goldrat!
Next week we'll Summon the remaining six!
Go vote on our home webpage!