After seeing Haruto in pain,
Kaito began to mess up his own Dueling.
And we're being pushed back by IV and III's tactics.
Go, Masshu Macu!
Infinity Cannon!
It's over, Kaito.
Take 3000 damage!
Trap, activate! Braveheart!
By halving my own Life, I can negate the activation of a Monster Effect this turn!
What?
Yuma!
The loser just had to make things complicated...
He sacrificed himself again...
You okay, Astral?
There's no helping you.
This is your Dueling, after all.
I'm used to it.
Why did you...?
I told you!
I said I'd bring you to Haruto!
Stay out of it!
I set one card and end my turn!
Geez! He could at least thank Yuma!
Please forgive him. Kaito-sama's desperate!
Here.
That's amazing, Brother!
These are... Haruto's memories.
Sure is pretty!
I know we just captured it and all, but can we let it go?
Huh?
I mean, it's pitiful to spend your entire life in a cage.
Haruto-sama...!
You sure are kind.
I will steal all of your memories from you!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Go on and draw your card!
"Number 43: The Miraculous Overlay,
Neo Galaxy Eyes Photon Dragon!"
Heh, don't be in such a hurry.
You sure are looking like a sorrowful mess.
Damn you IV!
That really was too much.
Too much!?
Have you forgotten the pain we've been through!?
Brother...
Just focus on your job!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Continuous Magic called OOPArt Pyramid Eye Tablet!
This card increases the Attack Power of OOPArt Monsters on my field by 800 points.
I activate Masshu Macu's Monster Effect!
When a Monster's Attack Power is changed, I can detach one Overlay Unit
and this card damages my opponent based on the difference.
Go, Masshu Macu!
Infinity Cannon!
The loser's Life is now a candle light flickering in the wind.
And you're next, Kaito!
Do it, III!
Masshu Macu, attack Galaxy-Eyes!
Fire of Vril!
Thanks to the effect of Stonehenge Shield, Galaxy-Eye's Attack Power is zero!
This ends it, Kaito!
Kaito!
Trap, activate! Battle Simulation!
When two Monsters battle, this card halves both Monsters' Attack Points,
and protects the Monsters from being destroyed in battle!
But you'll still take battle damage!
Kaito-sama!
Kaito!
You okay?
Hey!
Kaito...
It's not over...
I still have Life left!
What useless struggling.
You should obediently fall into Hell like your brother!
You bastard...!
Kaito!
Calm down!
Shut up!
How could you possibly understand my suffering... my sadness?!
Yeah, I can't.
I have no clue about you and Haruto's pain!
But I Dueled you!
I Dueled against you and understood you!
Dueling allows one to make new friends and forge new bonds.
And Dueling lets one change themselves and bring it on a whole new level!
Dueling isn't a tool for one to smash their grudges and hatred against each other!
I'll show you how I bring it!
Everything lies on this one draw.
Go, Yuma!
Right!
My turn! Draw!
It's here!
I activate the Magic Card Resurrection of the Dead!
Revive, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
He brought back his Number.
Hope's power won't end there!
This is how I bring it to ya!
Chaos Xyz Change!
Show yourself, Chaos Number 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope Ray!
That's...!
Chaos Number, he said?!
What is that Number?!
This boy... Yuma Tsukumo...
Tsukumo...?
Could it be...?
That's Yuma's light of hope!
See that? It's Hope's true form!
I've never seen this Number before...
How can... this loser have a card like that?
I activate Hope Ray's Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can increase this card's Attack Power by 500 points!
Overlay Charge!
Yuma, he's already used all of Masshu Macu's Overlay Units.
But if he uses the effect of Giant Killer, who still has Overlay Units attached,
we're done for.
I know that!
Then I decrease the Attack Power of an opposing Monster by 1000 points!
I select Giant Killer!
Go, Hope Ray!
Hope Sword Chaos Slash!
IV has 2400 Life left.
With this attack...
We beat IV!
He did it! Great job!
The Permanent Tram, Gimmick Box.
What?!
When a player is to take battle damage, this card negates that damage,
and is then Special Summoned as a Monster.
And this card's Attack Power becomes equal to the amount of negated damage!
No way...!
Even Hope Ray couldn't stop him?
He read through our attack?
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
And Hope Ray's Attack Power returns to normal.
You honestly thought you could defeat me?!
Let me show you what true despair looks like!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card Junk Puppet!
This card Special Summons a Gimmick Puppet Monster from my Graveyard with 1000 or less Attack Points in Defense Mode!
Revive, Gimmick Puppet - Necro Doll!
I Overlay the Level Eight Gimmick Box and Necro Doll!
I build the Overlay Network with these two Dark Attribute Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 40!
Gimmick Puppet - Heaven's Strings!
What?!
No way! A 3000 Attack Power Number!
Time to wrap up my fanservice.
Kaito, I'll send you to Hell alone first!
Heaven's Strings! Attack Galaxy-Eyes!
Heaven's Blade!
At this rate, Kaito will...!
Haruto...
It's finished this time for sure, Kaito!
Trap, activate! Trap Reborn!
This card halves my Life and lets me Banish a Trap Card in my opponent's Graveyard, gaining its effect!
I choose Battle Simulation!
Battle Simulation negates a battle between two Monsters,
and negates the Monsters' destruction!
Kaito-sama!
Again?! Will you guys cut the bullshit already?!
Just die already!
Just die!
Yuma...
You reduced your own Life again...
Wasting my fanservice is unforgivable...!
I won't forgive you guys!
I activate Heaven's Strings effect!
This card can detach an Overlay Unit once per turn
At the end of the next turn, all Monsters on the field will be destroyed!
And the Attack Power of the destroyed Monster will be dealt to the player as damage!
What did you say?!
This is the lineage of those fated to control the power of the gods!
This is the absolute finale!
Now! It's your turns!
Now if we don't defeat them by the end of Kaito's next turn, we have no chance of winning.
Kaito...
What the heck? Out of strength already?
Guess we win if you can't even stand up.
Kaito...
Stand! Stand up, Kaito!
Are you okay losing like this?
Stand!
Why aren't you standing?!
Kaito!!
He's right! Stand, Kaito!
Stand up!
Eh?
Stand up and fight!
Please stand up, Kaito-sama!
It's fine if you're a mess. Just don't give up until the very end!
You can't just give up like this!
If you don't protect Haruto...
....who else is gonna protect Haruto!?
Haruto...
I've let you get hurt again...
Brother! Brother!!
Haruto!
Haruto!!
Kaito.
If you want to see Haruto, you have no choice but to work for Dr. Faker-sama.
Get along with him well, Kaito.
You bastard!
I swear to... protect you at all costs!
Haruto!!
I'll take all the memories you siblings share.
I won't let you.
Huh?
I won't hand the memories I share with my brother to anyone.
Haruto!
Why are you here?
What the...?
What's happening?
You couldn't possibly understand.
Not how hard my brother tries to protect me!
Not how he's shielded me for so long!
This time I'll protect my brother!
What the hell?!
Kaito-sama!
What?!
This is...
What's happening?
Why...?
Haruto's power disappeared...
Haruto... You gave me this power, didn't you?
A new power has just awakened with the Kaito deck!
A new power?
This is the bond between siblings.
It's created a miracle!
Kaito-sama!
My turn!
Draw!!
Galaxy-Eyes' Attack Power is zero!
Your Life is a mere 100!
What can someone with one foot in the grave possibly do!?
You're the only dieing ones here!
I activate the Magic Card, Overlay Regenerate, from my hand!
This card revives Overlay Units equal to the number of Xyz Monsters on the field!
Astral, are you there?!
You told me that I me and Yuma were similar.
If that's the case, resonate with me!
Yuma, let's use our Monster to help Kaito!
Right!
Kaito, use my Monsters!
Go!
I release Hope Ray and Damage Release...
...to Advance Summon Photon Kaiser!
When Photon Kaiser is used as Xyz Material, it can be counted twice!
I Overlay the Level Eight Galaxy-Eyes and the two Photon Kaisers!
I build the Overlay Network with these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Surging silver energy!
Become the rolling waves and show your mighty form!
Descend, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Galaxy-Eyes just evolved!
This is what I felt...
Kaito's new power!
Go! I activate Neo Galaxy-Eyes' Monster Effect!
Photon Howling!
When Neo Galaxy-Eyes is Summoned using Galaxy-Eyes,
it negates the effects of all other Monsters on the field!
What?
It can activate its effect without removing Overlay Units?
I activate Neo Galaxy-Eyes' second effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it takes away all other Overlay Units on the field!
It then gains 500 Attack Points for each Overlay Unit taken during this turn,
and can attack repeatedly for each!
6000 Attack Points!
And it's got consecutive attacks?!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
III!!
IV, are you ready for your punishment?!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
After the fight ended, V suddenly appeared before us.
I then learned the truth that someone dear to me who was supposed to have disappeared...
What the heck is going on here?!
Yuma, do you think he really...?!
Grandpa R-Rokujuro!
You're saying you don't care about the Numbers?
Do I choose Astral or Haruto?
There's no way I can decide that!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Forked Paths of Destiny! Yuma Abandons Dueling"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!