Darn, the third Heart Piece…
Why…? Why…? Why doesn’t it match?! Considering I just got my third Heart Piece after all that…!
They aren't that easy to assemble.
The heart was divided into several shapes, so only one piece can connect with another.
Huh? Is that so? Then there's no way I can connect them!
Forget about that, Yuma .
We have to find an opponent who uses a Number next time.
The reason we participated in the Duel Carnival is to recover Numbers, after all.
Isn’t that your problem?!
And you know what, it's always because of you every single time that-
Kotori!
I missed.
The hell? That AR was really powerful!
No, Yuma! This is real!
This time for sure!
This way!
Keep running, will you?
W-What the heck is going on?
It would seem you are being targeted.
How's that possible?!
This way, Kotori!
Right!
Don’t underestimate me.
Do you think you can run away from me?
Let’s go, Flying-
Stop!
No!
Stop i-
Hold it, dammit!
So she really is after us!
Who in the world is she?
Move, move, move!
Eat this!
This way!
W-We should be all right all the way up here...
End of the line!
You guys can't run away no-
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Um...
You aren’t running away! Are you prepared?!
"Number 29: Railroad Deck, Take Off!
The Runaway Duelist, Anna"
J-Just hold on! What in the world is going on here, anyway?!
Hmph… You're as dishonest as ever, Yuma Tsukumo!
Aren't you Anna?!
Anna?
C'mon, don’t you remember? Anna Kozuki?
Although she transferred to another school two years ago, she always fought with boys, and protected bullied kids. That Anna!
Did we know someone like that?
If you don't remember me, I'll have to jog your memory!
I remember, I remember! I think I remember you now!
But why were you chasing Yuma?
It's obvious! It's for revenge!
Revenge?
Yuma Tsukumo! I... l-like.... y...
Huh?
Like I said! I... love you...
Forget it!
Don't tell me Anna...!
So I…
So what on Earth is going on here?!
I once put glue underneath your shoes...
...drew on your D-Pad...
...cut a hole in your swimming trunks...
...and put a rock in your riceball.
Just how mean are you...?
Ah, now that you mention it...
Do you remember now?
And I transferred two years ago...
That’s why I called you out that time, because I wanted to confess to you before I moved!
But you didn’t come… I thought you knew my feelings…
I am definitely taking revenge for this!
At least allow me to blow you to smithereens!
Wa…wait! I understand how you feel.
But you don’t have to do all that, do you? Please, if you want revenge that bad… then let’s do it in a duel!
In a duel?
Yuma, you can't settle this with her through dueling!
Fine.
I will be your opponent. I knew you would do that, so I started dueling as well!
That makes no sense...
Under the conditions that you'll belong to me if I should win!
Sure! I won’t lose in a duel!
Yuma!
Let's fight, Yuma Tsukumo!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Is this the so-called "human love”? that’s something beyond my understanding…
I'm going first! My turn, draw!
I special summon Roaring Express Train Rocket Arrow!
5000 Attack Power!? What a monster!
She summoned heavy-class monster right away!
This card cannot be normal summoned.
This card can only be special summoned from my hand if I do not have any card on my field.
And during my turn, it will be destroyed if I don’t send 5 cards from my hand to the graveyard.
5 cards from your hand? If you send all of them to the graveyard, doesn't that mean your hand will be empty?
During the turn I special summon Roaring Express Train Rocket Arrow, I can declare an attack.
When this card is face-up on my field, I cannot set other cards either.
I end my turn. Alright, let’s see how you will attack!
My turn, draw!
Yuma , we cannot defeat Rocket Arrow in a mere turn.
Yeah. Then I will wait for next turn. I set a monster in face-down defense position.
Then I set one card, and end my turn.
So you're gonna run away?!
I-I am not running away!
Then behold! My turn, draw!
I will not pay the cost, so Rocket Arrow is destroyed.
Insanity!
I set 5 cards, and end my turn.
Now 5 set cards? Plus no monster means no guard?
What is she thinking?
Alright, come at me!
No point in over-thinking this.
My turn, draw!
I Summon Gogogo Giant!
I direct attack with Gogogo Giant!
If this connects, that’s 2000 points of heavy damage! Go!
Wait, Yuma ! She has 5 set cards!
I destroy all the set cards on my field!
What?!
Then I special summon Snow Plow Engine Hustle Russell!
This card cannot be normal summoned.
When my opponent declares a direct attack, by destroying all of my Magic and Trap Cards,
I can special summon from my hand!
Show yourself, Snow Plow Engine Hustle Russell!
2500 Attack Points?! Gogogo Giant, stop the battle.
You must be scared!
Then I will attack!
I activate the monster effect of Snow Plow Engine Hustle Russell!
For every card on Magic/Trap Zone destroyed by this effect, I can inflict 200 damage to my opponent!
Which means, 5 Cards for 1000 damage?!
Yuma!
Alright! 1000 damage to start off!
So she's going for Effect Damage, is she?
What’s going on in this duel?
- No matter how you look at it, her moves are weird and nonsensical.
- Yahoo! Yes, I'm gonna win this!
- Yet, they all seem calculated.
- Hey! It's your turn!
Be careful, Yuma! She’s extraordinarily strong!
- Hurry it up! You've got nothing else!
- Shut up! I was just being careless!
- Hurry up and end your turn already!
Turn end!
- Okay, here goes!
- Yuma...
My turn, draw!
I activate a magic card, Temporary Schedule!
This card can special summon 1 Machine-Type monster with 3000 or more ATK from my graveyard in defense position!
Revive, Roaring Express Rocket Arrow!
That monster again?
She's got two level 10 monsters...
Here I come, Yuma! Let’s see if you can stop my Runaway Deck!
I overlay the LV10 Rocket Arrow and Snow Plow Engine!
I build the overlay network with these two monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, Super-Heavy Artillery Train Gustav Max!
3000 Attack Points!
Not to mention it’s a Rank 10 Xyz monster!
Have a taste of its power! I activate the monster effect of Gustav Max!
Once per turn, by detaching one overlay unit, this card inflicts 2000 damage to my opponent!
I-It transformed! Plus, 2000 points of damage?!
Go, Gustav Max! Ready to fire, Big Canon!
I did it! Hooray, hooray!
Now you only have 1000 Life Points left!
This duel is mine!
You didn’t forget that promise, did you?
Here’s the final blow! I attack 2000 ATK Gogogo Giant with Gustav Max, who has 3000 ATK!
Yuma!
Trap activate! Overlay Buster!
Until the end of my Battle Phase, one monster on my field gains 500 ATK!
I end my turn.
So you somehow survived, huh? But it will be over next turn!
What should I do? If I take Gustav Max’s effect again, I'll lose!
Honestly speaking, it’s not easy to defeat Gustav Max's 3000 ATK.
But there is a way.
Huh? And what's that?
Did you forget about your new allies?
New?
That’s right!
I got me some new friends!
My turn, draw!
I summon Zubaba Knight!
Then flip summon Rai-Rider!
I overlay the LV3 Zubaba Knight and Rai-Rider!
I build the overlay network with these two monsters!
Xyz summon!
Come forth, my new friend!
Drumming Fiend Tententempo!
A Monster with 1000 DEF?
Check it out! Drumming Fiend, Tententempo’s monster effect activates!
By detaching one overlay unit, it can send all Overlay units from my opponent’s Xyz monster to the graveyard!
What?!
And for every overlay unit send to the graveyard by this effect, it gains 500 ATK!
Drumming Sonic!
Now Gustav Max can no longer activate its effect!
Plus Tententempo will not take battle damage when in defense mode.
I set 2 cards and end my turn!
How... How dare you!
I'll show you what happens when I get angry!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Equipment Magic from my hand, Mechanical Connection!
By removing 2 LV8 or higher Machine-type monsters in my graveyard from play, the equipped monster’s ATK doubles!
Doubles?!
6000 Attack Points?! Isn’t that even higher than Rocket Arrow?!
What destructive power she has!
Plus, due to Mechanical Connection’s effect, when the equipped monster attacks a monster in defense position,
it will inflict piercing damage to my opponent according to the difference!
That means, since Tententempo’s DEF is 1000, if it's attacked, I'll take 5000 damage?!
This match is about to end. Yuma, you're mine now!
Or are you gonna cry for forgiveness just like last time?
Cry for forgiveness?
I mean the time I took your card away!
C'mon, if you want your card back, climb on up here!
I beg you!
- Give it back to me!
-Y ou were crying non-stop since you didn’t know how to climb a tree.
Huh? Wasn't that...?
Did I ever do that?
Still playing dumb?!
I am not! If I don't remember it, I don't remember it!
Then I'll make you remember with these 6000 Attack Points!
Yuma, you have 500 Life Points. If that 6000 Attack Power hits you...
This isn't the time to say that!
But it would be fatal to her as well.
Huh?
Here I come, Yuma ! Here’s the final attack!
I see!
Go, Gustav Max! Attack Tententenpo!
Yuma!
Gustav Hammer!!
Yuma : Trap activate, Recklessness!
When a monster in defense position was attacked, this card changes it to attack position and continues the battle!
2200 ATK? You can't defeat Gustav Max with that!
I can defeat it like this! I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Trap activate, Holy Armor, Mirror Mail!
Until the end of battle phase, the attacked monster will have the ATK of the attacking monster!
Their Attack Points are the same!
What the?
Next, when the Trap card Recklessness destroys an opponent’s monster this way, it will inflict damage to my opponent equal to destroyed monster’s ATK!
What?!
Go, Recklessness’s effect! 6000 damage!
I did it!
I... lost?
But why!?
Because you abused those 6000 Attack Points of yours to defeat me when I only had 500 Life Points!
I-If you didn’t do that, you wouldn’t have received huge damage from Recklessness!
Damn it!
Um, this may not be the time to say this, but...
Isn't the boy you like, Anna, Yoya Tsukune, not Yuma?
Yuya Tsukune?
Ah, now I remember that guy.
He always cried like a little baby in the teacher’s office.
Gimme!
Stare~!
It's because your name's so easy to mix up!
In any case, I'll spare you this time.
Oh yeah! Hold it, you! Where's the Heart Piece?!
Heart Piece?
You lost, so you gotta leave that behind!
What are you talking about?
Didn't you come here to participate in the Duel Carnival?
Why would I participate in that?
Then say so in the first place!
God, what a troubling girl!
But I thought it was a little strange.
No one would ever like Yuma.
Huh?! What was that?!
But it's a bit of a shame.
I really wish to see that unique dueling again.
Forget that girl! I never wanna see her again!
Yuma Tsukumo, huh...?
I'll remember this, Yuma Tsukumo!
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
Vegetable Death Match?!
You cannot declare an attack without eating a vegetable. Some original rules, huh?
Are you saying I will represent the image of tomatoes?
Everything's turning into tomatoes!
Yuma, why aren’t you attacking?
The winning formula is completed. But…
I will be the one to crush your ambition!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Yuma’s Greatest Ordeal! Fight to Death: Vegetable Death Match!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Yuma’s dueling hasn’t improved a bit.
Yuma: what are you talking about? I'm already really good now!
Then show me some proof.
Alrighty, I Normal Summon Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
And that's your proof!?