Astral! Astral!
Where are you, Astral!
I cant do this alone, help me please.
Orbital brothers 5 and 6!
Push.
Wha- what is this?
It seems like we're not welcome here at all...
Gotcha!
Take this!
Yuma, go!
We'll keep them busy, you go on ahead!
But...
Good way to 'bring it to 'em, class rep!
Yuma, please go on!
Good luck, Yuma!
Everyone...
To summarize, I got you with that one!
Come and get me!
Now your life is less than half of mine.
What will you do now?
I set one card and end my turn.
What is it? Now I have you in a stalemate.
My turn! Draw!
I can't protect myself from Kaito...
Yuma, what would you do?
Darn! Open! Open up!
Quickly!
Go away!
You there, get them!
If it continues like this...
What is it? It's your turn.
The answer is obvious. You would 'bring it to 'em', Yuma.
I summon Zubaba Knight!
Then I send 1 card from my hand to the graveyard to special summon Fallen Cone.
Then I activate the magic card 'Drop Exchange'.
With this card, I send 2 or more monsters from my side of the field to the graveyard,
to special summon a monster from my hand whose level equals the sum of the levels of those monsters.
The Level 3 Zubaba Knight and Level 1 Fallen Pinecone are sent to the graveyard.
I now special summon Kagetokage!
This monster cannot be normal summoned, it can only be special summoned from my hand.
Two Level 4 monsters.
I overlay Gogogo Golem and Kagetokage!
With these 2 monsters I create the overlay network.
Xyz summon!
Appear, No. 39, Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Just hold on Astral! I'll save you for sure!
Hm? That's... Kaito!
The other... who is...?
This is...?
The contract with you will be continued.
Contract?
The one who opens this door will gain a new power.
However, in exchange he will lose his most important belonging.
But there are some interfering with the contract.
Ah?
Eliminate them with this power.
Go through this door and gain the power of ZeXal!
Only when you're ready.
ZeXal?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Numbers 24:
The soul of Xyz Summon! ZeXal!!!
So you've finally appeared, Numbers...
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope! Attack Photon Leo!
Hope Sword Slash!
You're so predictable with your foolish skills!
I activate a Trap! Armored Back!
If a monster equipped with an equip card was destroyed, this card allows me to revive that monster and its equip card!
Be revived, Photon Leo!
So you revived Photon Leo.
For Galaxy Eyes he needs 2 monsters with 2000 or more ATK.
Is it coming?
I set one card and end my turn!
ZeXal is it...?
I will not tolerate this any longer! I will put an end to you now!
Prepare yourself!
Aren't you that...?
Orbital 7 at your service!
Scrap!
Be at my mercy!
My turn!
Direct attack!
Oh!? Will you come out?!
It's our turn for a while..!
Will you be pulled out, please!
My turn! Draw!
I summon Photon Circler!
Photon Circler has 1000 Attack.
It cannot be used to special summon Galaxy Eyes.
Then how about this?
I activate the effect of the Photon Spear equipped to Photon Leo.
The monster equipped with Photon Spear will count as 2 tributes for a special summon.
Behold my soul!
The incarnation of light, descend! Galaxy eyes Photon Dragon!
So it finally appeared! Galaxy Eyes Photon Dragon!
Galaxy Eyes, attack Hope!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
I activate the effect of Galaxy Eyes!
When Galaxy Eyes battles, it can remove both monsters from play!
Now your field is empty!
Go, Photon Circler, direct attack!
When the battle phase ends, Galaxy Eyes and Hope will return to the field!
And due to Galaxy-Eyes effect, Hope's overlay units will be absorbed!
For every Overlay Unit absorbed, Galaxy-Eyes' attack will increase by 500!
An attack of 4000!
Then I activate the Quick-Play Magic from my hand, Galaxy-Strom!
This card destroys one Xyz Monster that doesn't have overlay units!
Disappear, Hope!
Trap activate, Xyz Reflect!
When a Xyz monster would be destroyed by a card effect,
That effect is negated, and it inflicts 800 damage to my opponent!
What?!
Hmph, not bad!
But this level of damage is nothing...
Don't your remember how powerless Hope is in front of Galaxy-Eyes?
Not yet, I haven't finished Bringing it to you yet!
My turn, draw!
Allow me to show you the true form of Hope!
When my Life Points are below 1000, I can use Hope as material for,
Chaos Xyz Change!
Show yourself, Chaos Numbers 39!
Power of Hope, the messenger who turns Chaos into light! Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
Impossible! A Chaos Numbers?!
I can't believe the Numbers actually have this kind of power...
But Galaxy-Eyes still has the higher attack!
My target isn't Galaxy-Eyes!
I activate the effect of Aspiring Emperor Hope Ray!
By detaching one overlay unit, during this turn, Hope Ray's attack increases by 500!
Overlay Charge!
And then, the attack of my opponent's monster decreases by 1000!
I choose Photon Circler!
This is...?
Go, Hope Ray!
Attack Photon Circler!
Hope King Chaos Slash!
Is it over?
What!?
What a shame.
The Photon Circler you destroyed has an effect, that halves the damage from when it was destroyed in battle.
So he survived that attack?
I set one card, and end my turn!
Now the tables have turned.
My turn, draw!
Disappear in front of Galaxy-Eyes!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
I activate my Trap! Clean Barrier-Clear Force-!
When my opponent's monster declares an attack, that monster's attack returns to its original value!
Galaxy Eyes' original attack is 3000,
Thus the damage I receive is only 500!
So the damage isn't fatal...
but you only have 400 Life Points left!
Even though Hope showed its true form, it will end the same nonetheless.
Yuma...
Ah! The Emperor's Key!
Kaito...I cannot defeat this man...
Yuma...
Farewell...
What? Is that...?
The Emperor's Key...
Astral! Astral!
Answer me!
This place...
Now enter the gate...
Enter the gate and acquire your new power!
But in exchange, you shall lose your most precious belonging!
Do you have that conviction?
ASTRAL!
Yuma! Yuma, is that you?
Yeah! Are you alright?
Has the duel already started?
Yuma, unfortunately my life points are already close to zero...
Alright, just you wait! I'll come to your side!
Wait Yuma,
This world is different from yours
I don't know, if it's safe for you to come here.
Also, this is my battle.
Astral, you idiot, I won't let you carry everything on your own!
You and I have the same ambitions!
It's ZeXal!
That's what the voice at the gate said!
I have to acquire the power of ZeXal.
But do you know what ZeXal is?
Do I know? What is ZeXal?
It's the miraculous power which saved my world.
But... in exchange for it, a person will lose his most precious belonging.
I'll get that power!
Astral, in order to save you, I don't care what price I have to pay!
I'LL BRING IT TO 'EM!
Yuma...I...
MY TURN!
I...I construct the overlay network with myself and Yuma!
It's the moment for two seperate souls to crossover! Now the legendary power will come forth!!
Come, Yuma!
Lets bring it to 'em!
Xyz Change ZeXal!
What's...going on?
Wha...what is? This is...me?
And my power!
ZeXal!
This voice is from...Yuma Tsukumo!
You fused yourselves together?!
But you only have 400 Life Points left!
W-we can't do anything with that amount!
Lets win this, Yuma!
Everything depends on this draw!
Huh?
The strongest duelist will inevitably always create his duels through the cards he draws!
Concentrate your power, Yuma!
OK!
Let's go, Astral!
Take this! The Light! The Power! And combine yourselves on my right hand, to open the path toward Hope!
Shining Draw!!
Come forth! ZeXal Weapon!
Unicorn King Spear!
Unicorn King becomes an equip card for Hope Ray,
And increase Hope Ray's Attack by 1900!
Change! Unicorn Spear!
Now Hope Ray's attack far exceeds Galaxy Eyes!
His attack is 4400!
When Unicorn King Spear is equipped to Hope Ray, it negates the effects of an opponent's monster.
Your Galaxy-Eyes can't get away now!
Go! ZeXal Weapon! Unicorn Slash!
I activate my Trap! Photon Shock!
When I receive damage from a battle involving a photon monster, Photon Shock
deals the damage to both players!
What?!
Galaxy-Eyes!
Kaito... why are you collecting Numbers?
Why are you acting like the underling of the devil?
Hey, Kaito!
In order to save my brother, I had to sell my soul to the devil.
Your brother?
Don't tell me, that was...
Just what happened... to both of you?
I'll return this to you...
That's... Shark's soul!
Looks like you've woken up.
I... I'm...
It seems what Yuma said was true.
Yuma...
What are you guys doing?!
This doesn't look good!
Is everyone safe?
What's going on?
To summarise, just run for your lives!
Yeah!
But Yuma is still...
That guy's fine... believe in him!
Yuma... Yuma!
Eh... Wha- What is...?!
Yuma!
Yuma...
Yuma?!
Heh... Hey, Kotori!
Oooh, it's not just a 'hey', you're such an idiot!
You're still alive, Yuma!
Hahaha... of course I won't die...
Yuma!
I'm fine!
Yuma Tsukumo...
Kaito...
Yuma, there is something, I would like to ask.
What is it? Why are you so serious...
Yuma...what does that D on your T-shirt stand for?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
All of a sudden the time in our world has stopped, and there are 3 suns in the sky!
That sun.. should exist only in our world... don't tell me... Kaito!?
I am glad you are fine, Astral.
Tch! Something is messing with my memory!
Just...what is happening?
Yuma, we are reflecting the memory of our duels...
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
The Time has Come! The Emergence of 3 Suns!
Kattobingu da ze, ore!
What does that D on Yuma's T-shirt stand for?
Donkan
(Thickheaded)
Douheta
(Totally unskilled)
Dosukeba
(Totally goofy)
Douaho
(Totally Stupid)
Doudemoii
(Not Worth Worrying About)
Doukechi
(Cheapskate)
Dounimonaranai
(Helpless)
Dounimozannen
(Helpless Disappointment)
Du- Duel, that is what the 'D' stands for!