Congratulations to Kaito for his magnificent victory!
Now he will be the second semifinalist after Tron!
Only two positions remain open!
Who will advance and take those spots?!
I'm sure the hearts of all Dueling fans around the world are pumped!
Now, everyone, together with me!
Heart Burning!
If Tron and Dr. Faker are gonna use their own children as tools for revenge,
I won't forgive them!
Yuma, there is a strong resonance from the left side.
Resonance?
Is this the power of crests III and V had?
That must mean Tron's up ahead!
The probability is... high.
Okay! Let's go!
Now, this is the Magma Field!
Just who will come to this scorching hot field?!
It's Shark! He's so cool!
Geez, it won’t be fun without Yuma!
I finally caught you. You won't escape any longer!
Heh, you've got a terrible personality.
It's not like I was running away.
I was merely pretending so I could lure you here.
Right into this scorching hot Magma Field.
Because in this world of boiling hot fire,
you have the utmost disadvantage.
And that's because your deck is Water-Attribute based.
Your Monsters won't be able to survive long here.
Ah, IV-sama! I'm looking forward to your service today!
Service my butt. These guys don't know this guy's true personality.
IV's true personality... You mean...
He's a devil!
Duel!!
The first turn belongs to me!
My turn! Draw!
The Scorching Hot Magma Field, huh?
Don't take me lightly!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Plate Salvage!
Due to its effect, the Field Magic is negated for two turns!
Shark... And IV!
Yuma.
So he came.
But this is the Magma Field, isn't it?
It's not hot at all.
As expected of Shark.
It seems he stopped the Field Magic by using a Magic Card.
It's finally begun.
This is an important battle between IV and Ryouga.
Now, fight to your heart's content.
So I can confirm it with my own eyes.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
I Summon Tripod Fish!
Then, when there is a Fish-Type Monster on my field,
I can Special Summon this guy from my hand!
Come! Shark Sucker!
"Number 57: Shark Torpedoed!
The Nightmarish Fanservice"
He's got two Level Three Monsters!
Which means from the get go…?!
An Xyz Summon!
I Overlay the Level Three Tripod Fish and Shark Sucker!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Submersible Carrier Aero Shark!
I activate Aero Shark’s Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
it inflicts 400 damage to my opponent for each card in my hand!
I have three cards in my hand.
So that's 1200 points of damage!
Clever!
He gave his opponent Effect Damage on his first turn!
Shark is so awesome!
Yeah! Nice one, Shark!
To summarize, we're on your side here!
I set two cards face-down and end my turn!
Quite interesting that you were able to Summon an Xyz Monster in the very beginning.
It makes crushing you all the more rewarding!
My turn! Draw!
When there is no Monster on my field while you control an Xyz Monster,
I can Special Summon Gimmick Puppet Magne Doll from my hand!
Mag...net!
Then I Summon Gimmick Puppet Gear Changer!
This card can become the same level of a Gimmick Puppet on the field!
Gear Up!
Gear Changer!
Now IV has two Monsters with the same level as well.
Here it comes!
I Overlay the Level Eight Gimmick Puppet Magnet Doll and Gimmick Puppet Gear Changer!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 15!
Gimmick Puppet Giant Killer!
That's...!
He played it!
The Number that tormented Tetsuo and the Class Rep.
If you're going to come at me seriously, I'll return the gesture.
I'll show you the greatest fanservice there is!
What's that Monster?
IV-sama?
Whoops, what in the world?! What on earth is happening?!
During this fan-favorite, highly-anticipated showdown between Shark and IV,
What an accident to occur!
The anger in my heart is about to make it explode!
Heart Burning!
Is this their doing?
Sorry about that!
Since the following contents will be too inappropriate for people to watch,
I took the liberty of destroying all your cameras.
So, IV, send Ryoga to the abyss of darkness.
Force him to his knees!
I activate Gimmick Puppet Giant Killer’s Monster Effect!
It destroys Xyz Monsters on the field, and inflicts damage to my opponent equal to their total Attack Powers!
Oh crap!
Shark!
Then I attack directly with Gimmick Puppet Giant Killer!
I activate the Permanent Trap, Bubble Bringer!
This card can negate my opponent’s direct attack!
Phew…He just blocked that.
Oh well.
When my turn ends, Plate Salvage’s effect will vanish too.
You'll feel the scorching Hell next time!
I end my turn!
What the? Oh, hot!
It really is like a scorching Hell.
So this is the Field Magic, Magma Ocean!
Decide whether I'm showing off or not only after you watch my Duel!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Hammer Shark!
Then I activate Bubble Bringer’s effect!
By sending this card to the Graveyard,
in exchange, I Special Summon Tripod Fish from my Graveyard!
When it's Special Summoned successfully, Tripod Fish’s level is increased by one!
You fool!
Thanks to the Field Magic, Magma Ocean, when a Water-Attribute Monster is Summoned, it is destroyed!
You Monsters will never be able to survive here!
Eat this!
What?!
What happened?
It's a Trap Card.
It activated on Shark's field.
What's that?!
The Permanent Trap Card, Adapting to Adversity!
This card can negate the effects of Magic or Traps that destroys a Monster!
Now my Monsters can survive in this scorching Hell as well!
Amazing! That's Shark for you!
The spirit he's betting this match on is extraordinary.
IV… I was framed by you in the National Championships.
Then my younger sister, who had nothing to do with this, was also hurt by you!
I will never...
...forgive you!
I will defeat you using any means necessary!
Yuma, he's serious about this.
Don’t tell me Shark…
The Monster special summoned by Bubble Bringer’s effect
can be treated as two Xyz Materials!
I Overlay Tripod Fish, which is now treated as two, Xyz Materials and Hammer Shark!
I use these three Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 32!
Marine Biting Dragon - Shark Drake!
That's from before!
The Number!
Yes, the Number III gave Ryoga.
By my orders, mind you.
I've been waiting for this moment, Ryoga.
In order to spread the darkness in your heart even more!
That's III's...
I knew V and Tron were plotting something, but...
They actually utilized III to give this Number to Ryoga?!
Although I never told you that.
Tron...! Why?!
Well, if I told you, there was a chance you could leak our plan!
You've got a loose tongue, after all.
Everyone has their own role.
V has V's. III has III's.
And mine... What's my role?!
To beat Ryoga into the abyss of darkness!
Everything has been going well so far.
Just as I planned.
Cornering him to this degree,
And forcing him to Summon Shark Drake...
Are those in your plan too?!
That's right.
You could be in danger if you get careless.
You know the power of Ryoga and his Shark Drake well, don't you?
Ryoga's power?
Go! Shark Drake!
Attack Gimmick Puppet Giant Killer!
I then activate Shark Drake’s effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit,
it lowers the Attack Power of the Gimmick Puppet Giant Killer I just destroyed by 1000,
and Special Summons it to IV’s field!
Why would he return the opponent’s Monster?
Well, uh...
Shark Drake can attack the Monster Special Summoned by this effect once again.
And there you have it, Kotori.
Huh? What?
IV's only got 1500 Life left.
If this goes through, Shark wins!
I won't let you!
I Special Summon Gimmick Puppet Night Joker from my hand!
This card can be Special Summoned by banishing the Giant Killer in my Graveyard!
That sure was a close one!
But I admit your response in that moment was very impressive.
Now you can continue to fight.
Which means you can corner Ryoga even further!
You spared your life, IV. I'll end my turn there!
Look there! Ryoga's still into this!
You have to try harder!
I know that!!
Eh?
Who's IV... talking to?
I know that!
My mission is to beat Ryoga into the darkness of his heart!
For that, everything up until now...
Calumniating him in the tournament...
Heavily injured his younger sister...
Everything was for the sake of you, Tron!
I followed your orders this entire time!
Huh? Tron's orders?!
What's he mean?!
Are you here, Tron?! Hurry up and show yourself!
I'm right here.
You bastard!
Tron's over there?!
He's probably using some kind of power
to allow only one person to sense his presence.
Bingo! I'd expect no less from you, Astral.
Tron! What is your aim?
Cornering Shark...
Beating the darkness out of his heart...
What are you doing it all for?!
Since there is no need to hide anything,
I will just answer everyone.
The reason I decided to beat Ryouga’s heart into the darkness
is so I can manipulate him.
And use him as an assassin to go after Dr. Faker.
Assassin?!
Stop joking! I'm not interested the least bit in doing that!
Even you don’t want to, you can’t escape anymore!
You will become my puppet to manipulate.
My own personal doll.
Me and my brothers fought with all we had for your sake, Tron!
So why are you not after us...
No, why are you after Ryoga and not us?!
I can't accept that!
Like I told you, everyone has their own role.
When it comes to defeating Dr. Faker, Ryoga is far more...
I won't accept it! I will never accept that!
I will defeat Dr. Faker!
Not a guy like him!
I'll show you that I'm strong enough to do it!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card from my hand, Puppet Ritual!
This card can call a “Gimmick Puppet” Monster from my Graveyard back to my field!
Come, Gimmick Puppet Magne Doll!
I Overlay the Level Eight Gimmick Puppet Night Joker and Gimmick Puppet Magne Doll!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 40!
Gimmick Puppet Heaven’s Strings!
Then I activate the Equip Magic from my hand, Destiny Strings!
And I equip it to Gimmick Puppet Heaven’s Strings!
By sending a card from my deck to the Graveyard,
if that card is a Monster Card,
the equipped Monster can attack up to the same number of that Monster’s level,
without destroying your Monster!
The one I drew is the Level Eight Gimmick Puppet Necro Doll!
Thus it can attack Shark Drake eight times!
What'd he say?!
He can attack eight times in a row?!
Do it, Heaven's Strings!
Heaven's Blade!!
Shark!
According to Destiny String’s effect,
without destroying the Monster, it can attack consecutively and inflict damage!
Continue, Heaven’s Strings!
Torment Shark Drake nice and good!
Suffer! Suffer even more, Ryoga!
He can't...
Stop it! This isn't a Duel!
Dueling does not exist for rage and revenge!
I will not let you interfere.
I can't move!
Yuma!
The entertainment is just getting started from here on out, after all.
Be a good boy and watch from over there.
No! Stop already!
Dueling is something that makes people happy!
Keep suffering, Ryoga...
Suffer, suffer more, and agonize before falling into Hell!
This is the fifth attack!
As long as they Duel, everyone can become fiends, or even companions!
Hurting each other isn't Dueling at all!
Become friends with everyone, eh?
You really are just like him.
Like Kazuma Tsukumo.
Tron...!
He did say that pretty often too. Something like “friendship” and “making people happy”.
I-If you all didn't get my father involved into this in the first place…!
Yuma...
The one who took your father away from you is Dr. Faker.
If you have anyone to hate, it should be Faker.
Doing so, the darkness will be born inside your heart.
Then it will spread.
I did promise you, after all, that I will eat your heart out next time.
Stop joking! I won’t forgive you!
You're the one who made Droite suffer!
And you're the one who used III and V as tools for revenge!
Not bad. The darkness in your heart is growing.
The hatred will amplify that darkness. Feel free to hate.
And Dr. Faker!
Shut your mouth!
Now here comes the last one!
How was it, Ryoga?
But it isn't over yet!
I activate Gimmick Puppet Heaven’s Strings’ Monster Effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it places a String Counter on Shark Drake!
When next turn ends, Shark Drake will be destroyed,
and you will take damage equal to its original Attack Power.
Then we'll have a true farewell!
I'll end my turn with that!
Shark...
Shark! Answer me!
Hey, you can hear me, can't you, Shark?!
Shark!
Shark... can't be...!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
Although he was heavily injured, Shark stands and continues to fight!
But IV’s onslaught is still ongoing mercilessly.
Under these overwhelmingly disadvantaged circumstances,
the only method left for victory is…
IV’s trump? Don’t tell me…!
Why would you give power to him?
Tron, you bastard!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Shark Awakens! A New Chaos Number Appears"
No, Shark, stop it!
Today we'll be introducing Number 32, Shark Drake!
It can attack the Monster is just defeated.
Quite shark-like to not let its prey escape.
What's wrong, Yuma?
We ran out of time before I could explain the gag!