Robin!
To save the people of this world,
Today is also a banquet of justice!
Different Dimension ESPer Robin, here I come!
Crossing over from a far away dimension,
Idid it in order to defeat you!
Robin!
You dare to defy our master, King of Darkness Dead Max?
How courageous of you!
My justice is without limits!
Surprise Punch!!
Could this be? Galaxy Queen's true form is...
The one I always searched for, my mother...
Robin! Dead Max's curse shall be placed upon you!
And now, all of you will follow my orders.
Be quiet!
Geez... people are trying to sleep here.
Yuma! Yuma!
What is it?
That boy Robin, it seems like he came from a different dimension, just like me.
Hah? What are you talking about? That's TV.
TV?
Like I said, that's live action!
Live action?
In any case, he is...
So annoying!
Fine, you can keep watching.
"Next time - The heated final battle! Robin is forever!"
Al--right!!
And now it's time to bring it to 'em!
Who should I duel with, I wonder?
Yuma.
Let's go home.
But why?
Today, I must affirm Robin's fate with my own eyes.
Ha?!
If he really came from another dimension,
Then maybe, there's a good chance he'll know something about my lost memories.
Again, what are you talking about?
Like I said, that's just a live action!
Hey hey Yuma! Have you heard!?
What is it?
Robin is coming over to our area!
What?
They are coming to a set by the shoreline to shoot some scenes!
Ha...
We should go check it out.
This terrible feeling is unbearable...
Aahh, Robin-sama!
Imust go meet Robin as well!
Robin is great and everything,
But I'm gonna go duel...
Let's go, Yuma!
But I was gonna duel...!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Here comes Different Dimension ESPer Robin!!
However, his true self is...!?
This guy is super popular...
"Numbers 7: Banquet of Justice!
Here comes ESPer Robin!!"
Robin-sama!
At this rate, we won't meet him at all...
Everyone, got a problem~ura?
These kind of things, you can leave it to me~ura!
Everything in this world has its hidden ways~ura.
Acting nervous like an outsider, this will only make you seem more suspicious~ura.
But if you walk in freely, you'll look just like one of them~ura!
Ah-- Hard day of work~ura!
Last night was sushi at Roppongi~ura.
Then it's off to get rich at the Ginza midnight reservation~ura.
What are you talking about?
Like I said! Good sushi, free taxi!
Now!
Aah, unbelievable!
That Robin is really here...
Prepare yourself!
King of Darkness, Dead Max!
That voice... It's Robin!
He's here... Robin's here!
It's the real deal!
King of Darkness Dead Max.
Today we will settle this once and for all!!
King of Darkness Dead Max...
Could that be my enemy...?
Watch out, Yuma!
That's one of Dead Max's servants!
That's just a costume.
Costume...?
This stuff is all made up.
Yuma!
You can fly in the sky?
No matter how you look at it-- of course I can't fly!
I'm falling! Aah--!
Oh no!
You all! Just how the heck did you get in here?
Now, come with me to the guard office!
You're a duelist, aren't you?
This is your deck, isn't it?
Huh? What the...
Oh man! That was close!
I can't believe I dropped my deck case...
The life of the duelist was...
Unbelievable!
Thank you! You totally saved me!
No need to thank me.
However, I have a request for you.
Request?
Please, join me in a grand banquet of dueling!
So you like to duel?
Yeah, a little bit.
In that case let's do it right now!
Really!?..
...no, I mean..
Do you really mean it?
Yeah!
I'm Tsukumo Yuma!
Let's hurry up and duel...
Yuma. Aside from dueling right now,
Ask him if he knows anything about me.
Like I said, he doesn't know anything about you!
What's wrong?
T-T-That thing!
It's only a spider...
I...I'm terrible at dealing with bugs...
You are?
Hurry, please do something about that spider!
Huh? Where's Yuma?
Everything's fine now.
You saved me...
Thank you...
What's with you anyways?
The great ally of justice is afraid of spiders?
All of this...
It's just a fantasy that everyone made up.
My true self is neither powerful nor courageous, compared to Robin.
I'm just a cowardly person who can't even stand spiders.
However, this image that I've created...
To tell the truth, I'm fed up with it.
Everyday, I play out the Robin you see on TV...
However...
There's no one out there that truly understands me.
Not really sure what's going on, but...
Wouldn't it be great to just let out your true self?
You mean it?
Thank you!
You're the first person to ever say that to me!
Hey you, won't you be my friend?
My name is Fuya Okudaira.
Fuya?
Of course, Fuya!
Hurry up, let's have a duel to our friendship!
Robin!
That child, who is it?
Mother...
Mother !?
Didn't I tell you to not talk to any unrelated outsiders?
That's... Galaxy Queen...
I-I understand, mother...
No, you don't get it!
If you keep exposing yourself to your fans like that,
You'll end up ruining your hard-earned image!
Think about all the hardship I went through to make you a star!
It's best for you to live your life protecting Robin's image.
Come now, please leave us alone.
H-Hey..!
If you tell anyone that you've met Fuya,
I'll sue you for trespassing!
Wait a sec! Let me go!
Please leave!
Come, hurry up!
Yuma!
Fuya! We're friends, aren't we!
That's why,
One day we'll duel for sure!
It's fine...
There's no chance to keep that kind of promise...
No one can save me from this...
Somehow, being a star is pretty terrible...
Just what in the world does this mean?
Why is Robin also named Fuya?
Robin isn't Fuya, it's not like that!
Fuya is suppose to be Robin.
What?
Like I said, Robin is just a live action.
Characters from TV shows don't exist in real life.
In that case, was I deceived?
That's just Fuya playing as Robin.
Playing...
Then, about my memories...
Like I said, he really doesn't know anything about you!
I see...
Huh? What is it?
Are you disappointed?
I mean, do you feel kind of lonely?
What do you mean by lonely?
Lonely means that,
You're feeling pain from being alone by yourself.
Alone by yourself...
Then, is Fuya also in pain?
He was crying out for help.
No one can save me from this...
What's this? You little...
If you're gonna throw empty cans around like it's nothing...
Later you might be one of King of Darkness Dead Max's servants!
Huh?
Take this! This is the banquet of justice!!
What's wrong with you? You punk!
Since you were planning to run over that kitten,
You must be a servant of King of Darkness Dead Max!
Take this! This is the banquet of justice!!
According to eye witnesses,
They said it was the works of popular TV series main character, ESPer Robin.
Was it the real Robin that did all this?
All of this is just slander.
Robin would never do anything like that!
Agreed!
Robin would never do anything like that.
Like I said, why do I have to come too?
Did you want me to patrol all by myself?
With this, we will clear Robin's name once and for all!
Without a doubt, that guy is Robin's imposer.
That's right...
A timid guy like that...
What are you saying?
No, I mean... I-It's nothing...
Over there!
Are you alright?
Yuma!
Wait a sec!
You...
Yuma?
Mind your own business.
Where's the culprit?
No... I lost him.
That's without a doubt Fuya himself.
Just what in the world happened to him?
Why would a guy like him...
Those kind of things...
Find out the truth for yourself, Yuma.
Find out for myself...
But how?
By carrying out your promise to Fuya.
Duel with Fuya.
He is looking for a duel.
A duel is a sacred ceremony.
As duelists, you'll understand each other through a duel.
No one can save me from this...
Yeah. You're right!
The one who can save Fuya is...
...none other than you.
Fuya.
Acting like Robin and all that, what are you trying to do?
So you came, Yuma.
Even when I told you to stay out this...
You...
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
I've got to live up to my mother's expectations.
Your mother?
King of Darkness Dead Max and his followers...
All must be eliminated...
Fuya...?
Because I am, for real...
I'm the real Different Dimension ESPer Robin!
Yuma!
Do you still not understand?
Iam truly the one and only Different Dimension ESPer Robin!
It's best for you to live your life protecting Robin's image.
You...
So is this your conclusion?
What do you mean by that, Yuma?
That guy... He thinks he's become the real Robin!
What?!
So you mean that his soul didn't return from the world of live action?
You're right...
The guy must have been suffering the entire time!
I'll swing down the holy sword and uphold my banquet of justice!
Stop this, Fuya!
Yuma, why do you stand in my way?
I see. You must also be one of King of Darkness Dead Max's servants!
Fuya...
No, Robin!
Duel with me!
I 'll open your eyes!
I accept, Yuma!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
I'm bringin' to ya!!
My bringing it to 'em?! Or your banquet?!
Duel!!
Robin is...
The seal of the Numbers?!
The Numbers have grown the darkness within his heart!
Why do you always have to bring trouble with you wherever you go?!
I'm up! My turn!
Draw!
I summon Beastial Warrior Puman!
Be careful, Yuma.
Puman is Robin's teacher and holds the ability to call forth to him with his sword.
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Here goes!
My turn! Draw!
I summon Gogogo Golem!
Go!
Gogogo Golem!
Attack Puman!
Gogogo Blow!!
Trapped you!
Trap, activate!
Trion Barrier!
If I have three Tri-Star Trions in my hand,
this card can force an attacking Monster into Defense Mode!
I can then Special Summon three Tri-Star Trions!
Come, Tri-Star Trions!
It's the banquet of Special Summoning!
Three at once?!
I set one card and end my turn!
My turn!
Draw!
I release two of the Tri-Star Trions for an Advance Summon!
Come out, Different Dimension Esper Star Robin!
An Advance Summon!?
Advance Summon...
You release Monsters on your field to call forth a powerful Monster.
Moreover, Star Robin requires the release of two Monsters.
It's an extremely powerful Monster, at Level 10.
And then, I activate the effect of the third Tri-Star Trion!
When Trion is used as the material for the release of an Advance Summon,
I can negate their Monster Effects and Special Summon them onto the field!
It's the banquet of Trion's revival!
After, I activate Space Ration from my hand!
This card only activates its effects when there's a Different Dimension Esper Star Robin on my field!
Its effect allows me to draw two cards from my deck!
I'll then Overlay my three Level One Trions!
I construct the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
Exceed Summon!
Come forth, Number 83!
Galaxy Queen!!
The Numbers appeared!
Galaxy Queen!
It's the powerful enemy sorcerer fighting against Robin's team!
I equip Galaxy Queen with the Equipment Magic, Cursed Seal of Dead Max!
This card makes it so that Galaxy Queen's Battle Position can't be changed.
And she cannot be destroyed, no matter what!
Finally, by using one Overlay Unit,
Galaxy Queen's effect activates!
Galaxy Queen, along with the other Monsters on my field, become immortal until the end of my turn.
And that attack gains the power of Piercing Damage!
Now, I shall grant you all my power!
All the Monsters take Piercing Damage...?
This is bad!
If Gogogo Golem is attacked and the Defense Power is lower than the Attack Power...
...you will take damage.
Go, Beastial Warrior Puman!
Black Slash!!
Once per turn, if Gogogo Golem is in Defense Mode, it's not destroyed in battle!
But you still take Piercing Damage!
Go, Star Robin!
It's the banquet of justice!
Surprise Punch!!
I set a card face-down!
Turn end!
It would appear that your bringing it to 'em is far superior to my banquet!
Not yet...!
My bring it to 'em doesn't end here!
Let's start the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
Each turn, you're able to Normal Summon how many Monsters?
One? Two? Or maybe three?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Robin... No, Fuya!
This Number is the curse of your mother!
It's causing you pain and suffering!
Isn't that what you feel in your heart?!
He was lonely.
Yuma, I brought his mother!
8000 Attack Points!?
The pieces of our victory have been gathered!
Let's win!
I'm definitely gonna break your curse!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Star Robin is Forever"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
And the answer is...
Just one!
However, if you use the effects of Magics, Traps and Monster Effects...
you can Summon three Monsters at once!