Duel cleared.
Duel cleared. Now unlocking.
Cleaning. Cleaning.
Cleaning. Cleaning. Cleaning.
C'mon, hurry it up!
Returning. Returning.
Shoot!
What?!
Shit!
Introducing the staff of the World Duel Carnival!
Shoot, I totally didn't bring it to that test today!
I wonder if you even can "bring it" to a test?
I always bring it to everything!
What's wrong?
Did you stray away from your mother?
An O-Bot?
What's it doing over there?
Is it broken?
It looks like these little guys are trying to tell us something.
Wh-What the?!
So we saved their mother?
Thank goodness.
Say, Yuma...
Maybe we should help this O-Bot?
Don't be ridiculous!
Let's see... This goes with that...
This cord, maybe?
Yuma, are you sure about that?
Nope. No clue.
Yuma, try connecting the interior cord.
So I just gotta connect these two?
Why don't you try using this?
Guess it's worth a try.
Garbage. Garbage. Garbage. Garbage.
Let go!
Well, it's gotta be fixed, since it's picking up trash now.
Don't just stand there, you guys!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Y-You...
"Numbers 21:
Yuma vs Trashbot Obomi!:
Irritate.
It followed us here! My god!
My god.
Since it's here, maybe you should look after it.
Gimme a break!
I'm busy Dueling!
I don't got time for this-
Duel.
What?!
You really wanna Duel?!
But wait. Do you even got a deck?
Duel.
I activate the Magic Card, When You Wish Upon A Star.
When I have two Monsters on the field with equal Attack Power and Defense Power,
this card allows me to select one of the Monsters and change their level to the other's.
I change the level of Rubbishrobo Kettaroo to the same Level Four as Rubbishrobo Cyclacooda.
I Overlay the Level Four Rubbishrobo Kettaroo and Rubbishrobo Cyclacooda.
I use these two Monsters to construct the Overlay Network.
Xyz Summon.
Come out. Wind-Up Panzer Zenmaister.
I use Zenmaister to Direct Attack Yuma.
That was amazing, Bot!
You suck. You suck.
What was that?!
Yuma, the Dueling tactics of this machine far surpass your own.
You're really strong!
What?
Gosh...
But it looks kinda happy.
Could this O-Bot be... a girl?
This O-Bot is?
I feel sorry for this O-Bot!
Let's give her a name!
O-bo...
What do you think about "Obomi the Shining Robot"?
The hell's that?
Oh, come on!
Let's just stick with Obomi! Obomi's fine!
Obomi. Obomi.
Looks like she's taken a liking to you, Yuma.
Yuma. Yuma. Yuma.
C'mon, I've got enough issues carrying Astral around with me.
Carry Obomi. Carry Obomi.
Good night, Obomi.
Ive finished preparations.
This time we're gonna clean them out, my dear O-Bots.
Obomi!
Man, where'd she go off to?
What the heck?
She went star gazing or what?
I'm home...
Another jewelry theft?!
I was so gonna nail him this time!
Hold it, Yuma.
You're helping me with this.
What do you want all of a sudden?
Jewelry theft?
I finally managed to debunk one of the images taken by the security cameras that was shown on the local news station.
But I can't really make much of this.
That's...
Could that be... Obomi?
The culprit's a Dueling genius.
He's been able to break through countless security timed Duels at different locations.
I see. If Obomi's the culprit, it comes as no surprise that their Dueling tactics would be this advanced.
Did Obomi really...?!
It took about 17 minutes before the police were notified of the incident.
The criminal will likely not show himself before then.
So then...
If we arrive at the scene of the crime 17 minutes before it occurs,
there is a high probability that we will catch the criminal in the middle of his heist.
I see!
H-Hey! Yuma!
Got another member in the crew tonight!
I never would have imagined that the O-Bot I used during the jewelry theft would come back.
No one even noticed-
Gimme a break!
Who the hell are you people?!
Shut it! Just what the hell are you making our Obomi do?!
Obomi who?
What're you talking about?
This is my loyal slave!
You're wrong!
Obomi's our friend!
So give Obomi back!
Hey you, go and eliminate them.
Hey, Obomi!
Don't you remember us?
Obomi...
Obomi!
Did Obomi really forget about us?
Yuma...
Obomi, let's Duel!
Duel. Duel target confirmed.
Preparing to Duel.
Yuma, do you have a plan or something?
Not sure...
But maybe with this card...
Obomi, I'm gonna make you remember us during this Duel for sure!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
Yuma...
The first move is mine!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Gagaga Magician!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
My turn. Draw.
I play Eco Magic ~Stop Littering!
This card banishes two Rubbishrobo Monsters from my deck.
I can then add one Rubbishrobo into my hand.
I Summon Cyclacooda.
Also, I activate the Magic Card, Eco Magic ~Re-usable!
This card lets me Special Summon the two Banished Rubbishrobos onto the field.
I Special Summon Rubbishrobo Cleanaga...
...and Persokong.
She going for it?!
I Overlay the three Level Four Rubbishrobos!
I construct the Overlay Network using these three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come out, Recycle Rewrhinobot!
Recycle Rewrhinobot, attack Gagaga Magician!
Yuma!
I know!
Trap, activate!
Half Unbreak!
It makes a Monster on my field undestroyable,
and halves the damage the player would receive!
So Obomi really forgot about us...?
I swear I'm gonna make you remember, Obomi!
My turn!
Draw!
I'm Summoning a new friend of mine!
Come!
Gagaga Girl!
Gagaga-senpai!
Gagaga!
And an Equipment Magic!
I equip the Wonder Wand to Gagaga Girl!
This card increases the Attack Power of a Spellcaster-Type Monster by 500 points!
Well done. We've gathered our pieces to victory.
I activate Gagaga Magician's effect!
Until the End Phase, I can change Gagaga Magician's level from four to eight!
But why, Yuma?!
Then another Magic Card!
I activate Gagaga Thunder!
This card targets one Gagaga Monster I control.
It inflicts 300 points of damage to my opponent equal to the difference in their levels!
Gagaga Magician's a Level Eight and Gagaga Girl's a Level Three, so the difference is five!
So that's 1500 points of damage!
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
At the End Phase, Gagaga Magician's level goes from eight back to four.
But why, Yuma?!
Gagaga Girl has the effect to reduce the Attack Power of an opponent's non-Xyz Monster to zero!
And if you changed the level of Gagaga Magician to three instead of eight,
you could have Xyz Summoned Leviath Dragon.
If you attacked the zero Attack Power Rewrhinobot, you could have won!
Just winning isn't enough!
Obomi!
My turn. Draw.
I Summon Rubbishrobo Kettaroo.
I activate Rewrhinobot's effect!
I can detach one of its Overlay Units to increase the Attack Power of another Monster by 500 points.
Crap!
I detach three Overlay Units.
I raise Kettaroo's Attack Power up 500 points!
It's got 2300 Attack Points?!
First, I use Rewrhinobot to attack Gagaga Girl!
Trap Card, open!
Gagaga Guard!
When I control two or more Gagaga Monsters,
a Gagaga can't be destroyed during this turn!
I then use Kettaroo to attack Gagaga Magician.
Gagaga Guard, protect Gagaga Magician!
Yuma!
What in the world are you thinking?!
Once again... I have to play that Duel out once again...!
You aren't...!
Are you trying to recreate the Duel you had with Obomi before?!
Come back to me, Obomi!
The two of us will have fun Dueling together again!
Obomi!!
Come back to your senses, Obomi!
I... activate... effect... of... Rewrhinobot.
When I have no Xyz Material during the End Phase,
I can destroy the Monster with the lowest Attack Power on my field.
And both players take the original Attack Power of the destroyed Monster as damage.
Yuma, if she activates that effect next turn, both of your Life Points will drop to zero.
I won't let it end like this.
Not until she plays that card!
It's near time...
...for its switch to trigger.
Wh-What the?!
Detonation Program launched. Detonation Program launched.
In one minute, the program will end and you with it.
Wh-What's going on here?!
Obomi's gonna explode?!
The only way to avert this is to get Obomi to cancel the program herself in just one minute.
One minute...?
Yuma, it all depends on your next turn.
On my draw...?
I'm gonna being it to 'er!
Draw!!
It's here!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand! When You Wish Upon A Star!
When there are two Monsters on my field with the same Attack or Defense,
I can make both of their levels the same as the one I choose!
I change Gagaga Girl's level to match Gagaga Magician, a Level Four!
You... you...
You... you... you...
You... suck...
That's it, Obomi! Come back to us!
Obomi!
I get it! Yuma's remaking the Duel he had with Obomi to get her to remember us!
You suck. You suck.
Awright!
Obomi!
Obomi's still not free?!
Then we'll try it once again!
I Overlay the Level Four Gagaga Magician and Gagaga Girl!
- Yes!!
- Yeah!!
I use the two Monsters to construct the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come out, Numbers 39!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Yuma!
Obomi!
I activate Gagaga Girl's effect!
When Gagaga Girl is used to construct the Overlay Unit with Gagaga Magician,
she can reduce the Attack Power of one of the opponent's Xyz Monsters to zero!
I bring Rewrhinobot's Attack Power to zero!
Obomi, I'm gonna save you right now!
Hope Sword Slash!!
Obomi!
Yuma, you suck.
You suck.
- You did it!
- Great job!
- Yes!
- I did it!
Shit! That damn shabby robot!
It is all right.
Huh?
We already have the backup bombs set up.
- Ready.
Y-You guys are all idiots!
The criminal responsible for the consecutive jewelry theft incidents has been taken into custody outside Sakuyami.
How annoying~!
That was supposed to be my scoop!
I'm off!
Yuma. Duel Lunch.
Duel Lunch.
Whoa!
Now I'm gonna own in the Duels today!
Yuma, you suck. You suck.
Hey! Stop it!
I do not suck!!
Let's begin the Duel!
Here's this week's quiz!
What do you call the Summoning method that uses two or more Monsters of the same level?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Numbers Hunter Kaito!
He's finally appeared at my school!
Who could have done something like this?
It's gone... The Lord's Key is gone!
The Lord's Key was stolen?!
Astral's inside of it!
Yuma!
Why is Shark Dueling Kaito?!
The power of ZeXal...!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Stolen Lord's Key! They Clash - Kaito VS Shark"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is... Xyz Summon!
You're free to Xyz Summon when you collect two or more Monsters of the same level on the field.
Everyone should Xyz Summon to play powerful Monsters!