And in the end, it finally appears in front of us…!
What a ridiculously large Monster!
This Dyson Sphere is a space fortress
capable of engulfing the sun.
That ability is unmatchable!
Kaito, all of your attacks will be useless!
Impossible...! You're saying I can't attack it?
That is right. When Dyson Sphere has Overlay Units attached to it,
it is able to negate all of my opponent's attacks.
So that's why my attack didn't go through?
But now I know its effect!
Don't be so sure of that.
I know exactly what you are thinking.
Because the one who taught you how to Duel...
...was me, after all.
V was Kaito's teacher?!
When Tron... No, when my father went missing...
...my family was split apart.
My younger brothers were taken
to an orphanage as such a young age.
In order to investigate the truth behind my father's disappearance,
I stayed with Dr. Faker.
And that is when I met you brothers.
When I watched you brothers...
I may have very well saw myself and my brothers in you.
And you wished to be stronger.
You wanted to acquire the power to protect your brother.
Thus, I taught you about Dueling.
However, I never expected that I would battle you again in this manner.
But if you are trying to get in my way,
I will not show you any mercy!
Kaito…
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
I set one card and end my turn!
My turn. Draw!
"Number 56: The Great Decisive Battle of Outer Space!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Strikes Back"
I know...
What you are thinking.
Dyson Sphere's Attack Power is 2800.
However, Galaxy-Eyes' Attack Power is 3000.
Therefore, you think I won’t declare an attack, right?
But it seems you still aren't completely aware of Dyson Sphere’s second ability!
Second ability?!
I activate Dyson Sphere's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, it can attack directly!
What?!
A direct attack with 2800 Attack Points?!
If that attack connects… Kaito will…!
Kaito-sama!
Trap, activate! Photonize!
When there is a Light-Attribute Monster on my field,
my opponent’s attack is negated,
and my Light Monster’s Attack Power will increase equal to the Attack Power of my opponent’s attacking Monster!
So he utilized the opponent’s direct attack to his own advantage.
It’s useless. I have already foreseen your Dueling.
Trap, activate! Space Gate!
What?!
When there is a Dyson Sphere on the field, it can negate the activation of my opponent’s Trap Card and destroy it!
Take it, Kaito!
The pain I suffered from Dr. Faker, and my grudge against him for tearing my family apart!
Kaito!
Kaito-sama!
I can’t believe that Kaito… is being beaten this badly!
This man's Dueling...
...is scarily flawless!
You only have 200 of your Life remaining.
This match has already been decided.
Give up, Kaito.
You cannot defeat me!
Stand up, Kaito!
If you collapse over here, what will happen to Haruto?
Haruto...
Kaito!
Shut up!
I don’t need your sympathy!
Wha...?!
That’s right! Shut your mouth, Foolma!
What the heck?! Yuma may be an idiot, but he isn't some foolish pig!
Note: Tonma is an Asian pun used to call someone an idiot. It comes from the word "ton", which means pig.
Eh?!
Look, you...
How surprising, Yuma, that you actually treat Kaito as an ally.
Kaito is the son of Dr. Faker, the one who betrayed Kazuma-san!
And most importantly, he is a Numbers Hunter!
If Kaito survives, then that means…
One day you will be hunted by him as well!
Of course I know that!
But I once had a Duel with Kaito.
Therefore, no matter how he thinks, he is my friend!
And my goal too!
Friend, you say?
Kazuma-san did treasure that as well.
But, that ideal was completely wrecked and betrayed by Dr. Faker!
Can you forgive...that kind of person’s son?!
When I realized all of the truth, I…
Chris!
Please wait! Wait!
Where are you... Where are you going?
Chris!
Chris...
Enough of this nonsense!
I will defeat you and recover your Number!
In the end, you do not understand our hatred in the least, it seems.
Shut up! My turn! Draw!
Dyson Sphere...
It can negate attacks, and is able to attack directly!
Although at first glance that effect seems invincible...
But there is a way.
I see it! Dyson Sphere’s weakness!
I activate the Magic Card, Overlay Break!
This card can send all Overlay Units to the Graveyard,
and that Monster now changes to “can be destroyed by battle”!
I expected no less from Kaito.
Huh? What? What happened?
Dyson Sphere can only negate battles when it has Overlay Units.
Because of Kaito’s Magic card,
Dyson Sphere’s invincible effect is negated.
Plus, even the effect of “only Numbers can be destroy Numbers” is negated too!
I-I get it!
Now Dyson Sphere has become a huge pile of scrap!
Go, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
I already expect that move as well.
I activate another effect of Dyson Sphere!
What?!
When Dyson Sphere is attacked while it has no Overlay Units,
it can recover Overlay Units from Graveyard!
At this moment, I activate Dyson Sphere’s first effect!
When it has Overlay Units, my opponent’s attack will be negated!
It’s futile, Kaito.
No one is capable off destroying Dyson Sphere!
Kaito's Life has fallen to 200.
When next turn comes…
I...
...set one card and end my turn.
My turn. Draw!
It's coming...!
A direct attack!
I activate the Equipment Magic, Gravity Blaster!
What?!
Once per turn, this card can increase equipped Monster’s Attack Power by 400,
plus it can negate my the opponent's Monster’s effects!
Why didn't he attack directly?!
Why would V do that?
Kaito, you should know the reason.
Mere victory won't be enough.
My true victory will only determined when I crush Galaxy-Eyes , your embodiment!
Get moving, Dyson Sphere!
Galaxy-Eyes!
Kaito!
Trap, activate! Mirror Shade!
By halving my Life, this card can negate the damage I received!
Kaito-sama!
It's impossible! There is no way he can win this!
Kai…Kaito…is going to lose?
Kaito's Life is 100.
V's Life remains untouched.
Even for Kaito, under these circumstances…
Kaito, it's very painful, isn't it?
Unbearable, isn't it?
But that's enough already.
With this, you can release yourself from all kinds of suffering.
Whether it's the mission as a Numbers Hunter, or the pain brought by Haruto…
This is the final act of pity I can give you.
You're wrong...
Until now, not even for a single moment...
...did I ever consider Haruto as my pain!
He's… Haruto is my everything!
He's my reason for living!
Kaito...
He has always given me hope!
I won’t give up.
Not on myself or on Haruto!
Very well. Come at me!
My turn. Draw!
This is...! This card is...!
This card will...
...save me?!
Haruto...
This is my fate...
I...
...activate the Magic Card, Feelings Towards the Future!
What?! What’s that card?!
I…I can’t believe you have a card I don't know!
A card like that...
...was in your deck?
Regardless of how much you may know about me,
there's no way you can know about this card.
Because this card is the only one in my life my father gave me!
Kaito’s father…Dr. Faker gave him that?
Until now, I haven’t used this card even once.
Absurd... You hate your father so much...
And yet you put that card in your deck?!
Why would you ever do something like that?!
It's obvious!
It's obvious, isn't it?!
Anyone would want to protect their family, no matter who they are!
Just like you guys wish to protect your own family!
That’s why Kaito will always hold that card,
because he has hope for his own family!
Hope for his family?
That's why Kaito-
Shut up!
I don’t need you to speak for my heart.
Magic card, Feelings Towards the Future!
This card can Summon three Monsters with different levels from my Graveyard!
Revive, Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
And Photon Slasher! Photon Pirate!
But Monsters Special Summoned by this effect will have their Attack Power changed to zero!
It’s meaningless, Kaito! Their Attack Points are zero!
Plus, they're different levels. What good can they do?
Is that really the case?
What?
I activate the Magic Card, Shift Down!
This card can change all levels of Monsters on my field,
all to be the same of the Monster with highest level!
I raise all Monsters’ Level to eight!
What?!
I Overlay the Level Eight Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon, Photon Slasher, and Photon Pirate!
I use these three Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Great Galaxy of Reversal!
Become the rolling waves of light and show your mighty form!
Descend, my very soul!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
At this moment, I activate the effect of Field Magic, Cosmic Frontier!
When I Xyz summon successfully, I can draw one card!
It's here!
I activate Neo Galaxy Eyes' effect!
Photon Howling!
When Neo Galaxy-Eyes is Xyz Summoned successfully,
it can negate effects of all Monsters except of itself!
Dyson Sphere is...!
I activate the Magic Card, Big Bang Panic!
This card changes all face-up Magic or Trap Cards on my opponent’s field
to my opponent's Monster’s Overlay Units!
And with every additional Overlay Unit, my Monster gains 800 Attack Points!
And by detaching one Overlay Unit, I activate the effect of Neo Galaxy-Eyes!
It absorbs all Overlay Units from Dyson Sphere!
For Every Overlay Unit absorbed, it gains 500 Attack Points!
It's got 6800 Attack Points?!
And Neo Galaxy-Eyes can attack up to the Number of Overlay Units it absorbed!
Ever since that moment, somewhere deep within my heart,
I was chasing you all along.
And now, finally...
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Ultimate Photon Stream!!
Kaito, so is this your strength?
After revenge, only emptiness remains.
I am aware of that fact.
V, no, Christopher Arklight.
It’s been a long time since someone used that name to address me.
So that's V’s real name?
Together with my father, I have given up my family’s name.
Kaito, I did try to save my father.
But when my father returned from the Parallel Worlds,
his heart was already consumed by vengeance towards Dr. Faker.
I wasn't able to stop him.
Nevertheless, I guess that is what “parental relationship” is all about.
You're wrong.
I fight because I resist my father.
One day when I manage to resolve Haruto’s case,
I will settle the score with Dr. Faker using my own hands!
Kaito...
I see. So you have already become this strong, huh?
Chris, I will inherit your feelings.
And I will settle the score with Tron in your place!
Kaito...
You guys are indeed my…
...little brothers.
Chris...
Kaito.
Yuma...
Wait for me! I will definitely make it to the next stage!
Let's go, Orbital 7!
U-Understood!
Bu…But the glider is out of order.
I-I just got stared down...
U-Understood!
Now I will undergo urgent operation!
Please wait for 3 seconds. 1…2…3!
Let's...
...sleep together.
Tron and Dr. Faker...
When two of them took action,
I was transported to this world.
Which means that was your father’s intention, who is in the Astral World currently.
My father wished for me to stop Tron and Dr. Faker, together with you.
Yuma.
Right!
I'll do it! I'll do this!
I will give those egocentric adults a lesson too!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
On the scorching Magma Field, the Duel between Shark and IV has finally started!
The shocking truths revealed by IV, plus Tron’s sudden appearance…
On this field, his Monsters…
I can’t believe you would give Numbers to…
He can attack eight times in a row?!
Dueling isn't a tool for rage and revenge!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Shark Torpedoed! The Nightmarish Fanservice"
Hey, Shark!
Shark!
That was awesome how you beat Dyson Sphere, Kaito!
But that means Kaito will use Dyson Sphere when we fight him next.
Kaito is truly our greatest enemy.
I ain't gonna lose!
I'm gonna bring it to 'im!