So you've come, Kaito.
Chris... No, V!
Why?! How could you?!
What's the deal?
They haven't been broadcasting the Duels this whole time.
Is Yuma okay?
Something isn't right.
Kaito-sama! I can't stay put any longer!
Even if he turns me into scrap, I will stay by Kaito-sama's side!
I am his humble tool!
Where the heck are we even riding to?!
Geez, slow down a little!
But I gotta hurry and find someone who can fight me in the one-on-one Duels!
That may be true, but even
if you blindly ride through the darkness...
What do you think's gonna happen
if you fall into another Trap again?!
What?!
Did someone fall into a Trap?!
Humble tool...
Orbital?!
Oh~! You're the source of humbleness!
A-Are you okay? You're not broken, are you?
Huh?
Yikes! You're that dreadful scrap woman!
Gosh, I'm gonna throw you off!
Gah! Hold on a minute!
I have to hurry to Kaito-sama's side!
You're going to Kaito?
That's right... I have something I need to tell him.
Orbital! Show me the way!
U-Understood!
Kaito...
I always knew the day would
come where we would fight each other.
On that day I learned the truth...
I was consumed by feelings of hatred and revenge.
Ever since that day...!
You hurt Haruto.
I'll make you regret doing that! Here I come!
Duel!!
I'll take the first turn. My turn! Draw!
I Summon Planet Pathfinder!
Then I Special Summon Solar Wind Jammer!
This card can be Special Summoned from my hand by halving its Attack Power.
Then I activate the Magic Card, Tannhäuser Gate!
This card changes the levels of my two Monsters to the total of their combined levels.
My Monsters are Level Four and Five.
Thus, my two Monsters become Level Nines!
Two Level Nine Monsters...
I Overlay the Level Nine Planet Pathfinder and Solar Wind Jammer!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network.
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Number 9!
A Number!
What!?
Sky Canopy Star - Dyson Sphere!
Where is your Number?!
The moment I successfully Xyz Summoned,
because of the effect of the
Field Magic activated here, Cosmic Frontier,
I can draw one card!
I set one card face-down and end my turn.
Where is his Monster...?
What's wrong?
It's your turn, Kaito.
My turn! Draw!!
Even if I can't see what it looks like,
if he Summoned a Monster...
I Summon Photon Delta Wing!
Photon Delta Wing, attack his Monster!
Photon Missile!!
What!?
Unfortunately for you, your attacks won't be able to reach me.
Im-Impossible...!
Are you done now? Then I suppose it's my turn.
Draw!!
I use Dyson Sphere to attack Photon Delta Wing!
What!?
What in the world just happened?
You wouldn't know, would you?
My current Dueling goes far beyond your comprehension.
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too late for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Wow, this is amazing! Is this space?
This appears to be the Space Field.
"Number 55: Galaxy Eyes Sealed?!
The Cosmic Class Number Appears!"
I'll confirm the verification signal on the D-Pad.
It's Kaito-sama!
On that space ship!
H-Hold on! You're going too fast!
B-Because this thing won't do what I tell it to!
Geez, you really are an idiot.
Are you harmed, Kaito-sama?
K-Kaito!
You people...
Kaito...
Kaito, I have something I need to tell you.
Tell me?
Yeah, Droite... During Droite's Duel...!
That Tron jerk took her down!
Droite... fought desperately against Tron for your sake!
But...
Kaito...
Droite liked y-
That's none of my concern.
You...!
How could you...?!
Kaito-sama...?
Damn you, Kaito!
Yuma Tsukumo.
Kazuma-san's son.
You're...
I didn't think all the actors would gather in one place like this.
This could very well be the act of fate.
I have something I want to ask you.
My dad... Where's my dad?!
Very well. Before this Duel unfolds,
I shall tell you all that I know.
Stop joking around! I don't want to listen to anything you have to say!
Come on, let's continue the Duel already!
Kaito, this story is related to you as well.
Why do you think our family appeared in this Duel Carnival?
And why do you supposed we went after you siblings?
Why do we seek revenge against your father, Dr. Faker?
That Dr. Faker is...?
Dr. Faker is Kaito's dad?!
And you guys want revenge against him?
What the heck does he mean?
My dad and Kaito's dad were...?
You'll know the answer once you hear this story.
Five years ago from this date...
A scientist as well as Kaito's father, Faker,
spent a great amount of time researching a way to open the door to the Parallel Worlds with my father, Byron.
I am observing distortions in the dimensions all over the place.
And despite that, why can't I specify its location?!
Why can't I?!
Faker...
Come drink this and calm your nerve-
I have no time for that!
If I don't find the door to the Parallel Worlds soon...!
Faker...
That's right.
There's someone else looking for the door to the Parallel Words other than us...
Chris, bring up that image.
Yes, Father.
He's quite the interesting person with considerable talent, you see.
A man who is an adventurer, Kazuma Tsukumo.
This is nice. I can take it easy for a while here.
No one will bother me here.
Huh?
Well... Guess not.
Wow, that's some impressive equipment.
Welcome.
I'm grateful that you came all the way here when we called you on such short notice.
Kazuma Tsukumo.
I am Byron Arclight. I am in your hands.
A Gravity Charter Electromagnetic Wave Map, huh? That's incredible.
There is no time for this!
Huh?
I have investigated all the phenomenon that has been occurring!
But I haven't been able to find anything.
Something... Something's missing!
Kazuma, will you give us your opinion on
all of our research regarding the Parallel Worlds, whether we're right or wrong?
If we find that door, the history of mankind will be changed.
I bet we'll get more wealth
and fame than we'd ever think imaginable!
Wealth and fame...
I have no need for such worthless nonsense!
I have to find the door to the Parallel Worlds at all costs!
Hearing that puts my mind at ease.
Kazuma! You...
The only thing I'm interested in is genuine adventure!
So you were testing us...
Look at this.
If we want the door to the Parallel Worlds to open itself,
we have to observe any unusual behavior within the 21 passage points that are invoked on the map.
If we analyze them, I suspect we will be able to specify where the next door will manifest itself.
A 21 formulaic equation, huh?
That's right. The answer has already begun to reveal itself.
I'm just one step away.
But that one step is...
It won't appear.
Huh?
Absurd...! All of the observations are...
The location isn't within 21 passage points.
There are some things you just can't understand in a lab.
There's still two passage points remaining. In other words, there's 23 points where occurrence is possible.
I-Is that... really true!?
Yes. The answer is that this is really a 23 formulaic equation.
Thus, we began gathering new information in order to calculate a new formula.
We reached a single conclusion.
And the place we were headed...
...was the location where we believed the next door to the Parallel Worlds would reveal itself.
Well, our adventure begins now.
You guys will wait here and be on standby.
It will just be us going from here on out.
Just the three of us.
It'll be okay. Don't worry, Chris.
Father...
I saw nothing beyond this point.
What happened after is what my father told me from his memories...
Kazuma-san guided the three of them down the mountain toward the bottom of the Earth.
Kazuma-san, do you really think we'll be able to get there?
Our destination is unprecedented territory.
But that is why there's meaning in taking up the challenge.
We gotta bring it to 'em.
Bring it to 'em?
It's the feeling to never give up on a challenge.
Is that a picture of your family?
Yes.
The boy's obsessed with Dueling.
Oho, my family as well.
We have three sons.
Faker also has two sons.
Why is Dr. Faker so concerned with all this?
I'm not sure, but Faker is a true genius.
He must be thinking about something.
As for me, no matter what it takes,
I want to help him find the door of the Parallel Worlds.
Dr. Faker must be happy to have such a good friend like you.
Good friend, huh?
"When two souls are offered up, the door shall open."
As I figured.
Three days after that...
My father and the others finally reached their destination.
Are these some kind of historic ruins?
Could this be...?!
It is! I can't be wrong! This is the Parallel World's...
If that's the case, the door to the Parallel Worlds must be up ahead!
Faker! Kazuma!
Don't move!
I see. In order to keep out intruders, they've set all sorts of traps in here.
We haven't even seen the real threats yet.
Those without wisdom and courage
shouldn't dare to step foot in here.
Are you all right, Faker?
Huh? Yeah.
It's a dead end.
Strange. There has to be something here.
That's...
What?!
This moment has come at last!
Faker!
I hold no hatred toward either of you.
What the hell are you doing!?
There is something written on the ground below your feet.
It says, "When two souls are offered up, the door shall open."
You don't... intend to sacrifice us!?
Faker!
I must find the door to the Parallel Worlds no matter what!
Dr. Faker! Wasn't Byron your close friend!?
Close friend? What nonsense.
If you call yourself my close friend,
you should be delighted to become my sacrifice!
Byron!
Faker!
After all, mediocre fools like you couldn't possibly understand!
I'm gonna Bring it to 'em!
Kazuma... Kazuma, let go of my hand!
If you don't, you'll also...!
It's a bit inappropriate and childish for this situation,
but people say if you Duel, you're sure to make friends.
Dueling and adventuring is the same to me!
If you adventure together with others, you'll all become friends!
Kazuma...
I won't ever give up!
Now disappear from my sight!
I'll never forget this grudge, Faker!
So that's how my dad met his end...
"If you offer up two souls, a new door shall be opened."
This is... Xyz Summoning!
But my father came back.
While wandering the threshold in the Parallel Worlds, he fed off his own thoughts for revenge.
However, his appearance began
to change greatly as compensation.
Into the form you see now of my father, Tron!
Wh-What'd you just say!?
Tron... That same Tron is III and V's dad!?
And the one responsible for all of this is Dr. Faker!
I will have retribution at all costs!
I live only for Haruto.
Kaito...
I have no interest in what he... Dr. Faker has done.
We're continuing the Duel! Move, Yuma!
My turn! Draw!
I Special Summon Photon Thrasher!
This card can be Special Summoned
when I have no Monsters on the field!
Then I Normal Summon Photon Pirate!
Photon Pirate can Banish one Photon Monster in my Graveyard in order to raise this card's Attack Power by 1000 during this turn!
He has two Monsters with over 2000 Attack Power on the field.
Kaito's about to play his trump card!
I release Photon Thrasher and Photon Pirate!
Darkness within the shining galaxy...
Become the light of hope and live as my servant!
The Embodiment of Light will now descend!
Appear before us! Galaxy Eyes Photon Dragon!
So you've appeared, Galaxy Eyes...
In the last turn, my 1800 Attack Power Delta Wing was destroyed and I received 1000 points of damage...
In other words, the invisible enemy has 2800 Attack Points.
Then I'll demolish it using the 3000 Attack Power Galaxy Eyes!
How foolish.
Go! Photon Stream of Destruction!!
What!?
Very well, Kaito. I will show you my Number!
What in the world is this?!
Wh-What the heck?!
It's ridiculously huge!
Impossible!
A Monster so very large that it enshrouds the very sun itself.
Sky Canopy Star - Dyson Sphere!
No other Monster can even hope to defeat it.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
V's Number is Dyson Sphere!
Its ability protects it from all attacks.
It's truly an invincible Monster!
You're kidding! Kaito's going to lose?!
He's read through every one of his attacks?!
Kaito... You're my friend!
You have a purpose!
I won't allow you if you lose!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Great Decisive Battle of Outer Space!
Neo Galaxy-Eyes Strikes Back"
What is that card?!
Today we're introducing Number 9: Dyson Sphere!
How big it is!
I won't lose to its size!
In the bathroom, I can make something way bigger-
What are you saying when people are eating dinner?!
I apologize...