So they're my opponents today, eh?
I have to give them some fanservice...
You're as distasteful as always.
You choose your opponents as your fans and send them off to Hell.
It's far too much of a hassle to search for a worthy opponent.
And I do have a ton of fans, you see.
And every last one of them are terrible Duelists.
God am I sick of it.
Collecting Numbers isn't exactly easy, you know.
Then maybe you'll think to take better care of those Numbers, IV.
Huh? If you got a problem with the way I'm doing it, why don't you try collecting them yourself, V?
Now isn't the time for me to act.
Oh? Are you tryin' to say I'm your pawn or something?
Then let's settle this here and now...
Brothers!
Please stop this! Fighting will do you no good.
You shut your mouth, III.
No, III is right.
IV, you said a bit too much.
You mustn't forget that noble heart of yours like the other two did.
Tron...!
Are you trying to label me as a troublemaker?
Watch your tongue!
Say wha-
I will not tolerate you being rude to Tron!
Got it...
III, you understand your role today, do you not?
I do, Brother V.
Ryoga Kamishiro is fighting desperately to find IV.
Give him this Number.
He is sure to come before you two eventually.
Yes, Brother V.
Dr. Faker...
We will steal everything from him.
Just as he did us!
V...
V, be sure not to let him know of my existence.
Dr. Faker thinks I'm dead.
It's my job to notify him of my presence, after all.
My brave Duelists, good morning!
It's day two of the World Duel Carnival!
That's right! Today's where things get real!
Clash your passionate hearts against one another!
Heart Burning!
I'm in top form today!
Yuma, in top form. How rare.
Heh! I'm different in this tournament today!
Check it out!
What is that? What is that?
They're Heart Pieces!
I already got three!
Let’s follow this momentum and qualify for the Finals!
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
I guess you're a bit overconfident.
Hurry up already!
Please wait!
Tetsuo-kun! And the class rep too!
They're really energetic too! Nice!
Hurry up, class rep!
Please wait-
That hurt...!
Hurry it up! We'll be late!
Hey!
Why're you guys in such a rush?
Yuma!
Listen here!
To summarize, this is why!
Who's that dude?
He's the Asia Champion, IV!
C'mon! He's the guy Shark fought in the National Championship.
Shark...
The guy I once lost to in the National Championship has appeared.
He... IV, lured me into his trap!
He even got innocent people involved!
So this man is the one Shark was talking about.
We're about to Duel against IV!
He appointed us!
Isn't that guy a dangerous opponent?
Whatever do you mean?
I heard he used unethical means for victory.
There isn't a Duelist more gentle than IV.
To be able to Duel against him...
To summarize, I already have no regrets in my life!
We gotta hurry!
Ah, you're right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Hey! Wait up!
You're gonna Duel in a place like this?
It's such a quiet place, so we should be able to take our time and enjoy our Duel with him.
Yeah. That's for sure.
Ah... I suppose that's true.
That's IV?
- It's IV!
You're IV-san, aren't you?!
I apologize for the wait, Todoroki-kun, Takeda-kun.
Well then, let us get started.
B-Before that, please autograph this for me!
Me too, me too!
With pleasure. Fanservice is my motto, after all.
Is this acceptable?
Thank you so much!
M-Me too!
Here you go.
Now for our Duel.
Tetsuo-kun, who’s going first?
Oh, right...
If you'd like, the three of us can go together.
The rules will be a Battle Royale betting all our Heart Pieces.
A Battle Royale?
Is he serious?
The Battle Royale rules makes it so all participants are enemies.
But Tetsuo and the class rep will no doubt be aiming for IV.
In other words, this is actually a 2-on-1 match.
He may be an advanced player, but these conditions still put him at the absolute disadvantage.
I want you two to realize the infinite possibilities during a Duel.
You guys could even defeat me in the process.
That's what Dueling is all about!
Wow, IV's a pretty nice dude!
Here goes!
Yeah!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazers, set!
AR Vision - Link established.
Duel!!
The second day of the World Duel Carnival has begun!
Only those who collect six Heart Pieces can advance to the Finals!
I'm definitely gonna complete the Heart Puzzle and make it into the Finals!
As I get closer, I stretch my hand out
towards that shining light leading towards tomorrow
I dream of a world that expands from my feet.
I haven't a clue of where things like dreams and hopes are at.
Even if I run looking for it, I still can't seem to find it.
I wonder if I have fallen into a gap of truth and lies.
Even so, our grand tale has yet to begin.
Let's move on towards tomorrow,
even if our road begins to fall apart.
I will jump forward, before all my
strength completely drains.
The closer I get, the further it becomes,
that truth that I must seize.
It's to find hope that we desire from a future unseen.
With a heart stronger than anyone else,
I'll learn to keep running up.
With the strength to win any battle,
despite just how weak I am,
My purpose is to find,
with these invaluable friends of mine,
The future of the world expanding
from my feet with my own eyes.
Please, you two go first.
According to the rules of a Battle Royale, the player with the later gets more of a disadvantage.
But he actually forfeits going first!
I'm going first!
"Number 33: The Hellish Tag Duel!
The Fiendish Hero, IV"
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Aye-Iron!
The Battle Royale rules state that none of the players can attack in their first turns!
I end my turn with that!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Debugger X!
That will end my turn!
Wow, you guys brought out some unique Monsters!
That's how it should be. It almost feels like I have no chance.
Tetsuo-kun, we were praised by IV!
Yeah! But don't let your guard down.
My turn! Draw!
I set a Monster in face-down Defense Mode!
I then set two cards.
I activate the Field Magic, Xyz Colosseum, from my hand!
This card can increases all Xyz Monster’s Attack Power by 200...
All Monsters other than Xyz Monsters cannot declare an attack.
And that is the end of my turn.
A cemetery?
A Colosseum for Xyz Monsters... Why play such a Field Magic?
After all, the opponent’s Xyz Monsters will gain Attack Power too.
In order to Summon an Xyz Monster, 2 or more Monsters with the same level are required.
Before we have enough Monsters, he is planning to seal our attacks using Xyz Colosseum.
But that won't work!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Tinplate Goldfish!
When this card is Summoned successfully, if I have another Tinplate Goldfish in my hand, I can Special Summon it!
I Special Summon Tinplate Goldfish!
Now he's got three Level Four Monsters on his field!
Gonna do it?!
I Overlay my two Level Four Tinplate Goldfish and my Aye-Iron!
I build the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Tinplate Archduke!
Amazing!
I can't believe you already Summoned an Xyz Monster!
I activate the effect of Xyz Colosseum!
Due to this card’s effect, the Xyz Monster, Tinplate Archduke, gains 200 Attack Points!
Here goes! I activate Tinplate Archduke's effect!
By detaching one Overlay Unit, I can change the battle position of one of my opponent's Monsters!
This can't be! All of a sudden, my face-down Monster is...
What a Duelist you are!
Th-That so?
Tetsuo-kun! You got praised by IV again! To summarize, I am envious!
I switch IV's face-down Defense Monster into Attack Mode!
The monster I set was Gimmick Puppet - Baby Face!
A Monster with zero Attack Points...
This is a good chance!
I know!
Tinplate Archduke, attack Gimmick Puppet - Baby Face!
Strike of the Archduke!!
I activate the Trap Card, Repair Puppet!
When a Level Four or lower Puppet Monster was destroyed by battle,
this card can Special Summon a Monster with the same card name from my deck!
Come forth, Gimmick Puppet - Baby Face!
But that Monster's useless against me!
I activate Tinplate Archduke's effect!
I detach one Overlay Unit...
...and change the battle position of my opponent's Monster!
Excellent! So you can use Tinplate Archduke's effect not once, but countless times per Duel?
Or maybe I should say, "This is bad."
Hey, isn't this impressive?
Yeah! It may be a two-man effort, but they could really beat the Asian champion!
My turn! Draw!
Maybe, just maybe...!
Even IV himself may have let his guard down!
IV's got a zero-ATK Monster on his field!
If we attack with a Monster that has 1600 or more Attack Power, we win!
I Summon Debugger Z!
When I successfully Summon Debugger Z when I have Debugger X on the field,
to summarize, I can Special Summon Debugger Y from the deck!
Oh! You have three Level Three Monsters!
I Overlay the three Level Three Monsters, Debugger X, Y, and Z!
I build the Overlay Network with my three Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Show yourself, Vaccinegal!
Also, because of the effect of Xyz Colosseum, she gains 200 Attack Points!
Nice one, class rep!
Go, Vaccinegal!
Whoa! If this happens...!
- We did it!
Yes!
We did it, class rep!
Yes! We defeated IV!
Wow, that was magnificent.
Such wonderful attacks.
But I did not take any damage.
No way! They destroyed his Monster...
Wh-Why...?
So sorry, but I activated the Continuous Trap prior to the attack, Gimmick Box!
When I am about to receive Battle Damage, this card can negate that damage,
and the trap Special Summons itself as a Monster Card!
Additionally, the negated value becomes this guy’s Attack Power!
Brother, please hurry.
If they haven't Summoned them during the previous attacks,
they don't have Numbers at all.
Numbers?!
It can't be! Are they also gathering Numbers?!
I'm aware.
Guess it's about time... I show them my true fanservice.
IV-san?
What're you talking about?
I shall offer you hope!
Then snatch it back!
It's at this moment that human beings make the most beautiful faces.
To let you have those expressions... that’s my fanservice!
My turn! Draw!
Your Dueling was splendid!
Both your combination and your tactics!
But despite that...
In the end, it was no where near the level needed to defeat me!
I Summon Gimmick Puppet - Scarecrow!
And then the Magic Card, Level Cross! Activate!
By sending a card from my hand to the Graveyard,
I can double the level of one Level Four or lower Monster!
I hope you thoroughly enjoy the taste...
...of my fanservice!
I Overlay my Level Eight Gimmick Box and Scarecrow!
I build the Overlay Network with my two Monsters!
Xyz Summon!
Come before us...
Number 16!
The messenger from Hell, the puppet who controls the strings of fate...
Gimmick Puppet - Giant Killer!
A-A Number?!
He had a Number?!
And then, the effect of Xyz Colosseum raises its Attack Power up 200 points!
And I activate the effect of Giant Killer!
By detaching one Overlay Unit...
Giant Killer can destroy all of my opponent's Xyz Monsters this turn!
And you take damage equal to the Attack Power of the Monster that was destroyed!
- What?!
Tinplate Archduke had 2400 Attack Points!
Take my fanservice!
- Tetsuo-kun!
- Tetsuo!
Tetsuo-kun...?
You're next!
I destroy your Xyz Monster!
And you take damage equal to the Monster's Attack Power!
Take this!
Class rep!
Fantastic! It's so beautiful!
Such painful and twisted expressions!
It shines only during my service!
And the true fanservice has only just begun!
I activate the effect of the Gimmick Puppet - Baby Face in my Graveyard!
When this Monster rests in my Graveyard after being destroyed in battle,
when the Monsters who destroyed them are also in the Graveyard,
by reviving the Baby Faces and then Banishing them,
I can Special Summon Tinplate Archduke and Vaccinegal!
It took Tetsuo's Monster from the Graveyard!
At this moment, because of the effect of Xyz Colosseum,
Tinplate Archduke gains 200 Attack Points!
I get it! He's using Xyz Colosseum for this purpose!
Why the heck's he reviving his enemy's Monsters?!
This is a looped attack!
You are nothing but puppets controlled by the strings leading to destruction.
You cannot escape from my control!
And your Monsters will be destroyed yet again!
Bask in the pain!
By pulling his opponent’s Monsters out from the Graveyard, he can launch a loop attack by destroying those Monsters again,
while inflicting damage equal to destroyed Monster’s Attack Power to the opponents!
This is cruel!
Not yet!
My fanservice hasn't ended!
Giant Killer!!
Wait! The match is over!
Did you not even noticed just how much they were enjoying my fanservice?
Go, Giant Killer!
Final Dance!!
Class rep!
Tetsuo!
Are these tombstones all Duelists defeated by IV?!
Hey, you all right?!
Hey!
How brutal!
Tetsuo! Pull yourself together!
Forget me... The class rep...
I can't believe this...
These guys really admired you!
So how could you do this?!
A worthy star gives everything for his fans!
And I truly mean everything...
What'd you say?
IV, I won't forgive you!
Fight me!
Are you going to become one of my fans as well?
Found you!
Shark!
Have you forgotten the face of your greatest fan...
IV!?
Someone gave me some water.
So I was able to paint a rainbow with ease.
I want to become someone perfect.
But it's very difficult.
Even with me suffering,
I can't seem to grasp victory.
I want to bloom!
I must be having some kind of weird dream.
But If I must fulfill this,
Then I don't mind being laughed at for it.
Since it's because your limits are decided on your own.
I'll show it, overcoming it to tomorrow.
Ah, I'm aiming for the big blue sky.
For all of its glory.
The Freesia of Desire.
All of those countless flower petals
They came at the expense of
me being able to reach those heights.
Ah, even though I lost my way today,
I still yearn for it.
That Freesia of Desire.
After approaching IV, a Duel between III and Shark begins.
Shark, did you say revenge??
Who on earth are they?
Anyhow, we need to get them to the hospital!
The field's under water?
Indeed, under these circumstances, there is a way to bring a reversal!! But that’s…
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Determined Revenge, Tragic Duelist, Shark"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
Gosh, Yuma! You farted, didn't you?!
I-It wasn't me! It was...
That's right! It was Astral!
Yuma, what is a fart?
A fart is he~! He~!
He~?