My name is Yuma Tsukumo!
I'm a first year middle school student, aiming to bring it to 'em to become the Duel Champion one day!
Eh? You're giving me Baby Tragon?
Isn't that an Exceed Monster?--
You can't, Yuma! Accepting Tokunosuke's card like that.
That guy's action definitely has hidden motives!
You guys are a little too distrusting...
But you were still deceived in the end.
If you lose this duel, as a result of the Ante Rule,
the Numbers cards will be taken away.
Why would you do this? Tokunosuke...
I thought we were friends!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope was... taken away!
You fell for it, conversely!
As long as this continuous trap card, Uratora C is on my side of the field,
This duel is mine for sure!
If I win, as promised, I'll be taking your Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
You're after my Number, aren't you?
T-Tokunosuke...!
Not sure what's happening, but my body is surging with energy...
What's happening..?
He took one of the Numbers away, didn't he?
One of the Numbers!?
No. 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope's number...
Tokunosuke...
What's wrong?
M-my body is...!
W-What's with these steams of light...
If we fail to win this Duel, then I will disappear.... from this world...
Don't tell me this guy is going to disappear...
Because I accepted his duel...
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and end your turn.
In any case, I have to win this duel...
Only Numbers can defeat other Numbers.
Right now my only other Numbers are,
Revise Dragon and Terabyte.
On my side of the field are my Level 4 Gagaga, and Level 2 Full Elf.
It's no use..
With these two, I won't be able to Exceed Summon...
Turn end!
So I see you've prepared yourself.
I'll take the victory in one shot.
My turn!
Draw!!
I attack Full Elf with Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Hope Sword Slash !!
With that, our life points are 2500 VS. 1900.
The tables has turned.
I set one monster in face down defense position.
Turn end!!
If I don't quickly summon my own Numbers,
At this rate it'll be all over..!
My turn.
Draw!!
Alright, I got it!
With this I can summon a Numbers!
I summon my Level 3 monster, Rai-Rider!!
And then, I activate Gagaga Magician's monster effect!
Once per turn before the end phase, this card's level can change to anything between 1 to 8!
I change Gagaga Magician to Level 3, the same level as Rai-Rider!
Alright, here we go!
I overlay my Level 3 monsters, Gagaga Magician and Rai-Rider!
With these two monsters, I construct the Overlay network!
Exceed Summon!
Appear! Numbers 17, Revise Dragon!
Numbers 17...?!
There are other Numbers?
In that case this one is mine too!
I activate my Continuous Trap card!
Hidden Mist!!
W-What's happening? This fog...
This is the fog of betrayal.
Continuous Trap Hidden Mist's effect,
When a monster is special summons to the opponent's side of the field, gain control of that monster!
Revise Dragon is...!
Here it comes...!!
You're kidding right? Revise Dragon too..
Astral..!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Yuma, with both Hope and Revise stolen away!
This is a duel he can't afford to lose!!
"Numbers 6:
The Treacherous Numbers!?"
Just as I thought, these photos are fake!
So they're just pasted onto some edited photos?
This one too...
This one too...!
So they were all photo manipulations?
This way we can prove Yuma's innocence!
But, who would do such a thing?
Hm...
That's right, Taichi-kun!
Taichi-kun might know something.
Could it be, that Taichi was in on this?
Taichi-kun!
This is Kotori.
Huh? W-What is it?
Can you hold on and listen to me for a sec,
Ah, I'm busy right now.
Taichi-kun!
Let's talk next time.
We got cut off...
Behind his voice, we can hear the sound of the school bell!
Astral!
Hey, Astral!
Astral...
He's talking to himself again...
Yuma.
It's about time you accepted that you've lost!
As for falling for the trap, you have no one to blame but yourself.
Why would you do this?
Why must you deceive others around you just to win?
That kind of thing? Definitely.
Dueling is meaningless if you're not the winner!
After all, this is the rule of our world!
I knew this more than anyone...
That was when I first started dueling...
Hm? So Toku-chan's starting to duel?
Will you let us teach you how to play?
Really?
However, we're playing with Ante Rule.
Ante Rule?
It's a gambling duel.
The winner takes the loser's cards.
Take them?
This way, you'll be able to duel seriously and get better real quick.
We're just looking out for you.
But that was all lies.
Day after day, those guys kept taking my cards.
That idiot, didn't even realize he's getting ripped off.
Thanks to him, we got some nice cards..
At that moment, I realized.
Everything has a hidden flipside.
Those guys putting up a smiling face just to get close to me, they're always hiding something. Isn't that right?
And then I've decided.
If that's the case, I'll pursue the hidden side of the world to its fullest!
Tokunosuke...
Taichi-kun!
He's not here..
But he's definitely somewhere at school.
Taichi-kun!
Taichi!
I vowed to use that hidden world to bring them my revenge.
In order to master the sleight of hand,
I practiced hard everyday.
And then, I took back the cards that were taken from me.
I was hated, but I'm glad.
After all, everything in this world has a hidden side.
As long as I won, everyone obediently wagged their tails.
That is human nature.
The true nature of society and such,
Lie and deceive if you can't win,
Same thing with dueling, winning means everything!
That's not dueling at all!
Winning is everything, and such...
Dueling is the clash between soul and soul!
If that's how you're gonna put it,
Then you can live forever like a hopeless loser.
No good, he's not around!
Same here.
The remaining place we haven't looked is...
The old gym!
That's the place for sure!
That Taichi...
Whoever's behind this, I'll definitely get it out of him!
Taichi-kun!
Just... Just a little bit more left...!
Why did you guys have to come over?!
I-I'm really sorry!
If I knew you were working on a dominoes line...
But why have dominoes in a place like this?
If I set all of this up,
Tokunosuke said he'll give me an Exceed Monster,
If I set this up by morning.
It's Tokunosuke!?
I knew it.
So it was Tokunosuke's doing.
So that means...
Yuma!
The only Numbers I have left is Terabyte.
In that case, I'll use this Magic card...!
Release Lease - when there's only one monster on my side of the field, I can release that monster.
After that, I can add one Level 3 monster from the deck to my hand.
Alright.
I'll release Baby Tragon!...
Baby Tragon...
Protect it..
Hey you, are you alright?
Baby Tragon...
But, Baby Tragon can't beat the Numbers!
I will...
Change Baby Tragon to defense position!
And then, I set one card faced down.
Turn end!
Trying to harden your defense, are you?
It's all useless!
My turn !!
Draw !!
That Yuma, where did he run off to?
Let's go check the shopping mall.
I activate Revise Dragon's monster effect!
Once per turn, by consuming one Overlay unit, its Attack power is increased by 500!
And then I flip summon!
Flip summon?
When a face down defense position monster is changed to face up attack position by the player.
In other words-- Even if it wasn't attacked, its flip effect can still be activated!
Appear!
Uragutan!
I activate Uragutan's flip effect!
Defense position monsters are switched to attack position!
Baby Tragon is changed back to attack position?
And then, I use Revise Dragon to attack Baby Tragon!
Vice Stream !!
I activate my trap card, Half Unbreak!
Half Unbreak - One monster on my side of the field cannot be destroyed by battle this turn,
And then, the battle damage to the player is decreased by half.
So you've been hiding a trap like that..
However, Aspiring Emperor Hope's attack power is 2500.
Half of that damage is plenty enough!
Go, Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Hope Sword Slash !!
Then, I activate magic card Book of Reversal from my hand!
With this card, one of my flip effect monsters is changed to face down defense position.
This way I can reuse its flip effect.
If this keeps up, even if I change Baby Tragon to defense position,
Uragutan's flip effect will change it back to attack position,
And I'll take battle damage..!
Bingo~!
It's great that you finally realized this.
However, you only have 300 life points remaining.
Next turn it'll be all over.
Turn end.
Damn...
Yuma!
Kotori, Tetsuo!
Yuma, just what in the world is...
You guys are too late.
The outcome is already certain.
2500 VS. 300 ?!
And how did Aspiring Emperor Hope and Revise Dragon end up on Tokunosuke's field...!?
Come on, Yuma.
It's your turn.
With 300 life points, I don't have a choice..
There's nothing I can do but to defend!...
It's my turn.
Draw !!
Needle Swordsman..
It's no use... at this rate I can't keep defending!
Looks like you didn't get the card you wanted.
At this rate I'm not even off the ground, and it'll be all over..
Yuma..
It doesn't matter how you feel, it's still no use.
On your side of the field,
You have an Exceed Monster from the bottom of the trash barrel.
Rank 1 Baby Tragon, that's all.
There's nothing you can possibly do.
There's no way out, isn't it...
Protect it...
This guy, why Baby Tragon...
I see...
So that's how it is..!
Let's go.
Baby Tragon!
I summon Needle Swordsman!
Attack power 300?
What can a card like that possibly do?
It certainly can, together with Baby Tragon!
That card from the trash can?
I'll rise to the sky !!
I activate Baby Tragon's monster effect!
By consuming one overlay unit, one Level 1 monster can attack directly!
Go, Needle Swordsman!
Attack Tokunosuke directly!
Merely 300 points of damage.
I can barely even feel it!
It's useless!
Alright, now!!
I activate Needle Swordsman's monster effect!
Hurricane-!
W-What's this?
When Needle Swordsman direct attacks successfully,
All of your face up Magic and Trap cards are returned to the hand!
All of it?!
That's right!
Your cards that took away Aspiring Emperor Hope and Revise Dragon,
Since they're no longer on your field,
Those two will come back to me once again!
My Numbers, they're...
Alright!
I got the Numbers back!
Hey you, are you alright?
Let's win.
Revise Dragon, attack that face down defense position monster!
Like I said, this is suppose to be my duel!
Let's go, Revise Dragon !!
Attack that face down defense position monster!
Vice Stream !!
Alright!
Nice! this way there's no more defending monsters.
Aspiring Emperor Hope, direct attack!!
Let's go !!
Hope Sword Slash !!
Alright !!
I did it !!
He won!
You did it Yuma!
Well done.
We protected the Numbers cards.
It's nothing! It's not like I did it for you!
Yuma!
What an awesome reversal finish, Yuma!
Thanks to Baby Tragon!
I lost..
B-But why?
Tokunosuke.
You can have it back.
This is...
It's your card, after all.
As an exchange, don't use it for underhanded tricks anymore.
Baby Tragon will be sad.
However, you're pretty powerful!
I'm powerful?
Yeah!
Specially, you're the first guy I've ever seen that use flip effects this well!
Yuma...
Hmph. I'm not falling for that.
Flattering me like that, what's your real intention?
Intention? There isn't!
I really thought you were powerful! That's why.
I don't believe you.
Did you really mean it?
Of course!
Yuma--!
Calling me powerful and all that,
This is the first time ever!!
Everyone always called me shameless and dirty..
It's decided. You can keep the card!
As a token of our friendship.
Really?
Alright!
I really wanted this!
Thanks a bunch, Tokunosuke!
With this, we'll become trusted bros!
Yeah!
All of this because he got a card, what a greedy guy...
Returning a desired card...
Observation result #9.
Even Yuma thinks of thing on the flipside..
This is the last one!
Wait a sec? you're kidding right?
Wait a minute!!
Why me--?!
Let's duel! This week's question:
If Rai-Rider attacks the defense position Chuubone, can it be destroyed? Or not destroyed?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
ESPer Robin is coming to our town!
However, Robin's actor, Fuuya is suffering.
Next time, Yu-Gi-Oh! ZEXAL -
Banquet of Justice! Here comes ESPer Robin!!
Rai-Rider would destroy Chuubone!
When the attacking monster's Attack Power is higher than the defense monster's DEF,
The defending monster is destroyed!
Yuma's new friend, Baby Tragon!
Now, attack the enemy directly!!