Kaito, you and I still haven’t settled the score yet!
Duel with me!
Interesting.
I guess we can call this the real Final.
Very well. I accept.
Yuma, Astral!
Great! I'm gonna bring it to ya!
Up until now, I've been fighting as
a Numbers Hunter for Haruto's sake.
But...
But I...
Brother, are you going?
Sure.
Brother...
It's fine. I definitely won't lose.
Astral, my whole body's kinda tingly!
Mine too.
Kaito's strong!
When we met him that first time, we came really close to getting taken down.
And I turned into ZeXal with you, when we were fighting him inside the Emperor's Key.
We also had a Tag Duel to save Haruto.
After all of that, I really started to think Kaito was a strong guy!
But no matter how much I may think of him,
my only goal is to surpass him!
Together with you, I will beat him for sure!
Yuma is bursting with fighting spirit.
I'm getting somewhat nervous myself, or not!
Can Yuma-kun win against Kaito?
No clue, but this is the true Final!
It's all right! It's Yuma we're talking about,
so he'll definitely win, meow!
What the?
Meo-what's that sound?
That's...?
Kaito!
I kept you waiting.
Show me the mood you guys are in!
Kaito-sama, will you please teach that Yuma dork a lesson?!
Kaito...
Kaito, I'll finally settle this today.
Let's fight!
With our Duelist's pride at stake, we will challenge you and win!
Yuma.
Astral.
With my full strength...
...I accept this fight with you!
Let's get started!
Let's go!
Duel Disk, set!
Duel Mode: Photon Change!
D-Gazer, set!
AR Vision: Link established.
Duel!!
Brother...
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Hey, my friends, what scenery do you suppose
awaits us on the other side of this hill?
Hey, my friends, let's climb it together
It's too soon for us to turn back now
The time has come to combine
together the power dwelling inside me
Gotta release my Soul Drive
Advance, advance, beyond the limits of your strength
Come along with me and burn our flame of life
Keep running, keep running, until you get there
Once again, once again, keep those challenges coming
My friends, keep on living in the here and now
Keep pressing onward together no matter what happens
Go!
Yu-
- Yuma!
You won't leave here until he's lost, got it?!
"Number 72: The Ultimate Showdown Has Come!!
Yuma VS Kaito: The Other W.D.C. Final!"
Sure, leave it to me.
Astral, you too! Don't look so grumpy and do your best!
Oh?! Don't tell me, you...
You can see this guy?!
He's become visible to me somehow.
Eh?!
Apparently, due to the effects of that battle,
there are a few people that have become able to see me.
Does that mean that Shark and Kaito, too...?
What's up, Astral, Yuma? Don't you want to come at me?
Got it. Here I go. I'm first!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Ganbara Knight in Attack Position!
That guy... Even though Ganbara Knight switches to Attack Mode when it's attacked...!
To summarize, Summoning a zero Attack Power Monster in Attack Position is just...!
Anyway, just do your best, Yuma-kun!
Yuma.
Wh-What's up?
Good job.
I activate the Continuous Magic, Zerozelock!
With the effect of this card,
Monsters on the field with zero Attack Points can't be attacked!
Since it's Kaito, we have to assume there's a good chance he'll bring out Galaxy-Eyes from the very beginning.
Together with the effect of Ganbara Knight, this is a double solution to face the enemy.
Yeah! I end my turn with that!
Now bring it to me!
Yuma, you certainly have become stronger...
But... My turn! Draw!
When I have no Monsters on my field, I can Special Summon this guy!
Appear, Photon Slasher!
Then I Normal Summon Photon Crusher!
Two Monsters with more than 2000 Attack Points!
Even knowing the defense we set up, he still went and Summoned them?
I release my 2000 Attack Power Photon Crusher and my 2100 Photon Slasher!
Darkness within the shining galaxy...
Become the light of hope and live as my servant!
The incarnation of light descends!
Come forth! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Galaxy-Eyes!
Be buried in the Galaxy!
Galaxy-Eyes, attack Ganbara Knight!
Hold it, Kaito!
Due to the effect of Zerozelock, you can't attack my zero Attack Power Ganbara Knight!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Galaxy Burst!
With this card, by halving the Attack Power of my Galaxy-Eyes until the end of the turn,
I can negate the effects of up to two face-up cards on the opponent's field!
Ganbara Knight's Monster Effect and Zerozelock's effect are sealed!
My defense!
As to be expected from Kaito.
He had already thought a step ahead of us when he Summoned Galaxy-Eyes, it seems.
Galaxy-Eyes, attack Ganbara Knight!
Photon Stream of Destruction!
1500 damage all at once!
So he's still no match for Kaito, or not?
That's me-ot the case!
That's right, Yuma, stand up!
I... I know... that.
Kaito! The Duel has just begun!
Yuma...
He's always like that.
You always stand up again and again.
Looking forward...
I activate the Continuous Magic, Battle Gravity!
With this card, when a player controls a Monster that did not battle,
he will receive 1000 points of damage!
Wa... Wait a sec! What do you mean?
So we have no other option but to battle against Galaxy-Eyes?
That's what it means!
I set one card and end my turn!
The effect of Galaxy Burst ends.
Galaxy-Eyes Attack Power and the effect of Yuma's Zerozelock return to normal.
No matter how much you struggle, it won't work on me.
That's right, Kaito.
That's what I expect a Duel with you to be like!
This happens and that happens and on it goes.
Isn't that totally fun?!
Fun?
What about my tactics are fun?
I don't know anything about tactics.
I'm talking about the throbbing of our hearts!
The throbbing of our hearts?
Sure, that throbbing is in a Duel, too!
That's what it means to bring it to 'em!
And when I Duel, I understand how amazing my opponent is.
Then we become friends!
Just take a look!
That throbbing spread and gathered everyone here together!
Yuma...
To summarize...
Yes, or not!
Cat!
Throb it to 'em!
He never changes.
His mood is unbeatable.
I've got the throbbing too...
...from Yuma's and Kaito's Duel.
Throbbing of the heart.
If you have this throbbing, everyone will become your friend!
You become one in a Duel!
Kaito, don't you think that too!?
If that's the case, then show me your best!
Huh?
The Numbers!
My true victory will be defeating your Numbers.
Now, call the Numbers!
Sure, I'll show it to you.
How I bring it to 'em!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Goblindbergh!
When Goblindbergh is Summoned successfully,
I can Special Summon a Level Four or lower Monster from my hand!
Come! Gagaga Magician!
I Overlay my Level Four Goblindbergh and Gagaga Magician!
I use these two Monsters to build the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Come forth, Number 39! Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Hope's here!
Here's your chance!
Yuma!
Hope.
Aspiring Emperor - Hope attacks Galaxy-Eyes!
Cat! But meo-why, when Hope has the lower Attack Power?
I detach one Overlay Unit to negate Hope's attack!
I don't know what you're aiming at, but did you forget?
With the effect of Battle Gravity, because you didn't battle, you take 1000 points of damage!
Yuma!
Sure!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Flash Effect!
When a Monster Effect is activated during battle,
it increases the Attack Power of one Monster by 800 points,
and negates the effects of all Monsters on the field!
What did you say?
Then Galaxy-Eyes' effect is...
It can't Banish Monsters anymore!
Hope's Attack Power goes up to 3300!
Also, the Monster Effects of both Galaxy-Eyes and Aspiring Emperor - Hope are negated!
Yuma, you...
Without the effect, Galaxy-Eyes cannot Banish Monsters,
and Hope's effect never negated the battle.
This means, I increase its Attack Power and the battle continues!
Galaxy-Eyes' effect is held off too!
Go, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Dream on!
Trap, activate! Battle Simulation!
When two Monsters battle, both their Attack Points are halved, and they will not be destroyed!
Clever!
So he managed to minimize the Battle Damage!
His spirit's not too shabby!
Kaito-sama!
I'm not done yet!
What!?
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Bi-Bind!
It can be activated by targeting a Monster on my field who had its Attack Power decreased!
The Monster's Attack Power is doubled during the battle!
Say what!?
Plus, the effect of Battle Simulation is negated, and the opposing Monster can be destroyed!
You can't mean... Galaxy-Eyes will...!
Go, Hope! Big Hope Sword Slash!
The effects of all Magic and Traps ends,
and Hope's Attack Power and effect goes back to normal.
I set one card and end my turn!
Got it!
I managed to inflict huge damage on Kaito!
How was it? How was it, Astral?!
Wasn't it awesome?!
I'm awesome, aren't I?! Aren't I?!
No matter how often he fails...
No matter how many times he gets in a jam...
He never gives up, desperately trying to stand up again.
Yes, and he enjoys Dueling from the bottom of his heart.
But as I am now...
Kaito...
Kaito, you can't be...
Hmm?
Yuma, Astral.
Kaito?
Brother... I knew it!
This is...
...the end.
Huh?
I can no longer... keep Dueling.
I surrender this Duel.
What are you talking about?!
What do you mean you can't keep Dueling?!
As I thought, my brother...
What do you mean by that?!
I can no longer...
...find any meaning in continuing to Duel.
Kaito...
Up until now, I've only been Dueling for Haruto's sake.
But now that Haruto has been saved...
...my reason to fight has disappeared.
That's why I can no longer...
Kaito.
Give it a break! You have been my goal!
I won't let you just quit like that!
Yuma, unlike you...
I can't give a passionate Duel.
Kaito...
Kaito, that's where you're wrong.
Yuma is fighting with me to collect the Numbers.
Victory will bring back my lost memories.
But that is nothing but collecting the past.
Dueling with Yuma brought something much more important to me.
Something more important?
It's friends.
Through Dueling, you are talking from heart to heart, deepening the bonds between your friends.
Kaito, the same applies to you.
For me, you are a very important friend.
Memories are things of the past.
Friends represent the future.
You don't need to be tied to the past anymore.
And, besides, haven't you already noticed this?
Isn't it this why you have come here?
All Duelists really are friends!
It lets one change themselves and bring it on a whole new level!
I promised Haruto.
I swore to let him see you!
I...
Kaito!
Kite it to 'em, Kaito!
I can feel your throbbing!
Yuma.
But your throbbing isn't this weak.
There's more to it than that! Much more! So show it to me!
Feel your own Kite it to 'em within you!
Kaito, this is all my fault.
Because of the expectations of us adults, I repeatedly made Kaito suffer.
Even now...
It's all right, Dad.
Huh?
I can see in my brother's eyes that he's trying to respond to Yuma.
This throbbing won't satisfy anyone.
I have no idea what lies ahead,
but I will open up my own path.
My own Dueling!
Kaito.
It looks like Kaito got his own Dueling back.
Yuma Tsukumo, you really are a remarkable guy.
Kazuma's son, he is.
Well, let's head back to our home.
Chris...
Thomas...
Michael.
Yes, Father.
Yuma, I'm certain that we'll meet again.
Alright, come on, Kaito!
Here I come! My turn! Draw!
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
Move on ahead, speeding up our throbbing beats
Listen boys and girls, here's the secret to boys and girls like you
You're really just so spontaneous, wild as can be
I bet you didn't know?
You might be a handful, but what's wrong with that?
Be up to no good, but learn for real
Go the unpredictable route and shuffle your cards with a goal in mind
Whenever you feel like you've lost your way, just take a minute to close your eyes...
Shout "stop!" with all you've got, and there's your boundary line.
We stand tall, until we have victory in our grasp
We won't just stop here, not when we don't want to have any regrets.
Even if we get hurt, we can't just hesitate now
We won't just give up, not when our future's a lot brighter than our today
Seriousness... It'll only make us keep fighting even harder
We'll always get as fascinated as we want, and we'll fight on every day
During our clash with our old nemesis Kaito,
a back-and-forth Duel commences with both sides using their full strength.
Who will the Goddess of Victory smile upon?
So this is Kaito when he's serious! If we let our guard down for a moment, we'll lose!
Yuma, let's come at him with all we've got!
He's using the same strategy I am!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"The Dream Grand Clash!
Double Hope vs Double Galaxy-Eyes!"
We'll both bring it to each other!
Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal powers up this October!
A new enemy has come from the Barian World!
The title will be "Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal II!"
It starts broadcasting October 7th, 5:30 PM!