A star has come to our town!
His name is Different Dimension ESPer Robin.
However, Robin's actor, Fuya, isn't that kind of guy at all.
He played Robin to live up to his mother's expectations,
But he became the real Robin instead!
Fuya.
I'll definitely free you from your curse!
I will end my turn like this.
Fuya...
Galaxy Queen...!
It's best for you to live your life protecting Robin's image.
No one can save me from this...
Fuya...
This Numbers...
It's exactly what's in your heart, isn't it?
That's it!
Yuma?
What's the matter, Yuma? At this hour..
Kotori! It's an emergency.
Go get Tetsuo and bring Fuya's mother over here!
Huh?
Right now Fuya,
No, I mean.. I'm dueling with Robin.
She has to watch this duel, no matter what!
Yuma...
Okay, I got it.
I'm counting on you, Kotori!
Fuya...
I'll bring you back to normal for sure!
I'm gonna bring it to you!
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
A battle with invincible monsters!?
How can Yuma save Robin like this!
Yuma.
Star Robin will inflict piercing damage until the next turn.
"Numbers 8:
Star Robin is Forever"
In order to avoid Robin's attack,
there's no choice but to use Aspiring Emperor - Hope's effect.
Of course I know that!
But for summoning Hope,
I only have one level 4 monster in my hand.
My next draw... I'm betting everything on it!
My turn!
Draw!
I got it!
Alright, let's go!
I summon Gagaga Magician!
And then, I special summon Shadow Lizard!
Although Shadow Lizard can't be normal summoned,
When a level 4 monster is summoned, I can special summon it from my hand!
I overlay my level 4 monsters, Gagaga Magician and Shadow Lizard!
I use these two Monsters to construct the Overlay network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear! Numbers 39, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!!
Yuma.
We have to defeat our enemies one by one, regardless of numbers.
I got it already!
However, Galaxy Queen can't be destroyed, due to the effect of Dead Max's Cursed Seal.
Huh? What's the matter?
Today you sure are awfully straight forward.
You idiot! I'm dueling for Fuya's sake!
I don't have time to argue with you.
I agree as well.
You on the other hand,
Isn't it rare for you to duel for someone else's sake?
He is very lonely.
No one can save me from this...
Somehow, I can understand that feeling.
You...
One way or another, in this duel,
Looks like we have the same goals.
Don't kid yourself!
Even if we have the same goal, I am who I am!
Let's win.
Right!
Go, Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Attack Beast Warrior Puman!
How naive!
Trap activate, Wings of Unity!
It's useless.
Trap card, Wings of Unity's effect,
When Star Robin is on my side of the field,
When my opponent participates in battle, that attack is negated.
And then, I special summon Phoenix Beast Galeruda!
He special summoned a Level 6 monster?!
Is everyone alright?
You're finally here!
You're late, Galeruda!
Seems like I finally made it.
What's with that monster?
Are they acting out the same scene from TV?
No way...
I can't believe I'm seeing this with my own eyes...
However, you should have gone back to the princess..
Hmph! There is no way I will leave you guys behind here!
Galeruda! Puman!
Robin!
Somehow...
Such fierce bonds!
I'm not quite sure what's happening, but...
My heart is all fired up.
Now is not the time to admire them!
He not only managed to stop my attack,
and now the guy's got 4 monsters on the field!
Then through the effect of Phoenix Beast Galeruda, I draw one card from the deck!
Damn it...
The only thing I can do right now...
Right now we must defend.
From your hand, we'll bet on that card on the right.
This one?
Not really sure what's going on, but...
I set one card face down.
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
Next, I'll summon another one of my allies!
What, another?!
When Star Robin, Beastial Warrior Puman and Phoenix Beast Galeruda are on my field,
I can special summon this card from my hand!
This is the grand banquet from my allies!
Come out! Iron Giant, Ironhammer!
W-What?!
You're here, Ironhammer!
Iron Giant, Ironhammer.
About to be thrown away for a missing screw on his head,
He's the ironplate warrior who was saved by Robin!
As long as I am here, don't even think about touching Robin!
3500 Defense Points...?!
Can I really defeat that...?
Yuma!
We brought her!
It's Fuya-kun's mother!
This is, just what in the world...
That's...
Fuya?
Fuya...
Is that really Fuya?
What on earth are you doing?
Fuya!
You there, who are you?
What are you saying?
I am your mother!
You, my mother?
Such ridiculous words.
My mother is right here.
Fuya...
I'm not this Fuya person you speak of.
I am Different Dimension ESPer Robin!
H-How can this be?
Fuya's mom!
The incident's real culprit is Fuya...
No, it's Robin!
T-That's... nonsense!
To answer his mother's expectations,
He worked hard with all his strength!
Huh?
To achieve that, he's trapped in the haction world with no return!
"Haction"?
Could he mean... Fiction?
Oh...
How can this be... Fuya!
Robin, it's best if you forever lived under my glory of darkness!
Is that how I've been acting?
Fuya, please listen to me!
Stop it already!
Please, just be quiet and watch this duel.
The figure of his mother in Fuya's heart!
We shall continue the duel.
By removing one Overlay Unit, I activate Galaxy Queen's effect once more!
Before my next turn, monsters on my field not only becomes invincible,
Their attack will also inflict piercing damage!
Now, Star Robin and his comrades,
You shall receive my magic once more!
Finish off the enemy who stands in your way!
I understand!
I activate the effect of Galeruda!
When Galeruda attacks, its ATK is increased by 300!
Go, attack Aspiring Emperor Hope!
Yuma!
I got it already!
By removing one Overlay Unit,
I activate Aspiring Emperor - Hope's effect!
Galeruda's attack is negated!
However, I still have my remaining attacks!
Take this!
This is the grand banquet of battles!
Star Robin, attack Aspiring Emperor - Hope!
Surprise Punch!!
I activate Hope's effect once more!
That attack is also negated!
But now, Hope has no more overlay units!
Looks like your banquet went overboard!
And then, I activate the effect of Iron Giant Ironhammer!
When Ironhammer is on my field,
Once per turn, one of my level 4 or lower monsters can attack directly!
What!?
Go, Puman!
Direct Attack!!
Black Slash!!
Yuma!
Damn it!
At this rate...
Yuma, activate the trap card.
Trap card?
Believe in me!
Geez...
Trap card activate!
Trap card, Sorrowful Appeal's effect,
When the opponent attacked directly and inflicted damage,
Take control of the highest defense monster on the opponent's field, until the end of my next turn!
Ironhammer, have you betrayed us?
Its nothing like that!
But, I don't want to defeated by such a weakling!
Hey...
Can't be helped.
I set one card face down.
Turn end.
However, why did you take Ironhammer?...
Ironhammer will go back to Robin's field, during his next turn.
That's good enough.
No, I should say,
If we want to beat him, this is the only way.
I don't get it at all...
Speaking of which,
You watched the show, right?
So what happened in the end?
The ending of that episode...
You still remember?
I couldn't see it because you turned off the TV.
So it's my fault?
My turn!
Draw!
Only in this duel, giving up is not an option.
Fuya...
I will surely...
I activate the continuous magic, Attack Regulation!
The effect of this card, when there are three or more monsters on the opponent's side of the field,
My opponent cannot declare an attack!
In any case, this will buy me some time.
Yuma!
What is it?
With this, the pieces to our victory is complete.
Let's win.
Ha?! We'll win?
Galaxy Queen can't be destroyed due to Dead Max's Cursed Seal's effect.
And thanks to the effect of Galaxy Queen's overlay units,
All of his monster becomes invincible!
I saw it!
When Robin Family is all together,
Robin will change Ironhammer into Different Dimension Jet Iron Mode,
And using its special attack, Iron Phoenix to crush the opponent.
You stupid Robin otaku!
Yuma.
Set down the two cards in your hand.
These cards?
I really don't like your orders, but..
I set two cards face down.
Turn end!
Useless struggle...
My turn!
Draw!
And now, your trap card's effect is now over.
Ironhammer will returns to my side of the field.
Huh? what on Earth just happened?
Star Robin!
Those guys are unforgivable!
I understand, mother!
That's enough!
Please, Fuya!
Silence!
I am Robin!
I must to carry on my existence as Robin!
Fuya...
Since you're planning to use Attack Regulations to seal off my attacks,
I activate a trap card!
Change! Jet Iron Mode!
When Robin Family is gathered on my side of the field,
By releasing all of them,
this card's effect can special summon Different Dimension Jet Iron Mode!
Come out, Jet Iron Mode!!
W-What's this?!
Different Dimension Jet Iron Mode,
His attack power is the sum of ATK of monsters released by Change Jet Iron Mode.
Because of that, its attack power is 8000!
8000 Attack Power?!
Just how the heck do we win against that?
Don't panic.
The trap card.
Trap card?
Ah--! Which one to activate?
That's right!
At times like this,
I need the Duel Riceball!
Not again, Yuma..
Alright!
My brain is working again!
The card I will activate is,
the Trap card, Burning Spirit!
Awesome!
Hope's attack power is doubled!
But Iron Mode's attack power is 8000!
There's no point!
Now prepare yourself!
All of my monsters has merged into one!
Your Attack Regulation only activates when there's three or more monsters on my field.
That effect cannot be activated!
Damn...!
Trap activate!
Wha..
I'm the one who's gonna activate it!
Trap activate!
Training Cyclone!
Traing Cyclone's effect,
When control of a monster is switched to the opponent, and that card was released,
We can destroy one Magic or Trap card the opponent controls.
In other words, the card I will destroy...
Dead Max's Cursed Seal!!
What?
This way, the card that protects Galaxy Queen is gone.
However, my attack will not be stopped!
The grand banquet of special attack!
Attack Aspiring Emperor - Hope, Iron Mode!
Go, Iron Phoenix!!
I knew this wasn't enough...!
No, this is fine.
There's still one trap card left on your field.
Trap card..!
With this, the pieces to our victory is complete.
I see!
Back then, you already...
Let's go!
Trap, activate!
Different Dimension Killer Move - Vector Change!
This card's effect,
When an opponent's monster is attacking,
That monster is changed to defense position!
What!?
Then one of the opponent's face up defense position monster is changed to attack mode!
Impossible!
This way, I can't attack...
Mother...
I-I...
No, this isn't over!
I set one card face down.
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
Alright! If he attack Galaxy Queen right now,
Robin will be defeated!
Yuma. Have you prepared yourself?
If that card is a counter to the attack,
We will be...
But, this is our only chance at winning this duel.
The only chance to bring Fuya back to normal...
Alright.
Let's go !!
I'm gonna bring it to ya!!
Aspiring Emperor - Hope, attack Galaxy Queen!
Hope Sword Slash!!
I activate the trap card, Star Robin is Forever!!
What!? It's a counter?
With this card,
When my opponent attacks, I can bring back Star Robin with 0 ATK from my graveyard.
And he takes the place of the attacked monster!
He won! Yuma won!
That wasn't a counter.
But why?
Even if Star Robin came back to the field with 0 ATK,
The results did not changed at all.
Why do something so meaningless?
It wasn't meaningless.
Fuya was protecting.
Protecting his mother...
This memory...
Fuya!
Fuya.
Mother!
What in the world was I...
That's...That's enough, Fuya.
To let you carry that much burden...
Mother...
I was mistaken.
I'm sorry.
Mother...
Mom...
Heh! Somehow, I'm pretty jealous!
This way, that guy can finally return to his true self.
But Yuma,
Why didn't you tell us about Robin sooner?
But you'd be disappointed, right?
If you found out Robin was the real culprit.
I didn't know you cared a little, too!
It's not like I c-care that much!!
You idiot!
What do you mean, idiot?
You are not delicate at all!
What do you mean, "delivery"?
Hey now...
In the end, isn't this all because you are a die-hard Robin fan?
Impossible! My powers...
Robin.
Mother...
Mother...!
Such a good episode, right?
Right?
Observation #10.
"I have come to comprehend human maternal love."
I think...
That memory of mine...
That's...
The memory of my birth...
Your name is... Astral.
Your mission, and the future of our world... It is entrusted to you...
Let's begin the Duel!
A monster is face-up when it's Normal Summoned in Attack Position.
Then, what about Defense Position? Is it face-up, or face-down?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
Ah--!!
Say what?!
Kotori was kidnapped?!
And she'll be freed when I win the Duel?
Could it be... the work of one of the Numbers?
Numbers or not, it doesn't matter!
Kotori, I'll save you for sure!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh! ZeXal!
"Cat Surprise - Cat Deck!?"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is... Face-down!
Not only face-down, but set horizontal as well!
It's easy to get wrong, so be careful!
No. 83, Galaxy Queen!
She makes her allies invincible with piercing effect!