It's useless...
I can see right through your heart as if it were lying in the palm of my hand.
Now show me your strength.
The power of those abominable Numbers!
Damn!
Go, No. 16 Shock Ruler!
Who the hell are you!?
My name is Jin.
A Numbers Hunter, and Kaito-sama's loyal servant.
Kaito!?
I will be taking your soul!
I'll bring it to em'!
Alright! I ain't late today!
With the new cards in this strengthened deck, I'll get my revenge on Kaito for sure!
What's with the gloomy face?
I can't do it after all...
Yuma, you and I are just different...
What are you talking about?
That goes without saying.
Yuma!
G-Good Morning!
Forget "good morning"...
Just come here for a bit!
You're going to explain yourself clearly today!
What's the big deal all of a sudden?
What's this!?
I found them on the net.
Lately, there has been an incident involving duelists being assaulted.
And it said that all of them had Numbers cards.
N-Numbers!?
In summary, you might know something about them.
So there was an incident like that happening?
I had no clue.
Don't play dumb!
Tell us the truth!
Aren't Numbers dangerous?
I-I really don't know!
Yuma!
I-I'm going to the toilet!
Hey Yuma!
Yuma...
Yuma, why didn't you tell them the truth?
It's obvious...
They can't know that I lost the battle against Kaito.
Kaito...
That Kaito seems to be looking for Numbers again.
Then we're gonna take the Numbers back from him!
He's not the type that you can win against by thinking of it.
Could you be scared of Kaito?
It's okay to be scared.
You can only regain your memory by beating Kaito and by gathering the Numbers, right?
What happens if we lose!?
Your soul will be taken and I will be annihilated from this world!
Why are you talking about such a dreadful thing-?
Good Morning...
Good Morning, em-uh C-Cat-chan!
You remembered me...
Who is Kaito?
This is bad! Excuse me, I'm gonna bust open!
Kaito? Numbers...?
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
they're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
The kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
The truth is, I was lonely. Until I met you.
I lied to myself that being alone was easier.
My favorite books and hobbies,
they don't seem to match.
You were the only one to nod in agreement with me.
Happiness and sadness and anger and
Do and Re and Mi and Fa and So and La and Ti and Do,
It doesn't work unless they're different,
the harmony and the scenario.
No one is exactly the same,
because that's the reason for living.
Even if the sounds are dissonant from time to time,
don't give up on the strength that will get you through.
When we reach the edge of the world,
the view we see will be the truth.
Whether it's rainy, or windy,
or a cold winter blizzard, or the burning sun,
They're all ingredients to color each day.
Don't lose heart, will or love.
the kindness you gave me was strict,
when we clashed I learned irritation.
It starts by recognizing our differences, dancing freely,
the creation of Heaven and Earth.
Numbers 17
"Numbers 17: The All-Seeing Seer:
The Terrifying Fortuneteller - Jin"
Kaito-sama, now you have a new Numbers power.
I was chosen by you, Kaito-sama!
I have gotten all of these just for you.
I can see it all.
I can see that my fortune-telling skills will help me get additional Numbers.
I'm going ahead!
Yuma, wait!
Sorry, Grandma wants me to do something!
Later!
Geez, he ran away again!
Kotori, we have a good idea.
The Numbers Club?
Yeah, we'll combine our efforts to solve the mystery of Numbers.
To summarize, If Yuma-kun doesn't wanna talk, we'll look for clues ourselves!
This is interesting ~ura!
Is it okay for me to enter this Numbers Club ~ura?
Tokunosuke!
That's right, you did have a Numbers, now didn't you?
That's correct ~ura!
And after holding a Numbers, your memory is...
Your memory is...?
I can't remember anything ~ura!
You...
E-Em...
I would also like to enter the Numbers Club.
Well uh...
I saw him... Yuma was talking to someone alone.
Could it be Astral?
What was he talking about?
About Numbers and about beating Kaito...
Kaito? Who is that?
Could he be related to these incidents?
Alright, let's all go search for clues.
That's right.
The five of us are in this Numbers Club!
Let's do it! Yeah!
If I know something, Yuma will acknowledge me!
So please!
To summarize, I hate things that cannot be explained logically.
I must find something about the Numbers!
"If we have the Numbers in our hands"
"Where are they, where are they now?"
"We'll show you for sure that we can"
"That we can make it all clear"
Hey...
You want to know about the Numbers?
Shark...
Hey, could you tell me anything about the Numbers?
Those cards aren't for people like you guys.... no, or even me for that matter, to be using.
What do you mean by that?
Don't involve yourself with the Numbers.
How did it go?
Nothing...
Same for me...
Didn't find nothin'!
To summarize, we couldn't find any clues!
You're naive ~ura!
You can't find intel in the revealed world.
Follow me, everyone, as I lead you to the hidden world.
This place...
Deep in the hidden world lies an old mansion where there are rumors of fortune telling.
Fortune telling?
He's sure to know something about the Numbers~ura!
To summarize, he's not your average person.
I have been awaiting your arrival.
Fate has brought you all here in my mansion.
You stray lambs...
My powers will lead you to the correct road you're seeking.
U-Um...
I saw it all.
You guys are investigating something, am I correct?
Do you know about it?
Of course I do!
The thing you guys are searching for...
It's here, and it's very thin...
About some card, huh?
They aren't just normal cards.
They hide some special powers.
These cards are from Duel Monsters...
The Numbers!
Yo-You're kidding!
We didn't even say a word about the Numbers!
I-Is this some kind of hidden trick?
What's that mean~ura?! There's no hidden trick behind it at all~ura!
Hey, just what do you know about the Numbers?
Numbers are wicked beings.
Wicked?
Those who posses the Numbers have their hearts taken from them.
And they also have their souls stolen from them!
Yuma is...
His soul...?
Did you just say Yuma?
My friend Yuma may not know that the Numbers are dangerous...
That's why we're trying to solve the mysteries of the Numbers.
I see, thank you for telling me this.
I'm worried about Yuma.
That your dear friend is a proprietor of the Numbers cards...
This is all an act of fate.
H-Hey Kotori!
I will make you guys into scapegoats!
You're upset again? How many times does this make today?
Geez, next time there will be a penalty for you!
Yuma!
Cat-chan!
Everyone has... Everyone has...
What's the matter? What happened?
Kotori has... Everyone has...
Hey Cat-chan! Hey!
The one who possesses the Numbers!
T-This voice...
My name is Jin.
The all seeing one!
Kaito-sama's loyal servant!
Kaito!?
Dear Yuma, I'm keeping your friends in custody.
Come at me and duel me with the Numbers at stake!
If you don't their lives are...
Cat-chan!
Cat...
Yuma! What was I...?
Cat-chan, lead me there!
I understand!
Wait a bit!
This is a trap!
In the case she was sent here as a way to lure us to them...
So what if it's a trap?
Why are you scared?
Kotori and the others are in danger.
But can you beat Kaito?
His strategies... His strength...
I saw it all in that duel!
Right now we cant win the fight.
So you won't duel someone if you're not 100% sure you'll win?
That's right.
My duel is for me staying alive.
Fighting your opponent and knowing that you're going lose is just foolish.
Why you!
I'm sorry, but you're going to have to give up on your friends.
STOP KIDDING ME!!
Yuma...
I get it, I now get what you feel.
I'll never borrow your strength again!
To summarize, where is this place!?
Help us ~ura!
Everyone, hang in there.
Kotori!
Could it be Yuma?
Yuma...
Kotori!
That is...
Tetsuo... Everyone...!
Welcome, Yuma-kun!
The one who possesses the Numbers!
This voice...
Bring Kotori and the others back, you jerk!
If you desire to save your friends, then duel me.
Kaito-sama is watching.
K-Kaito!
Astral?
Kaito-sama!
I will take away his Numbers for you, Kaito-sama!
What did you say!?
I'll take those Numbers of yours away!
Just fine!
I'll definitely win and save everyone!
Duel Disk, set!
D-Gazer, set!
Target lock-on!
AR vision - link established.
Duel!!
I'll have the first move!
It's my turn, Draw!
I summon Orange Shaman!
A monster with 0 attack power?
Then I set a card face-down and end my turn!
Here I go! My turn, Draw!
I summon Gogogo Golem!
How's that!?If you take his attack, you'll receive great damage in one blow!
I activate Orange Shaman's effect!
If the opponent summon an effect monster, I can Special Summon a "Shaman" monster from my hand!
Appear before me! Red Shaman!
Alright!
Another one with 0 attack power?
Be careful, Yuma!
What are you saying?
With their attack powers being 0, it's a change to deal great damage!
Go, Gogogo Golem!
Trap Card open! Dance of the Divine Protector!
This card, I chose a card from the opponent's  hand, and if it's a monster then the attack is negated!
I can see through everything!
Don't think you can fool me, you can't do such a thing!
Yuma, watch out!
You have 5 cards in your hand.
And only 1 among them is a monster card.
That card is the second to the right!
What!?
At this moment. due to Dance of the Divine Protector's effect the selected card goes to the cemetery and I can draw one more card!
Gagaga Magician was sent to the cemetery?
Could he have seen through it?
He only had 1 monster card in his hand.
As I though this guy, has some special powers given to him by Kaito.
Damn it, at this rate...
Yuma, protect it!
You must protect the Trap in the hand!
I don't have any choice now.
I set a card face-down and end my turn!
It's my turn, Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Shaman Call!
This, card If I have 2 Spellcaster-type monsters with 0 attack powers on my field,
I can Special Summon a level 4 or lower "Shaman" from my deck!
I Special Summon Green Shaman!
What!?
This is, why he continued to summon monsters with 0 attack powers.
Witness...
My No.'s strength!
I overlay the level 4 Orange Shaman, Red Shaman and Green Shaman!
The 3 monsters will open the Overlay Network!
Xyz Summon!
Appear No. 16!
Ruler of Color...
Shock Ruler!
This is his No.
I activate Shock Ruler's effect!
Once per turn, by detaching an Overlay Unit,
I declare 1 card type, and that type of card's effect negated until the opponent's second End Phase!
Has it's effect negated!?
Right, The card I declare can't be used for 2 turns!
I can see through it!
The type of the card your face-down is!
This is bad!
Your face-down is a Trap Card isn't it?
No way!
Now your attack negating chance is gone.
Shock Ruler, attack Gogogo Golem!
The lives of your friends depends on your life!
If you lose, everything will break and fall apart!
They will cry to death in the magma!!
What!?
Now before my strength...
Begone before Kaito-sama!
I'll take away your soul!
Go! Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon!
Astral!
It's... over...
I see, I'll afraid of Kaito.
Is this the feeling called "fear"?
Let's begin dueling!
Question of the week:
Does a used Magic Card go to your cemetery? Or does it go back to your hand?
Today's test is hard. I can't divide myself from pleasure and temptation.
I wanna watch TV when I get home.
The recent anime are fun.
In any case, this test is hard.
Language, Math and English are especially bad.
I'm only average at science and social studies.
The only thing I'm good at is P.E.
(Wait up, Baby!) For who's sake...
(Is that, Baby!) ...am I remembering...
(Just hold on, Baby!) ...the answer...
(What are we!? Baby!) ...they wanted?
Even if I write the correct answer on this paper,
in one year, in ten years, will anything change?
The world I drew in the corner of my dreams,
one day I will race through the open sky.
No one can blame this heart of mine.
Nothing is really correct!
The man who can see through everything, Jin.
My duel has reach a desperate situation!
What?! If I surrender, Kotori and others’ lives can be spared?
Yuma, don’t do it!
Just give the Numbers and myself to them!
Cut it out!
I want to win, for you, and your friends!
Next time on Yu-Gi-Oh ZeXal!
"Chaos Xyz Change, the Light of Hope Hope Ray!"
I'm gonna bring it to 'em!
The answer is it's sent to the graveyard!
Same as magic cards, trap cards will be sent to the graveyard after use as well. Keep that in mind, everyone!